[{"value": {"id": 1752835, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22144", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of deportations between 4 July and 31 December were (a) enforced and (b) voluntary.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["22140"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 491, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Home Office routinely publishes data on returns in the \u201cImmigration Systems Statistics\u201d quarterly release. Data on quarterly returns of individuals since July 2024 can be found in table Ret_D01 of the \u201creturns detailed datasets\u201d.The next full quarterl...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Deportation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "22140", "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752835", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752829, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22140", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many voluntary deportations took place between 4 July and 31 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["22144"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 491, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Home Office routinely publishes data on returns in the \u201cImmigration Systems Statistics\u201d quarterly release. Data on quarterly returns of individuals since July 2024 can be found in table Ret_D01 of the \u201creturns detailed datasets\u201d.The next full quarterl...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Deportation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "22144", "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752829", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753159, "askingMemberId": 4357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22269", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of mandating socioeconomic background reporting for all employers with over 250 employees.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4418, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department has not undertaken any such assessment. Companies are already required to disclose employee matters and can choose to include socioeconomic aspects where relevant to their business. For example, all large companies in the UK must include in...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment: Social Class", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753159", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752682, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21986", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on introducing more flexible paternity leave.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4418, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government is committed to ensuring that employed parents receive the best possible support to balance their work and family responsibilities.The Employment Rights Bill will increase the flexibility of Paternity Leave. This Bill will make Paternity Le...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Paternity Leave", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752682", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752863, "askingMemberId": 4673, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22068", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the Digital Markets Unit can make effective market interventions.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4418, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "On 1 January the pro-competition regime for digital markets entered into force. The Competition and Markets Authority (CMA) will operate the regime, as the UK\u2019s principal independent competition regulator. The Government has designed and implemented the r...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Digital Markets Unit", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752863", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752495, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21754", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will commission a national inquiry into rape gangs.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4370, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government is committed to using every lever to ensure all children are protected from sexual exploitation and abuse across our communities and online, regardless of who is perpetrating that horrific abuse. We are committed to continuing to learn from...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rape: Inquiries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752495", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752362, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21819", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to support people who are out of work but not receiving employment support.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4083, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "As part of the biggest reforms in a generation, DWP will shift from being a department for welfare to being a department for work. The Get Britain Working White Paper published in November set out plans to deliver fundamental reform of our health, employm...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Unemployment: Government Assistance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752362", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752478, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21923", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to help reduce the level of dependence on emergency food parcels.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4083, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "We are committed to tackling poverty and reducing mass dependence on emergency food parcels. On 30 July, the Secretary of State held a food poverty roundtable with key food poverty stakeholders to understand the key priorities in this area. We know that g...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Poverty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752478", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752342, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21654", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many youth hubs led by her Department are still in place.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4083, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "Youth Hubs bring together employment support from a Jobcentre work coach alongside external partners on external-partner premises for up to six months. Wider support available from partners in the Hubs is place-based, but could include skills and training...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Young Futures Hubs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752342", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752344, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21656", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress her Department's appointed menopause champion has made.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4083, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government\u2019s Menopause Employment Ambassador Mariella Frostrup has been working with policy officials to develop an action plan for her term of engagement. She has also spoken with government departments to promote and champion the role of women in th...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Menopause: Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752344", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752506, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21778", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether he has had recent discussions with the Northern Ireland Executive on the adequacy of road safety measures in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 413, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government regularly engages with the Northern Ireland Executive on the importance of infrastructure investment in Northern Ireland, including the road and transport network. Responsibility for road safety measures is devolved to Northern Ireland\u2019s De...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Roads: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752506", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752475, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21920", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she plans to publish research on the (a) Midlife MOT initiative and (b) digital Midlife MOT website.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4083, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Midlife MOT initiative consists of three key work strands: the Job Centre Plus (JCP) Midlife MOT, the Private Sector Midlife MOT and the Digital Midlife MOT. The Private Sector Midlife MOT pilot programmes concluded at the end of June 2024. Findings f...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Advisory Services: Older Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752475", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752505, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21777", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to allow up-to date medical information to be shared between the NHS and care staff in (a) Newcastle-under-Lyme constituency and (b) Staffordshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "At a national level, in partnership with NHS England, the Department is building the foundations for improved information sharing between care and health staff. Digital social care records, that contain a person\u2019s care information, are now in use by more ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Medical Records: Staffordshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752505", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752343, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21655", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress her Department has made on rolling out youth hubs.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4083, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "As of January 2025, there were 111 Youth Hubs fully opened across Great Britain with a further three in development. Youth Hubs are based in external-partner-owned premises. Local DWP teams and external partners delivering Youth Hubs jointly discuss the o...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Young Futures Hubs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752343", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752509, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21781", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children deemed to be at risk of abuse or neglect are home schooled in (a) Staffordshire and (b) England.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4653, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The department collects data on children in elective home education (EHE) from local authorities. The latest data, including at the local authority level, is published here:  https://explore-education-statistics.service.gov.uk/find-statistics/elective-hom...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752509", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752338, "askingMemberId": 5073, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21730", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of the availability of fire safety risk assessors who are able to carry out fire risk assessments of external wall systems.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4641, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department conducts regular capacity surveys and supplier engagement to ensure we have enough assessors to meet the expected requirement, in line with our objective in the Department\u2019s Remediation Acceleration plan to ensure capacity in the remediatio...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Buildings: Fire Prevention", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752338", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752455, "askingMemberId": 5275, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21884", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when she plans to announce the outcome of the consultation on cultural funding for the City of Dunfermline.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4641, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The consultation for this funding launched on 31 October with a deadline for responses by 13 December. Returns are being carefully considered. In line with our expectations that the process would take approximately 12 weeks, we hope to communicate a decis...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Culture: Dunfermline", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752455", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752371, "askingMemberId": 5263, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21869", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to expedite the removal and remediation of dangerous cladding on properties; and what steps she plans to take to ensure that properties that previously q", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4641, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Remediation Acceleration Plan (RAP) sets out key measures to fix buildings faster, identify remaining buildings still at risk and ensure that residents are supported through the remediation process.No leaseholder in a high-rise residential building sh...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Insulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752371", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752365, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21933", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department plans to take to tackle private parking companies issuing penalties to customers for taking too long to purchase a ticket due to (a) queues at the parki", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4641, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government is committed to driving up standards across the private parking sector for the benefit of motorists.The Parking (Code of Practice) Act 2019 places a duty on the Government to prepare a code of practice containing guidance about the operatio...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parking: Private Sector", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752365", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752331, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21595", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what representations his Department has received from the Government of Mauritius on the UK and Mauritius Joint Statement on the exercise of sovereignty over the Chagos Archi", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4264, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Governments of the UK and Mauritius issued a joint statement on 20 December setting out their continued commitment to finalising a treaty as quickly as possible, which will ensure the long-term, secure and effective operation of the existing base on D...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "British Indian Ocean Territory: Sovereignty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752331", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752212, "askingMemberId": 4869, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21708", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the increase to employers' National Insurance contributions will be covered in full for schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4125, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The government has agreed that public sector employers will receive compensation in recognition of the increase in their National Insurance contributions (NICs). That compensation will be additional to the \u00a32.3 billion increase to the core schools budget ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Employers' Contributions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752212", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752558, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21963", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has had discussions with the Leader of the House on scheduling a parliamentary debate on compensation for women affected by changes to the state pension age.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4077, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Sir John Hayes MP (Conservative, South Holland and The Deepings) has secured a Westminster Hall general debate on the topic of \u2018Compensation for women affected by changes to the State Pension age\u2019 on Wednesday 15 January 2025.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "State Retirement Pensions: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752558", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752290, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21576", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has changed the recipients by position entitled to pre-release access to reports since June 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5305, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Minister for Cabinet Office has not made any changes to pre-release access to official statistics since 5 July 2024. ", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Disclosure of Information", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752290", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752370, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21934", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of providing the Environment Agency with ring-fenced funding from the proceeds of fines placed on water companies for breachin", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4645, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Water (Special Measures) Bill will deliver on the Government\u2019s commitment to put water companies under special measures. It will drive meaningful improvements in the performance and culture of the water industry as a first important step in enabling w...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sewage: Waste Disposal", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752370", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752300, "askingMemberId": 4735, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21668", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of hydrogen blending in the transmission network.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4631, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government remains committed to assessing the case for hydrogen blending. In December 2024 we set out an intention to consult on transmission-level blending within Great Britain in early 2025, to gather evidence to help inform a strategic policy decis...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Natural Gas: Hydrogen", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752300", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752269, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21632", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2024 to Question 15453 on Local Government: Accountability, if she will take steps to make the data published under the Transparency Code mo", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4569, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "We are keeping the Code under review in the context of work to fix the foundations of local government and ensuring that it continues to support local accountability. Our approach to reforming local government is set out in the English Devolution White Pa...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Accountability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752269", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752914, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22230", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2024 to Question 19860, Prisons: Repairs and Maintenance, whether the expected performance parameters of private sector providers have changed since these contracts were awar", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4056, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The performance parameters of private sector providers are subject to ongoing contract management and are reviewed and, where appropriate, changed to align with the business requirements.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisons: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752914", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752913, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22229", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2024 to Question 19860 on Prisons: Repairs and Maintenance, if she will publish the 2023 assessment.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4056, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The assessment carried out in partnership with the Cabinet Office in 2023, was conducted in line with Cabinet Office guidance and was consistent with the options appraisal approach prescribed by HM Treasury. The information contained within the assessment...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisons: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752913", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752696, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22153", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will have discussions with Transport for London on mitigation of the potential impact of fare increases on commuters in London in March 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4943, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "Transport in London is devolved and decisions on TfL fares are for the Mayor of London and TfL. Department for Transport ministers and officials speak regularly with TfL on a wide range of issues impacting commuters in the capital.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Commuters: Greater London", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752696", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752410, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21809", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of bus services in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4943, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "Good local bus services have an essential role to play in keeping rural communities connected. The government introduced the Bus Services (No.2) Bill on 17 December as part of its ambitious plan for bus reform. The Bill puts the power over local bus servi...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bus Services: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752410", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752320, "askingMemberId": 5125, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21747", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many departmental bids have been (a) received and (b) approved by the Northern Ireland Public Sector Transformation Board.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 413, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "Following the establishment of an Interim Public Sector Transformation Board in May 2024, the interim Board ran a process to consider the 47 proposals which were received from Northern Ireland Departments. The Interim Board has recommended several proposa...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Northern Ireland Public Sector Transformation Board", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752320", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752411, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21810", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of changes to the bus fare cap on trends in the level of bus users.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4943, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The government is investing over \u00a3150 million to deliver the new \u00a33 cap on single bus fares in England outside London from 1 January until 31 December 2025. Under the plans of the previous administration, the \u00a32 cap on bus fares had been due to expire on ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bus Services: Fares", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752411", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752538, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21903", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will take steps to improve public transportation to help people stay connected with communities.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4943, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The government knows that a modern public transport network is vital to providing access to services and keeping communities connected. The government introduced the Bus Services (No.2) Bill on 17 December to put the power over local bus services back int...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Transport: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752538", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752378, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21836", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation entitled Investigation into suspected anti-competitive conduct by Vifor Pharma in relation to intravenous iron tre", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4418, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Competition and Markets Authority (CMA) is the UK's independent competition authority, and its consultations, including the live consultation relating to commitments offered by Vifor Pharma (https://www.gov.uk/government/consultations/consultation-on-...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "CSL Vifor", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752378", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752890, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22177", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of influenza cases in hospitals in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The UK Health Security Agency (UKHSA) surveillance of influenza hospitalisations operates during winter season only, where most influenza activity is typically observed. Trends vary across the season and are published weekly at the following link:https://...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Influenza", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752890", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752699, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22156", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the NHS is taking to improve the accuracy of tests used by GPs to diagnose chronic urinary tract infections.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "Diagnostic tests for chronic urinary tract infections (UTIs), such as urinalysis and urine culture, are widely available across all pathology networks in England. Ensuring accurate diagnostic testing not only aids more effective identification of infectio...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Urinary Tract Infections: Screening", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752699", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752908, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22238", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions his Department has had with public health officials on adverse side effects to the Covid-19 vaccine.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "Each COVID-19 vaccine candidate is assessed by teams of scientists and clinicians on a case-by-case basis, and only authorised once it has met robust standards of effectiveness, safety, and quality set by the United Kingdom\u2019s independent medicines\u2019 regula...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coronavirus: Vaccination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752908", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752369, "askingMemberId": 5323, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21916", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing a hub and spoke model to community pharmacy.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government is working towards introducing legislation to enable hub and spoke dispensing between different legal entities this year. This change will be enabled via amendments to both primary and secondary legislation and is subject to the usual parli...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pharmacy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752369", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752288, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21574", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of spending on mental health services for children and young people in each year for which data are available.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The following table shows actual spend on children and young people\u2019s mental health by clinical commissioning groups and integrated care boards: Financial yearAmount (\u00a3 million)2017/18687.22018/19753.32019/20841.42020/21938.32021/22994.82022/231,087.70202...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health Services: Children and Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752288", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752532, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21897", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that social care services are adequately funded to support individuals experiencing loneliness.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "Loneliness and social isolation can affect many people and impact on their health and wellbeing. The Government\u2019s current work to tackle loneliness includes: supporting a range of organisations through the Tackling Loneliness Hub, an online platform for p...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Loneliness: Social Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752532", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752880, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22172", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many of the planned additional 700,000 urgent dental appointments a year will be in (a) Bedfordshire and (b) the East of England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government is committed to tackling the challenges for patients trying to access National Health Service dental care. We are working to ensure patients can start to access 700,000 additional urgent dental appointments as soon as possible, targeting ar...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: East of England", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752880", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752489, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21949", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the backlog of people waiting for NHS dental appointments in North Cornwall constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21948"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "This Government plans to tackle the challenges for patients trying to access National Health Service dental care with a rescue plan to provide 700,000 more urgent dental appointments and recruit new dentists to areas that need them most. To rebuild dentis...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: North Cornwall", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21948", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752489", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752488, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21948", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to make NHS dental care more accessible for people in North Cornwall constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21949"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "This Government plans to tackle the challenges for patients trying to access National Health Service dental care with a rescue plan to provide 700,000 more urgent dental appointments and recruit new dentists to areas that need them most. To rebuild dentis...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: North Cornwall", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21949", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752488", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752772, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22020", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 28 of the policy paper entitled Plan for Change: Milestones for mission-led government, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, whether his Department plans to measure the succ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "We are committed to moving towards a Neighbourhood Health Service, with more care delivered in local communities to spot problems earlier, supporting people to stay healthier and maintain their independence for longer.We recognise the need for robust eval...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752772", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752881, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22173", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what criteria he uses for defining whether an area is a dental desert; and in what areas dentistry graduates will receive golden hellos.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "\u2018Dental desert\u2019 is a term used colloquially to describe areas struggling with access to National Health Service dentistry. There are a range of metrics which can be used to assess dental access.The responsibility for commissioning primary care dentistry t...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752881", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752860, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22120", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to support healthcare providers to ensure (a) uninterrupted access to essential patient care and (b) maintain the stability of primary care services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "It is vital that patients can access primary care services when they need it.In October 2024, we provided an \u00a382 million boost to the Additional Roles Reimbursement Scheme, enabling the recruitment of 1,000 newly qualified general practitioners (GPs) acro...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752860", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752249, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21726", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will set targets to reduce memory clinic waiting times in (a) Torbay, (b) Exeter and (c) Barnstaple.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government is committed to transforming diagnostic services, including the detection and diagnosis of dementia, and will support the National Health Service to increase capacity to meet the demand for diagnostic services. We are committed to improving...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Memory Clinics: Devon", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752249", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752670, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22104", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of (a) supervisor and (b) designated prescribing practitioners.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "NHS England is investing in training for independent prescribers, as well as initiatives to support the development and safe practice of designated prescribing practitioners (DPPs) and educational supervisors. This will ensure the National Health Service ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prescriptions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752670", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753322, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22478", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will implement a measure for general practice and primary care comparable to that of the mental health investment standard.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "Primary care providers, including general practices (GPs), are valued independent contractors who provide almost \u00a320 billion worth of services in the National Health Service. Every year, we consult with each sector both about what services they provide, a...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners and Primary Health Care: Investment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753322", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752905, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22222", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of providing financial protection to victims of (a) financially coercive and (b) other controlling behaviour.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4849, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "This Government was elected with a landmark mission to halve violence against women and girls (VAWG) in the next decade. We will use every tool within our power to target perpetrators and address the root causes of abuse and violence, including domestic a...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Domestic Abuse", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752905", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753173, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22348", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the local disabled facilities grants.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "We are giving older and disabled people more independence in their own homes through an immediate in-year uplift to the Disabled Facilities Grant (DFG) of \u00a386 million in 2024/25. This increase will provide approximately 7,800 additional home adaptations. ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disabled Facilities Grants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753173", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752194, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21669", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, when he plans to respond to the correspondence of 2 October 2024 from the hon. Member for Twickenham on the reciprocity of aviation qualifications.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4631, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "A response was issued on 6 January.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Members: Correspondence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752194", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753167, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22347", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of (a) the average wages paid to social care sector workers and (b) the current number of vacancies in the sector.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "answerText": "Skills for Care reports that most care workers as the entry-level occupation are paid on or just above National Living Wage. Average or mean hourly pay for all workers in the sector was \u00a312.36 in March 2024. Skills for Care also reported that the overall ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Care Workers: Pay and Vacancies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753167", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752898, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22211", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the CQC's publication of 27 November 2024 entitled CQC finds improvement in CAMHS wards at Birmingham Women\u2019s and Children\u2019s NHS Foundation Trust, when the CQC plans to publish th", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Care Quality Commission (CQC) carried out an assessment of Child and Adolescent Mental Health wards at Birmingham Women\u2019s and Children\u2019s NHS Foundation Trust in September 2024. The report of that assessment was published on the CQC\u2019s website on 28 Nov...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health Services: Children and Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752898", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752784, "askingMemberId": 5116, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22159", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to increase the maximum application amount for the Disabled Facilities Grant.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "We are giving older and disabled people more independence in their own homes through an immediate in-year uplift to the Disabled Facilities Grant (DFG) of \u00a386 million in 2024/25. This increase will provide approximately 7,800 additional home adaptations. ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disabled Facilities Grants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752784", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753108, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22289", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the most recent quarterly Gross Domestic Product growth figures published by the Office of National Statistics on levels of available Overseas Development Aid ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4518, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "At Phase One of the 2025 Spending Review, departmental allocations for Official Development Assistance (ODA) were reset for 2024-25 and provided for 2025-26. As set out at Autumn Budget 2024, this settlement provides departments with \u00a313.3 billion of ODA ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Development Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753108", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753256, "askingMemberId": 5263, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22495", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department plans to review the Lifetime ISAs property price limit.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4518, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Data from the latest UK House Price Index) shows that while the average price paid by first-time buyers has increased, it is still below the LISA property price cap in all regions of the UK except for London, where the average price paid is affected by bo...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Individual Savings Accounts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753256", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752754, "askingMemberId": 4799, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22089", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will assess the effectiveness of the Eat Out to Help Out Scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4518, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Following the conclusion of the Eat Out Help Out scheme, HMRC published statistical analysis, which included data on scheme\u2019s costs, take up, and geographical breakdown. The Covid Inquiry is also investigating the UK\u2019s response to and impact of the Covid-...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Eat Out to Help Out Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752754", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752789, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22079", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of providing duty relief to brewers of cask conditioned beers.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4797, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Draught Relief provides a duty discount for eligible draught beer and cider. Cask conditioned beers will be able to benefit from Draught Relief if they are sold in a container of 20 litres or more, connected to a dispense system and are below 8.5 per cent...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Beer: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752789", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752735, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22076", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the her Department's consultation entitled Transforming business rates, published 30 October 2024, whether she plans to meet with (a) British Business Improvement Districts, (b) The BID Foundation ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4797, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "At Autumn Budget, the Government published a Discussion Paper setting out priority areas for reform of the business rates system. This paper invites industry to help co-design a fairer system that supports investment and is fit for the 21st century. Treas...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates: Public Consultation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752735", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752824, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22118", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of changing the climate change levy exemption for natural gas combined heat and power.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4797, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Climate Change Levy (CCL) is a tax on the supply of energy to businesses and the public sector, introduced in 2001 to encourage energy efficiency. There are a number of CCL exemptions and reliefs, including for energy used by members of the Combined H...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Combined Heat and Power: Climate Change Levy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752824", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752687, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22058", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an estimate of the number of working age people who have reduced their working hours as a result of marginal state income deductions.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4797, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Office for Budget Responsibility's October 2024 Economic and Fiscal Outlook (EFO) contains forecasts and assessments of government policy. Once the impact of all the Budget measures are taken into consideration, the OBR expect the employment level to ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Working Hours", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752687", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752456, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21944", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of (a) expanding the base money supply and (b) other alternative monetary policy.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4518, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Monetary policy is the responsibility of the independent Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) of the Bank of England. This includes decisions on Bank Rate and the stock of UK government bonds held in the Asset Purchase Facility. It is for the MPC to judge how ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Monetary Policy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752456", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752887, "askingMemberId": 5286, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22219", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of putting a cap on insurance costs for small businesses.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["22218"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4518, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Insurers make commercial decisions about the terms on which they will offer cover following an assessment of the relevant risks. This is usually informed by the insurer\u2019s claims experience and other industry-wide statistics. The Government does not usuall...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Small Businesses: Insurance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "22218", "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752887", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752885, "askingMemberId": 5286, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22218", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential implications for her policies of trends in the cost of insurance.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["22219"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4518, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Insurers make commercial decisions about the terms on which they will offer cover following an assessment of the relevant risks. This is usually informed by the insurer\u2019s claims experience and other industry-wide statistics. The Government does not usuall...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Insurance: Costs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "22219", "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752885", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752870, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22209", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average processing time was for applications to the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme by people resident in Birmingham in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4849, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The table below shows the average time for decisions to be made on applications* for criminal injuries compensation by people resident in Birmingham**. Calendar Year of CICA decisionAverage time (days)20203352021440202249020233812024372 * The table does n...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Criminal Injuries Compensation: Birmingham", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752870", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752837, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22145", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were prosecuted for the (a) creation, (b) distribution and (c) ownership of entirely AI-generated indecent images of children in 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["22143"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4849, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Ministry of Justice publishes data on prosecutions for a wide range of offences, including offences involving the possession, creation and distribution of indecent images of children. Data up to and including June 2024 is available in the Outcomes by ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Intimate Image Abuse: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "22143", "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752837", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752834, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22143", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) children and (b) adults were prosecuted for the creation of indecent images of (i) children and (ii) adults using denudifying apps in 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["22145"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4849, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Ministry of Justice publishes data on prosecutions for a wide range of offences, including offences involving the possession, creation and distribution of indecent images of children. Data up to and including June 2024 is available in the Outcomes by ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Intimate Image Abuse: Prosecutions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "22145", "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752834", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752778, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22026", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, how she plans to measure progress towards her target for children to be thriving at school; and if she will mak", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4125, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Opportunity Mission will break the link between a child\u2019s background and their future success. Driving high and rising standards is at the heart of the department\u2019s vision for all schools, and these standards are crucial in supporting all children and...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752778", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752705, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22100", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 3 January 2025 to Question 19417 on Genetics: Diseases, how much funding was provided by NHS England to the Genetic Risk Equity project; and what that funding was used for", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The project began in 2022/23, with total spend being \u00a32.7 million. The following table showing the breakdown by year and to the nearest \u00a3100,000:YearSpend (\u00a3)2024/251,000,0002023/241,000,0002022/23700,000Source: NHS EnglandNote: The funding was spent on a...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Genetics: Diseases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752705", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752799, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22101", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of changes to (a) Business Property Relief and (b) employer National Insurance contributions on SMEs in the defence sector.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 483, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Ministry of Defence recognises the vital contribution that Small and Medium Enterprises (SMEs) make within the defence industry, and we have a long-standing commitment to improve our engagement with such suppliers in order to broaden and strengthen ou...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Small Businesses", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752799", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752716, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22030", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the impact of Cyclone Chido on communities in northern Zambia.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["22029"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4657, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Heavy wind and rain from Tropical Cyclone Chido have caused widespread damage in Mozambique and Malawi, and have resulted in extensive crop and infrastructure damage in parts of the region. Flooding has increased the risk of disease outbreak in a region w...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Zambia: Storms", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "22029", "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752716", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752715, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22029", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment has been made of the potential impact of Cyclone Chido on people in southern Africa.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["22030"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4657, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Heavy wind and rain from Tropical Cyclone Chido have caused widespread damage in Mozambique and Malawi, and have resulted in extensive crop and infrastructure damage in parts of the region. Flooding has increased the risk of disease outbreak in a region w...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Southern Africa: Storms", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "22030", "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752715", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752897, "askingMemberId": 5195, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22206", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appellants are waiting for First-tier Tribunal (Social Security and Child Support) appeals to be listed for personal independence payment in (a) Mid Cheshire constituency, (b) Cheshire and (c) England.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["22205"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5204, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Information about appeals to the First-tier Tribunal (Social Security and Child Support) (SSCS) is published at: www.gov.uk/government/collections/tribunals-statistics. The average waiting times data requested can be found under \u201cTribunal Statistics CSV f...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Personal Independence Payment: Appeals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "22205", "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752897", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752896, "askingMemberId": 5195, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22205", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time was for a First-tier Tribunal (Social Security and Child Support) appeal for (a) personal independence payment and (b) universal credit in (i) Mid Cheshire constituency, (ii) Chesh", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["22206"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5204, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Information about appeals to the First-tier Tribunal (Social Security and Child Support) (SSCS) is published at: www.gov.uk/government/collections/tribunals-statistics. The average waiting times data requested can be found under \u201cTribunal Statistics CSV f...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Security Benefits: Appeals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "22206", "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752896", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752855, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22007", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the value of Russian state assets in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4518, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government coordinates these figures closely with our G7 partners. There are sensitivities around publishing these figures, and other G7 partners have restrictions on their ability to publish. It is important, therefore, that a decision to release any...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Russia: Assets", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752855", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752274, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21719", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to support the comedy industry.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1446, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Comedy is a serious business. It is a vital performing art and contributes to the mental health and wellbeing of people, not just in the UK, but around the world. It forms part of our cultural landscape, enriching lives, shaping our collective identity an...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Performing Arts: Government Assistance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752274", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752760, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22088", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an estimate of the number and proportion of children who would be eligible for free school meals had the income threshold for people on Universal Credit risen with inflation\u00a0since\u00a02018.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["22087"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4653, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The new government has a central mission to break down barriers to opportunity for every child.The government has inherited a trend of rising child poverty and widening attainment gaps between children eligible for free school meals (FSM) and their peers....", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Free School Meals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "22087", "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752760", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752758, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22087", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils who are eligible for free school meals are not claiming it.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["22088"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4653, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The new government has a central mission to break down barriers to opportunity for every child.The government has inherited a trend of rising child poverty and widening attainment gaps between children eligible for free school meals (FSM) and their peers....", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Free School Meals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "22088", "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752758", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752460, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21947", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will take steps to ensure that Local Housing Allowance rates reflect rents in (a) rural and (b) urban areas.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 163, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "In April 2024, Local Housing Allowance (LHA) increased to the 30th percentile of local market rents for one year at a cost of \u00a37bn over 5 years.LHA rates are set within Broad Rental Market Areas (BRMAs), which are determined by rent officers at the Valuat...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Housing Allowance: Rents", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752460", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752477, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21922", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of creating an independent process to set benefit levels according to the cost of essentials.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 163, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "No assessment has been made. The Social Security Administration Act 1992 requires the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions to review benefit and State Pension rates each year to see if they have retained their value in relation to the general level of...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Security Benefits: Cost of Living", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752477", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752247, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21569", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many pensioners have returned to the UK from countries where their state pension has been frozen in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4077, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department does not hold the information to be able to answer this question.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "State Retirement Pensions: British Nationals Abroad", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752247", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752777, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22025", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, how she plans to measure progress towards her target for safer town centres; and what her target is f", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["22023"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1533, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "We are currently in the process of devising a new performance framework for neighbourhood policing to improve standards and performance across the country. We are engaging with police forces, the College of Policing and National Police Chiefs\u2019 Council to ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Crime Prevention: Urban Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "22023", "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752777", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752775, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22023", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 34 of the policy paper entitled Plan for Change: Milestones for mission-led government, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, how she plans to measure the success of the neighbo", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["22025"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1533, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "We are currently in the process of devising a new performance framework for neighbourhood policing to improve standards and performance across the country. We are engaging with police forces, the College of Policing and National Police Chiefs\u2019 Council to ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Policing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "22025", "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752775", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752355, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21927", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the child poverty strategy will include measures to tackle child homelessness.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4083, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Delivering our manifesto commitment to tackle child poverty is an urgent priority for this Government, and the Ministerial Taskforce is working to publish the Child Poverty Strategy in Spring 2025. The Taskforce\u2019s publication of 23 October \u2018Tackling Child...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homelessness: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752355", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752166, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21588", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will publish the internal equality impact assessment under the Equality Act 2010 for changes to (a) agricultural and (b) business property relief.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4797, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government published information about the reforms to agricultural property relief and business property relief at www.gov.uk/government/publications/agricultural-property-relief-and-business-property-relief-reforms. It is expected that up to around 2...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752166", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752373, "askingMemberId": 5190, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21817", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what guidance her Department will issue to non-agricultural businesses on the changes to Inheritance Tax announced in the Autumn Budget 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4797, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government published information about the reforms to agricultural property relief and business property relief at www.gov.uk/government/publications/agricultural-property-relief-and-business-property-relief-reforms. As with other tax changes, HM Reve...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752373", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752346, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21636", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of (a) family-owned businesses and (b) changes to Business Property Relief on the economy of local communities.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4797, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "At Autumn Budget 2024, the Government took a number of difficult but necessary decisions on tax, welfare, and spending to restore economic stability, fix the public finances, and support public services. These were tough decisions given the situationwe in...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates and Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752346", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752866, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22214", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of paying the State Pension in monthly instalments.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4077, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "State Pension payments are usually paid four weekly in arrears. People have the option to be paid weekly or in some circumstances bi-weekly. There are no plans to introduce alternative payment arrangements.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "State Retirement Pensions: Payments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752866", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752398, "askingMemberId": 5263, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21870", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of an increase in the rate of employers' National Insurance contributions on (a) hairdressers and (b) other small to medium-sized high street businesses that do n", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4797, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "In order to repair the public finances and help raise the revenue required to supportpublic services, the Government has taken the difficult decision to increase employer National Insurance contributions (NICs). The Government published a Tax Information ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Small Businesses: Employers' Contributions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752398", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752553, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21962", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to increase transparency in the (a) management and (b) adjustment of pension schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4077, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Trustees have a fiduciary duty to act in the best interests of the scheme membership, and are required by law to provide members with information about how the scheme has been managed. This includes legal duties about transparency and disclosure of inform...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pensions: Disclosure of Information", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752553", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752197, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21607", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the most recent review of the frozen pensions policy was.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4077, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "There has been no recent review of the policy. The policy on the uprating of UK State Pensions paid overseas is a longstanding one of successive Governments, which has been in place for over 70 years. UK State Pensions are payable worldwide, without regar...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "State Retirement Pensions: British Nationals Abroad", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752197", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752767, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22015", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of whether public spending plans in the (a) Autumn Budget 2024 and (b) Spending Review phase (i) one and (ii) two will require (A) compulsory and (B) voluntary redundancies in the civil ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4621, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "At Autumn Budget, this government committed to developing a long-term strategic workforce plan for a more efficient and effective Civil Service. During Spending Review phase two, departments will set out their long-term spending plans, including for their...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Service: Redundancy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752767", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752248, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21570", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has taken steps to notify British pensioners retiring abroad that their pension may be frozen.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4077, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The UK's policy on the up-rating of the UK State Pension for recipients living overseas is a longstanding one. The UK state pension is payable worldwide without regard to nationality and is uprated abroad where we have a legal requirement to do so. Up-rat...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "State Retirement Pensions: British Nationals Abroad", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752248", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752507, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21779", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether he has had recent discussions with the Northern Ireland Executive on the health service in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4788, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Improving health outcomes across the UK is a priority mission for this Government. Although health is devolved in Northern Ireland, the Government wants to work with the Northern Ireland Executive to transform its public services and improve outcomes for ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752507", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752470, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21771", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether he has had recent discussions with the Northern Ireland Executive on the number of people on hospital waiting lists in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4788, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Improving health outcomes across the UK is a priority mission for this Government. Although health is devolved in Northern Ireland, the Government wants to work with the Northern Ireland Executive to transform its public services and improve outcomes for ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospitals: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752470", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752786, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22099", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will publish a plan to help tackle the use of Uyghur slave labour in solar supply chains.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4998, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government opposes all forms of slave labour. The Government is clear UK businesses should monitor their supply chains and do everything in their power to remove any instances of forced labour they may find.Through the reconvened Solar Taskforce, the ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Solar Power: Supply Chains", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752786", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752845, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "21998", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 17 December 2024 to Question 19312 on Syria: British Nationals Abroad, what steps is he taking to provide consular support to British nationals in S", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5148, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Consular support is not available from the UK Government from within Syria as all British Embassy services in Damascus are suspended. This makes it difficult to provide direct assistance to British nationals located there. Nevertheless, each request for c...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Syria: British Nationals Abroad", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752845", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752808, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22072", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent progress his Department has made on helping to improve freedom of religion or belief of minority Buddhist communities in Southeast Asia.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4523, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The UK remains strongly committed to freedom of religion or belief (FoRB) for all abroad. It is our firm opinion that no one should live in fear because of what they do or do not believe in. We are championing the right to FoRB multilaterally, bilaterally...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Southeast Asia: Religious Freedom", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752808", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752833, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22053", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when he plans to reply to the letter from the hon. Member for Brentwood and Ongar dated 5 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 413, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "I replied to the Honourable Members letter on the 23rd December by email. ", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Members: Correspondence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752833", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752839, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "21993", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Israeli counterparts on their commitments to ensure aid delivery into Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5148, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The UK has made repeatedly clear to the Israeli authorities the need to improve aid delivery and increase the variety and volume of goods reaching Gaza. The Foreign Secretary made this clear in a call with Israeli Foreign Minister Sa'ar on 8 December. I h...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: Humanitarian Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752839", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752448, "askingMemberId": 5275, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21877", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking to help tackle the threat from the Russian shadow fleet in the (a) Baltic and (b) North Sea.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4264, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Our oil-related sanctions are having a significant impact, with Russia forced to shoulder a 25 percent reduction in oil and gas revenues from January to October 2024, compared to the same period in 2022. Where Russia has sought to circumvent those sanctio...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Russia: Shipping", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752448", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752810, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22074", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential implications for his policies on freedom of religion or belief of the imposition of legal restrictions on the Burqa in public s", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4264, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The UK continues to champion freedom of religion or belief (FoRB) for all. We are working to uphold the right to FoRB through our position at the UN, G7 and other multilateral fora and in our important bilateral work. These are ultimately matters for the ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Switzerland: Religious Freedom", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752810", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752520, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21792", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to help increase the (a) volume and (b) value of trade between the UK and Trinidad and Tobago.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 632, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department for Business and Trade is supporting UK businesses to access opportunities to grow trade with Trinidad and Tobago, including in areas such as critical infrastructure. In October 2024, UK Export Finance signed a Memorandum of Understanding w...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Trade: Trinidad and Tobago", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752520", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752832, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22052", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Prime Minister plans to reply to the letter from the hon. Member for Brentwood and Ongar dated 29 November 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5305, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "A response will be sent in due course. ", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Members: Correspondence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752832", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752868, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22207", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Standards and Testing Agency's publication of 20 July 2022, entitled Information: primary assessments in the 2022/23 academic year, for what reason it was decided not to undertake further ", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4125, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Statutory teacher assessment of science is undertaken annually at the end of key stage 2 for all pupils in the relevant cohort. Between 2014 and 2020, biennial national science sampling tests were used to supplement this teacher assessment data, with a na...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "National Curriculum Tests: Science", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752868", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752920, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22215", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will introduce the Future Homes and Building Standards as soon as possible.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4641, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Future Homes and Buildings Standards consultation was published in December 2023 and closed in March 2024; a government response, including implementation plans, has not yet been issued.Government fully supports the need for low carbon homes and build...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Building Regulations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752920", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752482, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21829", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the 2024/25 priorities and operational guidance, updated on 24 April 2024, what steps she is taking to hold NHS England accountable for implementing regular demand and capacity as", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department continues to support the National Health Service in England to increase cancer treatment capacity. NHS England had previously established a task-and-finish group to gather, collate, and compile available information to establish Systemic An...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Medical Treatments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752482", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752806, "askingMemberId": 429, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "21976", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which organisation is responsible for procuring radiotherapy machines.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Responsibility for purchasing radiotherapy treatment machines sits with local systems. The Government committed \u00a370 million for new machines in last year\u2019s Budget, to ensure that the most advanced treatment is available to patients who need it.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Radiotherapy: Medical Equipment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752806", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752401, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21800", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to reduce waiting times for cancer treatment.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "We know that patients are waiting too long for cancer treatment, and we will get the National Health Service diagnosing cancer on time or earlier, treating it faster, and we will improve patients\u2019 experience across the system.As we set out in our new plan...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Medical Treatments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752401", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753220, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22444", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department plans to mark World Wetlands Day in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The theme for World Wetlands Day 2025 is \u2018Protecting Wetlands for Our Common Future\u2019 and Defra plans to mark World Wetlands Day. In 2021 the UK co-sponsored the United Nations Resolution to designate 2 February as World Wetlands Day and we have since unde...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Wetlands", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753220", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752183, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21744", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department is taking steps to decrease the amount of time it takes for a repurposed medicine to be granted an MHRA licence.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Medicines and products Regulatory Agency (MHRA) reviews the efficacy, safety and quality of a repurposed medicine in a similar way to other medicinal applications. This review is part of the activities which MHRA contributes to under the Medicines Rep...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Drugs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752183", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752380, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21838", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation entitled NHS Pension Scheme: proposed amendments for April 2025, published on 10 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department launched the consultation \u2018NHS Pension Scheme: proposed amendments for April 2025\u2019 on GOV.UK on 10 December 2024, with more information available at the following link:https://www.gov.uk/government/consultations/nhs-pension-scheme-proposed-...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Workplace Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752380", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752182, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21743", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average length of time has been for a repurposed medicine to be granted an MHRA licence from the point of application in the last two years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21742"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "In the last two years, there has been one medicine to date, namely Anastrozole, coming through the Repurposed Medicines Programme, with more information available at the following link:https://www.england.nhs.uk/medicines-2/medicines-repurposing-programme...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Drugs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21742", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752182", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752181, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21742", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many repurposed medicines have successfully been granted MHRA licences in the last two years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21743"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "In the last two years, there has been one medicine to date, namely Anastrozole, coming through the Repurposed Medicines Programme, with more information available at the following link:https://www.england.nhs.uk/medicines-2/medicines-repurposing-programme...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Drugs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21743", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752181", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752675, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22109", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of increasing non-academic routes for people to train as nurses.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "We have a complete apprentice pathway for nursing, from entry level to postgraduate advanced clinical practice. NHS England is expanding routes into healthcare professions through apprenticeships. Our 10-Year Health Plan to reform the National Health Serv...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nurses: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752675", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752731, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22115", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been fined for accessing prescriptions without a valid Maternity Exception Certificate.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["22114"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "There are no plans to revise the application process for maternity exemption certificates that provide entitlement to free National Health Service prescriptions. The NHS Business Services Authority has advised that in 2024, 48,063 Penalty Charge Notices w...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prescriptions: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "22114", "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752731", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752730, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22114", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will simplify the process for obtaining Maternity Exception Certificates.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["22115"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "There are no plans to revise the application process for maternity exemption certificates that provide entitlement to free National Health Service prescriptions. The NHS Business Services Authority has advised that in 2024, 48,063 Penalty Charge Notices w...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prescriptions: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "22115", "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752730", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752350, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "21684", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria she will use to measure the success of the ambition to halve violence against women and girls.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4370, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "We are undertaking a programme of work to bring together suitable data and metrics to measure progress against the ambition to halve VAWG in a decade. We are working closely with The Office for National Statistics and other stakeholders in producing the m...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gender Based Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752350", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752708, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22092", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the English Devolution White Paper, published on 16 December 2024, whether unitary local authorities will be required to merge with neighbouring councils to mee", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4569, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "On 16 December, I wrote to all councils in two-tier areas and to neighbouring small unitaries alongside the White Paper, to set out our plans. I intend to formally invite unitary proposals in January 2025 from all these councils. I will ask for interim pl...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Reform", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752708", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752850, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22003", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2024 to Question 16959 on Gavi, the Vaccine Alliance: Finance, what discussions he has had with international partners on supporting (a)", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4657, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "As Minister for Development, I met with both the CEO of Gavi and the Executive Director of the Global Fund last Autumn to discuss upcoming replenishments. The UK is one of the largest donors to both Gavi and the Global Fund and we want to see successful r...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gavi, the Vaccine Alliance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752850", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752472, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21773", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what criteria he plans to use to appoint country-specific trade envoys.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 177, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Trade Envoys are appointed on their ability, relevant skills and experience. This can be based on market and or UK sector knowledge including previous government-to-government experience plus their commitment to support the Government\u2019s trade and investme...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trade Promotion", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752472", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752374, "askingMemberId": 5244, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21864", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he plans to take steps to recover the costs of compensation from Fujitsu relating to failures of the Horizon Post Office IT system.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 177, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government welcomes Fujitsu\u2019s acknowledgement of their moral obligation to\u202fmake a contribution\u202fto the cost of the Horizon scandal. Fujitsu\u2019s contribution will be decided once the\u202fPost Office Horizon IT Inquiry\u202fhas reviewed all the evidence\u202fand the Cha...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Horizon IT System: Compensation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752374", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752869, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22208", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent progress she has made on enactment of the socio-economic duty under Section 1 of the Equality Act 2010.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4657, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government is committed to commencing the socio-economic duty in the Equality Act 2010. The duty will require public bodies, when making strategic decisions, to consider actively how their decisions might help to reduce the inequalities associated wit...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disadvantaged", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752869", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752809, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22073", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent progress he has made on supporting (a) Rakhine Muslim and (b) Christian communities in Myanmar.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4523, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "We are committed to defending freedom of religion or belief for all. Since 2017, the UK has provided over \u00a348 million in aid including cash assistance and water, sanitation and hygiene services to the Rohingya and other Muslim minorities in Rakhine state....", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Myanmar: Religious Freedom", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752809", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752513, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21785", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to help increase the (a) volume and (b) value of trade between the UK and Jamaica.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 632, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department for Business and Trade is supporting UK firms to access opportunities in Jamaica across a variety of sectors, including critical infrastructure. In November 2024, the UK hosted Senator Aubyn Hill, the Jamaican Minister of Industry, Investme...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Trade: Jamaica", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752513", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752291, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21610", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of reports of attacks by Israel on medical facilities in Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5148, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The UK Government remains deeply concerned about the impact of military activity on healthcare facilities in Gaza. Medical staff and facilities must be protected, and civilians should be able to safely access medical treatment. It is unacceptable that nor...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: Israel", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752291", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752514, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21786", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to help increase the (a) volume and (b) value of trade between the UK and Malta.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 632, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "We are resetting the relationship with our European friends \u2013 including Malta \u2013 to strengthen ties, secure a broad-based security pact and tackle barriers to trade. We are working with the EU and bilaterally with Member States to identify areas to strengt...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Trade: Malta", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752514", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752554, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21952", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what discussions he has had with Sri Lankan authorities on strengthening business relations for British citizens who have set up companies in Sri Lanka.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 632, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "DBT has a team dedicated to supporting the UK-Sri Lanka trade and investment relationship. Officials have regular contact with Sri Lankan authorities through the annual UK-Sri Lanka Strategic Dialogue to promote areas of mutual interest, including bilater...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Companies: Sri Lanka", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752554", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752674, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22108", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to (a) monitor and (b) regulate delivery drivers working for food delivery companies to ensure they are using roads and pavements safely.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Everyone who drives, rides or cycles, including delivery drivers and riders, has a duty to behave in a safe and responsible manner, and to follow the rules set out in The Highway Code. They must also hold the necessary registration, tax, licence and appro...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Delivery Services: Roads and Pedestrian Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752674", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752709, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22093", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding has been allocated to support areas at risk of flooding; and when he plans to announce these.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4645, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "To ensure we protect the country from the devastating impacts of flooding, we will invest \u00a32.4 billion in 2024/25 and 2025/26 to improve flood resilience, by building, maintaining, and repairing flood defences. The list of projects to receive Government f...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Flood Control: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752709", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752872, "askingMemberId": 5164, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22182", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of trends in levels of costs for statutory external audit fees levied on National Park authorities on those authorities; and if he w", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Defra acknowledges that rising costs, including to fees required to fulfil statutory obligations, increase the funding pressures on National Park authorities. Public Sector Audit Appointments Limited (PSAA) independently sets fees for eligible bodies defi...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "National Parks: Audit", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752872", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752729, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22113", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that parking enforcement debt collection practices are equitable.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Local authorities may only charge reasonable costs in relation to fees for enforcement agents, these are clearly set out in the Taking Control of Goods (Fees) Regulations 2014. Enforcement agents responsible for executing warrants of control on behalf of ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parking Offences: Debt Collection", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752729", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752162, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21686", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2024 to Question 19468 on Special Escort Group, on what statutory basis the police are able to (a) stop and direct traffic and (b) exceed speed limits in non-emergency situ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "Powers for police to stop and direct traffic are set out in sections 35, 37 and 163 of the Road Traffic Act 1988.The exemption for speed is set out in section 87(1) of the Road Traffic Regulation Act 1984. The exemption to speed does not require there to ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Escort Group", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752162", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752867, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22204", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2024 to Question 20545 on Department of Health and Social Care: Correspondence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that 80% of hon. Members receive ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department is committed to meeting the target of responding to at least 80% of correspondence from Hon. Members within 20 working days. Parliament has a right to hold Ministers to account. We recognise there is room for improvement and we are committe...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department of Health and Social Care: Correspondence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752867", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753076, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22246", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of prostate cancer services in (a) South Holland and The Deepings constituency and (b) Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department is committed to improving the adequacy of all cancer services including for prostate cancer, this includes cancer services in South Holland and The Deepings and Lincolnshire. NHS England has funded 10 clinical audits, including a national p...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prostate Cancer: Lincolnshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753076", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752527, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21833", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how the additional funding announced in the Autumn Budget 2024 for the National Institute for Health and Care Research will be allocated.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The 2025/26 settlement for the National Institute for Health and Care Research (NIHR) will fund research into a range of health and care challenges facing the population. A key element of this investment is research to support the goals of the Government ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "National Institute for Health and Care Research: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752527", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752827, "askingMemberId": 5125, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22161", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help reduce inequalities of care for blood cancer patients.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the hon. Member to the answer I gave on 8 October 2024 to Question 5808.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Blood Cancer: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752827", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752698, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22155", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the NHS is taking to improve training for doctors on (a) understanding and (b) treating chronic urinary tract infections.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The standard of training for doctors is the responsibility of the General Medical Council (GMC). The GMC sets the outcome standards expected at undergraduate level. The curricula for postgraduate training is set by the Academy of Medical Royal Colleges fo...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Urinary Tract Infections", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752698", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752683, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21987", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people in the UK have been diagnosed with vitiligo.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department does not hold data on the number of people in England who have been diagnosed with vitiligo. Data relating to Northern Ireland, Scotland and Wales is a matter for the devolved governments.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Vitiligo", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752683", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752707, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22091", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with (a) his international counterparts and (b) the World Health Organisation on human metapneumovirus.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The UK Health Security Agency (UKHSA) has had no recent communications from the World Health Organisation or other countries in relation to human metapneumovirus (hMPV).UKHSA\u2019s long-term surveillance of hMPV in England, through systems covering general pr...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Viral Diseases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752707", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752416, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21871", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of not allowing carers to be vaccinated for Covid-19 on people requiring care.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government is committed to protecting those most vulnerable to COVID-19 through vaccination, as guided by the independent Joint Committee on Vaccination and Immunisation (JCVI). The primary aim of the national COVID-19 vaccination programme remains th...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coronavirus: Vaccination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752416", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752706, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22090", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many cases of human metapneumovirus have been identified in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "answerText": "The UK Health Security Agency\u2019s long-term surveillance of human metapneumovirus (hMPV) in England, through systems covering general practice surgeries and hospital laboratories, indicates that hMPV levels in winter 2024-25 are in line with what we would e...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Viral Diseases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752706", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752253, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21700", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 23 December 2024 to Question 19416 on Maternity Services: Nurses, if his Department will make an estimate of the number of close relative marriage neonatal nurses there ar", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": true, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department of Health and Social Care has indicated that it will not be possible to answer this question within the usual time period. An answer is being prepared and will be provided as soon as it is available.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Maternity Services: Nurses", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752253", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752281, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21701", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the (a) cost and (b) incidence of cousin marriage.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": true, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department of Health and Social Care has indicated that it will not be possible to answer this question within the usual time period. An answer is being prepared and will be provided as soon as it is available.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Marriage: Relatives", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752281", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752361, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21818", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the criteria are for Ministers to (a) intervene in an Integrated Care Board's reconfiguration proposal and (b) revisit decisions made in those proposals.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": true, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department of Health and Social Care has indicated that it will not be possible to answer this question within the usual time period. An answer is being prepared and will be provided as soon as it is available.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Integrated Care Boards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752361", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752175, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21696", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the implementation of a generational ban on tobacco sales on trends in the level of (a) counterfeit cigarettes and (b) contraband cigarettes b", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the hon. Member to the answer I gave to the hon. Member for Bridlington and The Wolds on 11 December 2024 to Question UIN 17992.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tobacco: Smuggling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752175", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752219, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21554", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to change meat inspection charges from April 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Food Standards Agency (FSA) charges operators to recover costs of meat inspection across its geographic remit of England, Wales and Northern Ireland. The FSA conducts an annual review of inspection charges ahead of each financial year. Charges applica...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Meat: Inspections", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752219", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752224, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21559", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of animal welfare at abattoirs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21553", "21555"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "As of 1 December 2024, the Food Standards Agency (FSA) and their Service Delivery Partner between them employed 282 Official Veterinarians (OVs) and 596 Meat Hygiene Inspectors / Official Auxiliaries, as well as 12 Trainee Official Auxiliaries.The Departm...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Slaughterhouses: Animal Welfare", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21553", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21555", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752224", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752220, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21555", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many Food Standards Agency welfare checks carried out by official veterinarians took place (a) on the farm, (b) during transport to the slaughterhouse, (c) upon arrival at the slaughterhouse an", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21553", "21559"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "As of 1 December 2024, the Food Standards Agency (FSA) and their Service Delivery Partner between them employed 282 Official Veterinarians (OVs) and 596 Meat Hygiene Inspectors / Official Auxiliaries, as well as 12 Trainee Official Auxiliaries.The Departm...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Farms and Slaughterhouses: Animal Welfare", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21553", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21559", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752220", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752218, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21553", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) official veterinarians and (b) meat hygiene inspectors there were as of 1 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21555", "21559"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "As of 1 December 2024, the Food Standards Agency (FSA) and their Service Delivery Partner between them employed 282 Official Veterinarians (OVs) and 596 Meat Hygiene Inspectors / Official Auxiliaries, as well as 12 Trainee Official Auxiliaries.The Departm...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Slaughterhouses: Inspections", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21555", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21559", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752218", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752503, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21918", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made an assessment of the potential impact of changing the funding for built environment Level 7 apprentices on the Government's commitment to build 1.5 million homes.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4698, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The government is committed to 1.5 million homes being built across this Parliament while spreading opportunities and economic growth supported by a strong skills system.The department is working closely with industry and across Whitehall on this ambition...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Apprentices: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752503", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752526, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21873", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to support college teachers who did not receive the 5.5% pay rise; and if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of tying pay increases for(a) college and (b) school teache", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4698, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Further education (FE) colleges, rather than government, are responsible for setting and negotiating pay within colleges. Colleges are not bound by the national pay and conditions framework for school teachers, but are free to implement their own pay arra...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Teachers: Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752526", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752174, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21695", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether additional powers will be made available to law enforcement officers to penalise (a) barber shops, (b) off-licences, (c) bookmakers, (d) pubs and (e) other non-grocery and non-newsagent pre", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21694"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Tobacco and Vapes Bill will put us on track to a smoke-free United Kingdom, helping to reduce around 80,000 preventable deaths and reduce the burden on the National Health Service and on the taxpayer.Whilst the published impact assessment on the Bill ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tobacco: Sales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21694", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752174", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752173, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21694", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Tobacco and Vapes Bill on the illegal sale of tobacco products in (a) non-grocery and (b) non-newsagent premises.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21695"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Tobacco and Vapes Bill will put us on track to a smoke-free United Kingdom, helping to reduce around 80,000 preventable deaths and reduce the burden on the National Health Service and on the taxpayer.Whilst the published impact assessment on the Bill ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tobacco: Sales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21695", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752173", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752443, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21859", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2024 to Question 20334 on Flexible Working, on what dates the Flexible Working Taskforce met in 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4418, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Flexible Working Taskforce met once in 2023, on April 24th. The government has continued to engage with stakeholders on a regular basis to discuss flexible working and related issues.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Flexible Working Taskforce", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752443", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752270, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21715", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to ensure sufficient recycling facilities are available to process end-of-life electric vehicle batteries.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4631, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The UK has the opportunity to boost its midstream processing and recycling of critical minerals, building on world-leading innovation and technical expertise in our chemicals and metals sectors. We continue to work with industry via the Automotive Transfo...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Batteries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752270", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752445, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21861", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people in Birmingham received awards under the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme in each of the last five years for which figures are available; and what the value of those awards was.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4849, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The table below provides the number of compensation awards paid in each of the last five calendar years to applicants living in Birmingham. Number of compensation awards paid to applicants living in Birmingham* **:Calendar YearNumber of awards paidTotal v...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Criminal Injuries Compensation: Birmingham", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752445", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752878, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22223", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to facilitate the recycling of blister packs.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Waste is a devolved policy, and the devolved administrations have their own arrangements for household and business recycling and waste collections. There are currently no plans for blister packs to be included in the list of materials to be collected at ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Drugs: Packaging", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752878", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752469, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21770", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will hold discussions with the hon. Member for Newcastle-under-Lyme on taking steps to protect the residents of Mallard Close, Madeley, from the effects of repeated flooding inci", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4645, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "To ensure we protect the country from the devastating impacts of flooding, we will invest \u00a32.4 billion in 2024/25 and 2025/26 to improve flood resilience, by building, maintaining, and repairing flood defences. The issues in the Mallards Close, Madeley, a...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Flood Control: Madeley", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752469", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752379, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21837", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation entitled Environmental permitting: standard rules consultation number 29, published on 9 December", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4645, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Environment Agency (EA) uses existing Government websites to publish permit consultations, posting a notification on GOV.UK that points to a consultation on the EA\u2019s Citizen Space website. The EA ensures its consultation information meets the accessib...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Incinerators: Waste Disposal", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752379", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752163, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21687", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to remove the gender-neutral toilets in her Department in Marsham Street.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1533, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The current number and location of gender neutral toilets in the Home Office\u2019s Marsham office was established under the previous government in October 2017, at a cost of \u00a336,963.20, and has remained unchanged since that time.There are no plans to spend fu...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Office: Sanitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752163", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752222, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21557", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many prosecutions there have been for slaughterhouses in England not having CCTV in the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4382, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "All approved slaughterhouses in England must have CCTV systems installed as required by the Mandatory Use of Closed-Circuit Television in Slaughterhouses (England) Regulations 2018. There have been no prosecutions for slaughterhouses in England for not ha...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Slaughterhouses: CCTV", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752222", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752317, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21677", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will launch an inquiry into grooming and rape gangs.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4370, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government's priority is to take action on delivering against the recommendations of the final report of the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse (IICSA). The Home Secretary announced on 6th January that we will be bringing in mandatory reporti...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752317", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752221, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21556", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has had discussions with the RSPCA on animal cruelty at RSPCA-approved abattoirs.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4382, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department engages regularly with the RSPCA on a range of animal welfare topics.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Slaughterhouses: Animal Welfare", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752221", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752233, "askingMemberId": 4500, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21639", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what date the Infected Blood Compensation Authority compensation scheme will open for members of the infected blood community to make claims.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4479, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Infected Blood Compensation Authority opened the compensation scheme to a small number of people in October 2024 as part of the initial development and testing of the compensation payment service. This will increase to around 250 people by March of th...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Infected Blood Compensation Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752233", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752217, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21552", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what animal welfare protections exist for farmed animals at slaughterhouses.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4382, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Welfare of Animals at the Time of Killing (England) Regulations 2015 and assimilated Regulation (EC) No 1099/2009 on the protection of animals at the time of killing set out extensive requirements to protect the welfare of animals at slaughterhouses. ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Slaughterhouses: Animal Welfare", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752217", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752232, "askingMemberId": 4500, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21638", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many members of the infected blood community were invited to start their claim for compensation between 17 October 2024 and 31 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["21637"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4479, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Between 17 October and 31 December 2024, the Infected Blood Compensation Authority invited 45 people to make a claim for compensation, comprising the initial group of 20 invitees and a further group of 25 at the end of December. The Authority made the fir...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Blood: Contamination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21637", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752232", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752231, "askingMemberId": 4500, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21637", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many compensation payments were made by the Infected Blood Compensation Authority between 17 October 2024 and 31 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["21638"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4479, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Between 17 October and 31 December 2024, the Infected Blood Compensation Authority invited 45 people to make a claim for compensation, comprising the initial group of 20 invitees and a further group of 25 at the end of December. The Authority made the fir...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Blood: Contamination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21638", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752231", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752319, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21679", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign nationals have been convicted for grooming.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4056, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Ministry of Justice publishes data on convictions for a wide range of offences, including grooming up to and including June 2024 in the Outcomes by Offences data tool, that can be downloaded from the Criminal Justice Statistics landing page here:Crimi...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children: Convictions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752319", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752322, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21727", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will publish all Departmental research undertaken in relation to the Government's response to the PHSO report on communication of Women's State Pension age on 17 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4077, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The research that has been used to inform the response is published, available online and is referenced within the response. The response itself has been deposited in the House of Commons Library and published on Gov.uk at https://www.gov.uk/government/pu...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "State Retirement Pensions: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752322", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752321, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21680", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to make being (a) the leader of and (b) involved in a grooming gang a statutory aggravating factor during sentencing.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4056, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Child sexual abuse and exploitation are the most vile and horrific of crimes - involving rape, violence, coercive control, intimidation, manipulation, and deep long-term harm.That is why this Government is determined to act \u2013 strengthening the law, taking...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children: Sentencing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752321", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752323, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21728", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of State Pension age changes on the six sample cases in the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman's report entitled Women\u2019s State Pension age:", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4077, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The six sample complainants were impacted by State Pension age changes introduced by both the Pensions Act 1995 and the Pensions Act 2011.The Ombudsman did not investigate the decisions to increase the State Pension age for women in 1995, or to accelerate...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "State Retirement Pensions: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752323", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752271, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21716", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to develop recycling technologies for end-of-life wind turbine blades and solar panels.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "This Government is committed to transition to a circular economy. We are developing a Circular Economy Strategy for England including a series of road maps detailing the interventions that the Government will make on a sector-by-sector basis, supporting G...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Energy: Infrastructure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752271", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752251, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21698", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many cases of gonorrhoea have been diagnosed in each of the last 30 years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The following table shows the number of gonorrhoea diagnoses in sexual health services in England between 1994 and 2023:YearNumber of gonorrhoea diagnoses19949,63119959,890199611,828199712,332199812,457199915,450200020,297200122,198200224,123200323,346200...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gonorrhoea", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752251", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752226, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21561", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many enforcement visits NSL Services Ltd made in (a) Bath and North East Somerset, (b) South Gloucestershire and (c) England in (i) September, (ii) October, (iii) November and (iv) December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21560"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The information requested can only be provided at disproportionate cost. A scan of both the Driver and Vehicle Licencing Agency\u2019s and the NSL Services Ltd databases would be required. Subsequent manual scrutiny and organisation of the data would be necess...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21560", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752226", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752225, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21560", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many reports of untaxed vehicles the DVLA have sent to NSL Services Ltd in (a) Bath and North East Somerset, (b) South Gloucestershire and (c) England.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21561"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The information requested can only be provided at disproportionate cost. A scan of both the Driver and Vehicle Licencing Agency\u2019s and the NSL Services Ltd databases would be required. Subsequent manual scrutiny and organisation of the data would be necess...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21561", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752225", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752282, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21662", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools will have to change their uniform policy to comply with the provisions in the Children\u2019s Wellbeing and Schools Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4125, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "School uniforms can play a valuable role in creating a sense of common identity among pupils and reducing visible inequalities. However, too many schools require high numbers of branded uniform items costing families hundreds of pounds. That is why the de...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Uniforms", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752282", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752556, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21957", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2024 to Question 19620 on Public Expenditure: Northern Ireland, if she will increase funding to Northern Ireland for the additional cost associated with changes to Employer Nati", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4621, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The UK Government has agreed to provide funding to the public sector to support them with the additional costs associated with changes to employer National Insurance Contributions policy. The Northern Ireland Executive will receive funding through the Bar...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Sector: Employers' Contributions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752556", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752407, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21806", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of rural broadband coverage.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1446, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "According to Ofcom\u2019s December 2024 Connected Nations report, just 0.1% of properties are unable to get decent broadband coverage (defined as at least 10 Mbps download speed and 1 Mbps upload speed), with 89% of rural UK residential properties having super...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Broadband: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752407", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752213, "askingMemberId": 4869, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21709", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects to resume processing asylum applications from Syrian nationals.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 491, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "We keep all country guidance relating to asylum claims under constant review, so we can respond to emerging issues. Following the fall of the Assad regime in Syria, the Home Office has withdrawn the Country Policy Information Notes and Guidance relating t...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Syria", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752213", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752452, "askingMemberId": 5275, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21881", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps NATO is taking to defend the High North.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4682, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "As a leading European Ally in NATO, the UK will defend and support our High North and Arctic Allies should the need arise, and contest malign and destabilising behaviours and activity in the region which threatens our interests, the interests of our Allie...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Arctic: Defence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752452", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752451, "askingMemberId": 5275, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21880", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has offered support to Finland in protecting sub-sea cables in the Baltic Sea.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4682, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Following recent damage to the Estlink2 undersea cable in the Baltic sea, the UK \u2013 acting as framework nation for the Joint Expeditionary Force (JEF) \u2013 has activated a JEF Response Option (JRO), known as NORDIC WARDEN, which will harness AI to track poten...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Cables: Baltic Sea", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752451", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752449, "askingMemberId": 5275, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21878", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, he last had discussions with NATO allies on protecting sub-sea cables in the (a) Baltic and (b) North Sea.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4682, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Recent incidents of damage to sub-sea cables underlines the importance of partners continuing to work together on shared challenges in the region. The Government regularly discusses strengthening NATO\u2019s protection of critical undersea infrastructure in en...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Cables: Baltic Sea and North Sea", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752449", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752450, "askingMemberId": 5275, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21879", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to help protect sub-sea cables in the North Sea from the Russian shadow fleet.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4682, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The UK Government constantly monitors and regularly assesses the security of critical national infrastructure, including energy and telecommunications assets. Following the incident damaging the Estlink 2 undersea cable between Finland and Estonia on 25 D...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Cables: North Sea", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752450", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752285, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21665", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of academy schools' facilities to comply with the duty in the Children\u2019s Wellbeing and Schools Bill to follow the national curriculum.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4125, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Every child deserves a cutting-edge curriculum taught by expert, qualified teachers, which sets them up with the knowledge and skills they need to achieve throughout life. The Bill will require all state schools to teach the reformed national curriculum, ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Academies: Facilities", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752285", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752403, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21802", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support community pharmacies.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Pharmacies play a vital role in our healthcare system. We are committed to expanding the role of pharmacies and to better using the skills of pharmacists and pharmacy technicians. That includes making prescribing part of the services delivered by communit...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pharmacy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752403", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752710, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22094", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average maximum number of patients registered per GP practice in England is.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The median number of patients registered at a general practice in England in December 2024 was 8,799.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners: Patients", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752710", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752490, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21950", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of reforming the NHS dental contract to (a) make appointments more accessible and (b) to tackle the backlog of people waiting f", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "To rebuild dentistry in the long term, we will reform the dental contract, with a shift to focus on prevention and the retention of National Health Service dentists. There are no perfect payment systems and careful consideration needs to be given to any p...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: Contracts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752490", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752201, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21567", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects the first overseas visitors to Northern Ireland arriving via the Republic of Ireland to be impacted by the UK Electronic Travel Authorisation scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4253, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "We are introducing the Electronic Travel Authorisation (ETA) scheme to enhance our ability to screen travellers upstream and stop those who pose a threat from travelling to the UK. The scheme, which already applies to nationals of Qatar, Bahrain, Kuwait, ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electronic Travel Authorisations: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752201", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752397, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21887", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will take steps to ensure the accessibility of touch screens for (a) card payment machines and (b) other services for people with visual impairments.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4518, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The government is committed to ensuring high standards of financial inclusion across the financial services sector. The Treasury continues to engage with UK Finance, the Financial Conduct Authority, the Royal National Institute of Blind People, and other ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Payment Methods: Visual Impairment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752397", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752205, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21604", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the answer of 17 December 2024 to Question 19693 on Department for Work and Pensions: Artificial Intelligence, on what date her Department decided not to publish that equality impact assessm", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4979, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Machine learning is currently used to flag cases requiring further examination. Our equality analysis found no issues of concern as set out in the Annual Report and Accounts. The most recent consideration of the release of this information took place foll...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Work and Pensions: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752205", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752444, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21860", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 11 December 2014 to Question 217660 on Teachers, whether the programme of talks referred to is ongoing.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4125, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Following the 2024 general election, the Programme of Talks forum was stood down to enable the department to develop new and improved ways of working with employer organisations, unions and other key stakeholders. This government is committed to resetting...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Teachers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752444", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752286, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21666", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of academy schools that do not currently comply with the duty in the Children\u2019s Wellbeing and Schools Bill to follow the national curriculum.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4125, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the hon. Member for Harborough, Oadby and Wigston to the answer of 29 July 2024 to Question 1038.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Academies: Curriculum", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752286", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752279, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21659", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications for Pension Credit were (a) received, (b) processed and granted and (c) processed and not granted in each month between July and December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4077, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Statistics on Pension Credit application volumes were published on 28 November 2024. This includes numbers of applications that were received, awarded and not awarded, up to 17 November 2024. Pension Credit applications and awards: November 2024 - GOV.UK....", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pension Credit", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752279", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752280, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21660", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many pension credit claims received since 1 August 2024 have (a) not been paid to the claimant and (b) refused on grounds the claimant is ineligible.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4077, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Because of how we capture our operational data, information on claims received over that period which have not been paid to the claimant/refused on the grounds of the claimant being ineligible is not available and to provide it would incur disproportionat...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pension Credit", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752280", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752939, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22202", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many transactions have been blocked under the National Security and Investment Act 2021 since 5 July 2024; and which transactions were blocked.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4820, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government publishes notices of final orders made on GOV.UK - this includes cases that are blocked, unwound, or cleared subject to conditions. The Government also publishes annual reports to provide information about the transactions that it has been ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foreign Investment in UK: National Security", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752939", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752562, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21955", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has had discussions with the England and Wales Cricket Board on the scheduled Champion's Trophy match with Afghanistan.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4607, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The UK Government condemns the appalling erosion of women and girls\u2019 rights in Afghanistan.Participation in the ICC Champion\u2019s Trophy match is a matter for the England and Wales Cricket Board and the International Cricket Council. My officials are in cont...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cricket: Afghanistan", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752562", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752935, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22198", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2024 to Question 15229 on Senior Civil Servants: Freedom of Information, what best practice guidance does the (a) Cabinet Office FOI Clearing House Internal Review and (b) i", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4820, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Cabinet Office has not issued either internal or external guidance on whether Freedom of Information Act requests requesting information on senior civil servants should be disclosed. All requests are considered on their own merits in all circumstances...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Freedom of Information", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752935", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752327, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21591", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the funding level of the Integrated Security Fund will be in (a) 2025/26 and (b) each of the following five years.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4820, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The ISF funding level in 2025/26 will be published shortly. Funding levels for future years will be considered as part of the second phase of the Spending Review. ", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Integrated Security Fund", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752327", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752195, "askingMemberId": 5117, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21746", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether funding for the School Games Organiser network will continue beyond March 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4607, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government has confirmed funding for the School Games Organisers (SGOs) until the end of the 2024/25 Academic Year. Funding beyond then will be confirmed ahead of the start of the 2025/26 Financial Year, with funding from April 2026 onwards subject to...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "School Games: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752195", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752395, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21853", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation entitled Open access restriction at Biggar (margin - winter): how to comment, published on 11 Dec", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21839", "21840", "21841", "21842", "21843", "21844", "21845", "21846", "21847", "21848", "21849", "21850", "21851", "21852"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the hon. Member to the answers given on 6 December 2024 to Questions 16894 and 16902. These are the pages for the consultations referred to: Open access restriction at Christy Pool to North Point: how to comment - GOV.UK Open access restriction at...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rights of Way: Walney Island", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21839", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21840", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21841", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21842", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21843", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21844", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21845", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21846", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21847", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21848", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21849", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21850", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21851", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21852", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752395", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752394, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21852", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation entitled Open access restriction at Biggar to Tummer Hill: how to comment, published on 11 Decemb", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21839", "21840", "21841", "21842", "21843", "21844", "21845", "21846", "21847", "21848", "21849", "21850", "21851", "21853"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the hon. Member to the answers given on 6 December 2024 to Questions 16894 and 16902. These are the pages for the consultations referred to: Open access restriction at Christy Pool to North Point: how to comment - GOV.UK Open access restriction at...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rights of Way: Walney Island", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21839", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21840", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21841", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21842", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21843", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21844", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21845", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21846", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21847", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21848", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21849", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21850", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21851", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21853", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752394", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752393, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21851", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation entitled Open access restriction at Walney airfield: how to comment, published on 11 December 202", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21839", "21840", "21841", "21842", "21843", "21844", "21845", "21846", "21847", "21848", "21849", "21850", "21852", "21853"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the hon. Member to the answers given on 6 December 2024 to Questions 16894 and 16902. These are the pages for the consultations referred to: Open access restriction at Christy Pool to North Point: how to comment - GOV.UK Open access restriction at...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rights of Way: Walney Island", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21839", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21840", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21841", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21842", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21843", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21844", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21845", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21846", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21847", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21848", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21849", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21850", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21852", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21853", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752393", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752392, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21850", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation entitled Open access restriction at Hare Hill (trail): how to comment, published on 11 December 2", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21839", "21840", "21841", "21842", "21843", "21844", "21845", "21846", "21847", "21848", "21849", "21851", "21852", "21853"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the hon. Member to the answers given on 6 December 2024 to Questions 16894 and 16902. These are the pages for the consultations referred to: Open access restriction at Christy Pool to North Point: how to comment - GOV.UK Open access restriction at...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rights of Way: Walney Island", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21839", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21840", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21841", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21842", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21843", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21844", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21845", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21846", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21847", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21848", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21849", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21851", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21852", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21853", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752392", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752391, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21849", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation entitled Open access restriction at North End Marsh: how to comment, published on 11 December 202", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21839", "21840", "21841", "21842", "21843", "21844", "21845", "21846", "21847", "21848", "21850", "21851", "21852", "21853"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the hon. Member to the answers given on 6 December 2024 to Questions 16894 and 16902. These are the pages for the consultations referred to: Open access restriction at Christy Pool to North Point: how to comment - GOV.UK Open access restriction at...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rights of Way: Walney Island", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21839", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21840", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21841", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21842", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21843", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21844", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21845", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21846", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21847", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21848", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21850", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21851", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21852", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21853", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752391", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752390, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21848", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation entitled Open access restriction at Walney airfield (trail), published on 11 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21839", "21840", "21841", "21842", "21843", "21844", "21845", "21846", "21847", "21849", "21850", "21851", "21852", "21853"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the hon. Member to the answers given on 6 December 2024 to Questions 16894 and 16902. These are the pages for the consultations referred to: Open access restriction at Christy Pool to North Point: how to comment - GOV.UK Open access restriction at...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rights of Way: Walney Island", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21839", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21840", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21841", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21842", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21843", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21844", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21845", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21846", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21847", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21849", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21850", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21851", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21852", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21853", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752390", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752389, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21847", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation entitled Open access restriction at Biggar (trail- summer), published on 11 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21839", "21840", "21841", "21842", "21843", "21844", "21845", "21846", "21848", "21849", "21850", "21851", "21852", "21853"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the hon. Member to the answers given on 6 December 2024 to Questions 16894 and 16902. These are the pages for the consultations referred to: Open access restriction at Christy Pool to North Point: how to comment - GOV.UK Open access restriction at...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rights of Way: Walney Island", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21839", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21840", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21841", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21842", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21843", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21844", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21845", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21846", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21848", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21849", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21850", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21851", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21852", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21853", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752389", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752388, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21846", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation entitled Open access restriction at North Scale (trail), published on 11 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21839", "21840", "21841", "21842", "21843", "21844", "21845", "21847", "21848", "21849", "21850", "21851", "21852", "21853"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the hon. Member to the answers given on 6 December 2024 to Questions 16894 and 16902. These are the pages for the consultations referred to: Open access restriction at Christy Pool to North Point: how to comment - GOV.UK Open access restriction at...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rights of Way: Walney Island", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21839", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21840", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21841", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21842", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21843", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21844", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21845", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21847", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21848", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21849", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21850", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21851", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21852", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21853", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752388", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752387, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21845", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation entitled Open access restriction at Biggar (margin- summer): how to comment, published on 11 Dece", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21839", "21840", "21841", "21842", "21843", "21844", "21846", "21847", "21848", "21849", "21850", "21851", "21852", "21853"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the hon. Member to the answers given on 6 December 2024 to Questions 16894 and 16902. These are the pages for the consultations referred to: Open access restriction at Christy Pool to North Point: how to comment - GOV.UK Open access restriction at...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rights of Way: Walney Island", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21839", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21840", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21841", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21842", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21843", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21844", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21846", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21847", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21848", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21849", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21850", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21851", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21852", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21853", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752387", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752386, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21844", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation entitled Open access restriction at Biggar (trail - winter): how to comment, published on 11 Dece", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21839", "21840", "21841", "21842", "21843", "21845", "21846", "21847", "21848", "21849", "21850", "21851", "21852", "21853"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the hon. Member to the answers given on 6 December 2024 to Questions 16894 and 16902. These are the pages for the consultations referred to: Open access restriction at Christy Pool to North Point: how to comment - GOV.UK Open access restriction at...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rights of Way: Walney Island", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21839", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21840", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21841", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21842", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21843", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21845", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21846", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21847", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21848", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21849", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21850", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21851", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21852", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21853", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752386", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752385, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21843", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation entitled Open access restriction at South Walney nature reserve: how to comment, published on 11 ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21839", "21840", "21841", "21842", "21844", "21845", "21846", "21847", "21848", "21849", "21850", "21851", "21852", "21853"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the hon. Member to the answers given on 6 December 2024 to Questions 16894 and 16902. These are the pages for the consultations referred to: Open access restriction at Christy Pool to North Point: how to comment - GOV.UK Open access restriction at...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rights of Way: Walney Island", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21839", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21840", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21841", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21842", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21844", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21845", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21846", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21847", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21848", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21849", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21850", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21851", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21852", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21853", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752385", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752384, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21842", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation entitled Open access restriction at North Scale (margin): how to comment, published on 11 Decembe", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21839", "21840", "21841", "21843", "21844", "21845", "21846", "21847", "21848", "21849", "21850", "21851", "21852", "21853"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the hon. Member to the answers given on 6 December 2024 to Questions 16894 and 16902. These are the pages for the consultations referred to: Open access restriction at Christy Pool to North Point: how to comment - GOV.UK Open access restriction at...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rights of Way: Walney Island", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21839", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21840", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21841", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21843", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21844", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21845", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21846", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21847", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21848", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21849", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21850", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21851", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21852", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21853", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752384", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752383, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21841", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation entitled Open access restriction at Rape Haw to Creephaw Marsh: how to comment, published on 11 D", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21839", "21840", "21842", "21843", "21844", "21845", "21846", "21847", "21848", "21849", "21850", "21851", "21852", "21853"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the hon. Member to the answers given on 6 December 2024 to Questions 16894 and 16902. These are the pages for the consultations referred to: Open access restriction at Christy Pool to North Point: how to comment - GOV.UK Open access restriction at...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rights of Way: Walney Island", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21839", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21840", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21842", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21843", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21844", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21845", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21846", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21847", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21848", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21849", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21850", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21851", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21852", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21853", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752383", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752382, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21840", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation entitled Open access restriction at South Walney: how to comment, published on 11 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21839", "21841", "21842", "21843", "21844", "21845", "21846", "21847", "21848", "21849", "21850", "21851", "21852", "21853"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the hon. Member to the answers given on 6 December 2024 to Questions 16894 and 16902. These are the pages for the consultations referred to: Open access restriction at Christy Pool to North Point: how to comment - GOV.UK Open access restriction at...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rights of Way: Walney Island", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21839", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21841", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21842", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21843", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21844", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21845", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21846", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21847", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21848", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21849", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21850", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21851", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21852", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21853", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752382", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752381, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21839", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation entitled Open access restriction at Christy Pool to North Point: how to comment, published on 11 ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["21840", "21841", "21842", "21843", "21844", "21845", "21846", "21847", "21848", "21849", "21850", "21851", "21852", "21853"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the hon. Member to the answers given on 6 December 2024 to Questions 16894 and 16902. These are the pages for the consultations referred to: Open access restriction at Christy Pool to North Point: how to comment - GOV.UK Open access restriction at...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rights of Way: Walney Island", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21840", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21841", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21842", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21843", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21844", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21845", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21846", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21847", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21848", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21849", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21850", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21851", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21852", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "21853", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752381", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752307, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21646", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will take steps to ensure that the funding model for inner London boroughs meets local demand.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["21642"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4569, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The provisional Settlement for 2025-26 makes available \u00a369 billion for local government, which is a 3.5% real terms increase in councils\u2019 Core Spending Power on 2024-25. The final Settlement will increase further, to incorporate the \u00a3515 million of fundin...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Finance: Greater London", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21642", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752307", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752303, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21642", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate she has made of the funding gap for London councils in the next four years.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["21646"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4569, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The provisional Settlement for 2025-26 makes available \u00a369 billion for local government, which is a 3.5% real terms increase in councils\u2019 Core Spending Power on 2024-25. The final Settlement will increase further, to incorporate the \u00a3515 million of fundin...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Finance: Greater London", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "21646", "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752303", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752522, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21794", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to help increase the (a) volume and (b) value of trade between the UK and Germany.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 632, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Reinvigorating the UK\u2019s relationship with our European partners is a top priority for this Government. Germany is already the UK\u2019s largest trading partner within the EU. Last summer, we launched negotiations for a bilateral treaty that will aim to strengt...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Trade: Germany", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752522", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752521, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21793", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to help increase the (a) volume and (b) value of trade between the UK and France.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 632, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Reinvigorating the UK\u2019s relationship with our European partners is a top priority for this Government. My officials regularly engage with counterparts in the French Government to identify opportunities to increase bilateral trade and investment, including...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Trade: France", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752521", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752523, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21795", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to help increase the (a) volume and (b) value of trade between the UK and Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 632, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Reinvigorating the UK\u2019s relationship with our European partners is a top priority for this Government. As the Prime Minister has made clear, we are committed to building an ever stronger relationship with Ireland. The UK-Ireland Summit in March offers the...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Trade: Republic of Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752523", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752483, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21830", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to address the regional variation in (a) access and (b) uptake to timely treatments for blood cancer patients.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "We will get the National Health Service diagnosing blood cancer earlier and treating it faster. We will start by delivering an extra 40,000 operations, scans, and appointments each week, as the first step to ensuring early diagnosis and faster treatment.T...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Blood Cancer: Medical Treatments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752483", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752895, "askingMemberId": 5132, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22164", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve access to healthcare services for children with cerebral palsy.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "We want a society where every person, including those with a long-term condition such as cerebral palsy, receives high-quality, compassionate continuity of care, with their families and carers supported. We will change the NHS so that it becomes not just ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cerebral Palsy: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752895", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752337, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21702", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve NHS diagnostic processes for glioblastoma brain tumours.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department is working with NHS England in taking steps to improve diagnostic processes in the National Health Service for all patients with cancer, including those with glioblastoma brain tumours.We will get the NHS diagnosing cancer, including brain ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Glioblastoma: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752337", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752819, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22083", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department\u2019s cancer strategy will include (a) a prostate cancer screening programme and (b) alternative measures to improve prostate cancer diagnosis for people at higher risk.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The National Cancer Plan will include further details on how we will improve outcomes for cancer patients, including those living with prostate cancer. The Plan will aim to speed up diagnosis and treatment, ensuring patients have access to the latest trea...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prostate Cancer: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752819", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752236, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21641", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure early identification of cardiac problems in young people.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "NHS England has published a suite of national service specifications and standards for Paediatric Cardiac Services, which define the standards of care expected from organisations funded by NHS England, to support and improve the diagnosis and treatment of...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Heart Diseases: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752236", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752354, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21926", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make shingles vaccinations available to all people aged over 65.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Shingles vaccination was originally routinely offered as part of the national immunisation programme to those aged 70, using the Zostavax vaccine. In 2019, the Joint Committee on Vaccination and Immunisation (JCVI) recommended that the programme should be...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Shingles: Vaccination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752354", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752747, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22037", "questionText": "To ask the Right hon. Member for Kenilworth and Southam, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, whether the Electoral Commission has issued guidance on whether a returning officer may levy a prescribed fee for the supply of an e", "answeringBodyId": 36, "answeringBodyName": "Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1560, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Electoral Commission provides guidance to support returning officers to deliver well-run elections that maintain public confidence, including on the inspection and supply of candidate spending returns and declaration.The Commission\u2019s guidance states t...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Candidates: Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752747", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752746, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22036", "questionText": "To ask the Right hon. Member for Kenilworth and Southam, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, whether the Electoral Commission has issued guidance on whether the loan of accommodation to a Parliamentary candidate in the short ", "answeringBodyId": 36, "answeringBodyName": "Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1560, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Electoral Commission\u2019s guidance sets out the law, which states that the loan of accommodation to a Parliamentary candidate during the election campaign would typically be notional spending and a donation.However, if the accommodation provided is an in...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Candidates: Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752746", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752252, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21699", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the (a) average and (b) maximum cost to the NHS was of untreated gonorrhoea in the latest year for which data is available; and what assessment he has made of the impact of this on the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The information requested is not held centrally.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gonorrhoea: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752252", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752745, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22035", "questionText": "To ask the Right hon. Member for Kenilworth and Southam, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many and what proportion of local authority returning officers have sent to the Electoral Commission copies of Parliamentary can", "answeringBodyId": 36, "answeringBodyName": "Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1560, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Electoral Commission has received candidate spending returns from returning officers for all 650 constituencies contested at the 2024 UK parliamentary general election. To support transparency, the Commission plans to publish headline spending and don...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Candidates: Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752745", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752744, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22034", "questionText": "To ask the Right hon. Member for Kenilworth and Southam, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what guidance the Electoral Commission has provided on the use of single notional invoices in candidate returns made under the Repre", "answeringBodyId": 36, "answeringBodyName": "Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1560, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Electoral Commission provides guidance to support candidates to understand the law and their reporting obligations.The guidance states that where candidates have split costs for an item of spending, each candidate must report the proportion of the cos...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Candidates: Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752744", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752352, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21924", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which body within the NHS will be conducting the review into the case for lowering the screening age for prostate cancer; what the scope of this review will be; and when he expects to receive recom", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Screening for prostate cancer is currently not recommended in the United Kingdom, due to the inaccuracy of the current best test Prostate Specific Antigen.A UK National Screening Committee (UK NSC) review looking at whether to offer screening for prostate...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prostate Cancer: Screening", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752352", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752235, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21640", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of rolling out cardiac screening to young people.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The UK National Screening Committee (UK NSC) last reviewed screening for sudden cardiac death (SCD) in people under 39 years old in 2019 and concluded that screening should not be offered. More information on the review is available at the following link:...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Heart Diseases: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752235", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752223, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21558", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of prostate cancer services in (a) Bath and North East Somerset, (b) Swindon and (c) Wiltshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department is committed to improving the adequacy of all cancer services including for prostate cancer, including cancer services in Bath and North East Somerset, Swindon and Wiltshire. NHS England has funded 10 clinical audits, including a national p...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prostate Cancer: South West", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752223", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752306, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21645", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to review the rates of the Local Housing Allowance to reflect housing costs in inner London boroughs.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 163, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The decision at Autumn Budget to maintain Local Housing Allowance (LHA) rates at current levels for 2025/26 considered a range of factors such as rental data,the Government\u2019s missions and wider fiscal context.LHA rates were last increased in April 2024 at...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Housing Allowance: Greater London", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752306", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752178, "askingMemberId": 4573, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21658", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to the correspondence of 11 December 2024 from the hon. Member for Tooting, reference number RA60941.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4253, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Home Office responded to the correspondence on 7 January.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Members: Correspondence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752178", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752435, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21823", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to extend free NHS dental repairs to teeth damaged by seizures from epilepsy.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Free National Health Service dental care is available to people who meet the following criteria: under 18 years old, or under 19 years old and in full-time education; pregnant or have had a baby in the previous 12 months; being treated in an NHS hospital ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: Epilepsy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752435", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752436, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21858", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the net cost to the public purse was of Schedule 4 and Schedule 8 compensation to operators for disruption on the rail network in 2023-24.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4943, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Schedule 4 and Schedule 8 compensation transactions are primarily between bodies whose costs and revenues are included in the Department for Transport\u2019s group budgets, therefore these have no net cost to the exchequer.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Train Operating Companies: Compensation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752436", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752200, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21732", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of biodiversity net gain in delivering for biodiversity as intended.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Mandatory biodiversity net gain is an important means of ensuring development makes a net positive contribution to nature. It is in the early stages of implementation. The policy has been designed to achieve long-term benefits for biodiversity, with major...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Biodiversity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752200", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752721, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22112", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the formal response to the public consultation on options for changing the way pavement parking is managed outside London, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of bringing fo", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "In 2020, the Department undertook a public consultation on measures for changing the way pavement parking is managed outside London. We are assessing all options and will publish a formal response to the consultation, summarising the views received and an...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parking: Pedestrian Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752721", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752347, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21681", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans she has to provide funding for the expansion of electric vehicle chargers in (a) Rutland and South Kesteven and (b) other rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Rutland County Council was allocated \u00a3569,000 and Lincolnshire County Council, which South Kesteven sits within, was allocated \u00a36,380,592 combined capital and resource funding through the Local Electric Vehicle Infrastructure (LEVI) Fund to expand public ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Charging Points", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752347", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752154, "askingMemberId": 5052, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21723", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to ensure better value for money for motor insurance customers; and what steps she is taking to make car insurers more accountable.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "We are committed to tackling the increased costs of motor insurance to deliver on our manifesto commitment, including how this impacts different demographics, geographies, and communities.The cross-government Motor Insurance Taskforce, including the stake...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Insurance: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752154", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752153, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21685", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance he has provided to Government departments on publishing details of individual Civil Service pensions for senior officials under (a) Financial Reporting requirements and (b) the Freedom of Informati", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4820, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "In relation to what guidance the Cabinet Office has provided to government departments on publishing details of individual Civil Service pensions for senior officials: (a) Financial Reporting requirements - The Cabinet Office issues an \u2018Employer Pension N...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Service: Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752153", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752415, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21814", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to help increase the availability of electric vehicle charging infrastructure.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government\u2019s Local Electric Vehicle Infrastructure Fund is providing local authorities in England with over \u00a3380m to support the installation of tens of thousands of public chargepoints. As well as significant funding, the Government continues to make...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Charging Points", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752415", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752377, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21835", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation entitled Registering historic, classic, rebuilt vehicles and vehicles converted to electric, published on 9 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The call for evidence on \u201cRegistering historic, classic, rebuilt vehicles and vehicles converted to electric\u201d was published in line with the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency\u2019s accessible documents policy.\u202fThis is available on https://www.gov.uk/governm...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Registration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752377", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752273, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21718", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the role of energy storage and back-up systems in managing the intermittency of wind and solar power generation.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4998, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government recognises the vital role of energy storage and back-up systems in delivering clean power. As set out in our Clean Power 2030 Action Plan, we are committed to developing a flexible energy system that ensures security of supply through long ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752273", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752208, "askingMemberId": 4869, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21705", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve the availability of GP appointments in Nottingham East constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "We are committed to improving capacity and access to local services across the country, including in Nottingham East. That is why we have already begun recruiting 1,000 newly qualified general practitioners (GPs) through an \u00a382 million boost to the Additi...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners: Nottingham East", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752208", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752399, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21798", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of access to emergency dentistry.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Dental Statistics - England 2023-24, published by the NHS Business Services Authority on 22 August 2024, is available at the following link:https://www.nhsbsa.nhs.uk/statistical-collections/dental-england/dental-statistics-england-202324In England, in...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752399", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752372, "askingMemberId": 5275, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21874", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the safety of LED headlights on (a) cars and (b) other vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "National collision statistics, which can record headlamp dazzle as a contributory factor, do not show any discernible trend to suggest that advances in lighting technology are contributing negatively to road vehicle collisions. However, noting increased p...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Lighting", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752372", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752560, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21954", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Road Vehicles Lighting Regulations 1989.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "All manufacturers must demonstrate that their vehicles and equipment comply with international vehicle approval requirements before they are permitted to offer their products for sale, and these include detailed provisions for vehicle lighting. The approv...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bicycles: Lighting", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752560", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752209, "askingMemberId": 4869, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21706", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of the sale of Royal Mail on its (a) workforce and (b) customers.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4418, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government has ensured that the potential takeover of Royal Mail has been properly scrutinised and that appropriate guarantees have been put in place to protect the interests of the workforce, customers and the country. These guarantees include the bi...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Royal Mail", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752209", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752272, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21717", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to speed up the delivery of planned electric vehicle charging stations.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government is taking several steps to speed up the delivery of both private and public electric vehicle chargepoints. In December, the Government announced that it will make changes to planning legislation to facilitate off-street chargepoint installa...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Charging Points", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752272", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752375, "askingMemberId": 5219, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21856", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the penalties are when the LAeq noise contour threshold at Stansted Airport is exceeded; and who enforces those noise restrictions.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4316, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "Stansted Airport\u2019s noise contour limit has been set through a local planning agreement. Enforcement of local planning conditions at Stansted Airport is a matter for the local authority, Uttlesford District Council.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Stansted Airport: Noise", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752375", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752316, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21667", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he plans to investigate the business practices of rent-a-roof companies under the (a) Feed-In-Tariff and (b) Renewable Heat Incentive scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5099, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department is aware of allegations that have been made about the business practices of some companies that operated rent-a-roof or leasing models in the Feed-in Tariff and Domestic Renewable Heat Incentive schemes. Ofgem is currently looking into thes...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Energy: Feed-in Tariffs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752316", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752400, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21799", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department plans to take to improve access to mental health services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "Too many people are not receiving the mental health care they need, and we know that waits for mental health services are too long. As part of our mission to build a National Health Service that is fit for the future and that is there when people need it,...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health Services: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752400", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752358, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21895", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of benefits for disabled people.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 163, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "The extra costs disability benefits, Attendance Allowance, Disability Living Allowance and Personal Independence Payment (PIP), provide a contribution towards the extra costs that may arise from a long-term disability or health condition. The extra costs ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Security Benefits: Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752358", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752464, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21766", "questionText": "To ask the Right hon. Member for Kenilworth and Southam, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many formal recommendations the Committee has made to the Electoral Commission since 12 December 2019.", "answeringBodyId": 36, "answeringBodyName": "Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1560, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Speaker's Committee has made no formal recomendations to the Electoral Commission since 12 December 2019.The Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission is a statutory body established in part to examine performance and to review and approve the E...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electoral Commission", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752464", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752349, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21683", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of creating a new sign asking drivers to move to the right at short slip roads.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department has not made an assessment of introducing a sign asking drivers to move to the right at short slip roads. There are currently no plans to introduce this.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Road Signs and Markings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752349", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754481, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23245", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with stakeholders on the potential side effects of the COVID-19 vaccine.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754481", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754506, "askingMemberId": 5346, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-16T00:00:00", "uin": "23244", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of revising sentencing guidelines to protect the right to protest.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754506", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754533, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23243", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will provide a breakdown of spending on brain cancer research in 2023-24.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754533", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754479, "askingMemberId": 5322, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23242", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if her Department will take steps to respond to the letter from Liberal Democrat hon. Members on the nationalisation of South Western Railway.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754479", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754507, "askingMemberId": 5319, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23241", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, which Northern Irish companies received funding from the \u00a31.8m for regional cyber skills projects.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754507", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754467, "askingMemberId": 5319, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23240", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she had discussions with the Minister of Education in Northern Ireland on Clause 56 of the Children's Wellbeing and Schools Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754467", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754487, "askingMemberId": 5304, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23239", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average wait time in the Royal Hampshire County Hospital's Accident and Emergency department was between December 2024 and January 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754487", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754486, "askingMemberId": 5304, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23238", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the cost of agency staff employed by Royal Hampshire County Hospital was in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754486", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754485, "askingMemberId": 5304, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23237", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to tackle the shortage of social care packages in (a) Royal Hampshire County Hospital and (b) Winchester.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754485", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754536, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23236", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of integrating hybrid-fuelled boilers with (a) electric air-source heat pumps and (b) smart technology to help decarbonise residential pr", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754536", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754524, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23235", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of hydrogen-hybrid vehicles on achieving the UK's net-zero emissions targets.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754524", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754482, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23234", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the use of hydrogen for heating.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754482", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754438, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23233", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of amending the Online Safety Act 2023 to help tackle fake news through (a) AI-generated content and (b) deepfakes.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754438", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754509, "askingMemberId": 5280, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23232", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of changes made to employer's National Insurance contributions at the Autumn Budget 2024 on bed provision in the private adult social care sector in (a) Scotlan", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754509", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754508, "askingMemberId": 5280, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23231", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of changes made to employer's National Insurance contributions at the Autumn Budget 2024 on costs to the private adult social care sector in (a) Scotland and (b", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754508", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754466, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23230", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people in Northern Ireland who (a) have their vehicles damaged by stolen cars where the driver is not apprehended and (b) do not have comprehensive insu", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754466", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754464, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23229", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average full-time salary was for (a) classroom and (b) all teachers in (i) academies, (ii) free schools, (iii) local authority maintained schools and (iv) all publicly-funded schools in 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754464", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754459, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23228", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation on Local audit reform: a strategy for overhauling the local audit system in England, publi", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754459", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754458, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23227", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the Consultation: provisional local government finance settlement 2025 to 2026, published on 18 December 20", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754458", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754457, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23226", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the call for evidence on DSIT Central Statistics User Engagement Exercise, published on 18 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754457", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754456, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23225", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation on Raising product standards for space heating, published on 17 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754456", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754455, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23224", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment with the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation on Provisional police grant allocations: 2025", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754455", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754454, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23223", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation on Copyright and Artificial Intelligence, published on 17 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754454", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754453, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23222", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make an assessment with the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation on UK Emissions Trading Scheme: free ", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754453", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754452, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23221", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make an assessment with the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation on Benchmarking operators\u2019 performance in rail passenge", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754452", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754451, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23220", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make an assessment with the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation on Draft information and guidance on storm overflows, p", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754451", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754450, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23219", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the call for evidence on Capacity Market: consumer-led flexibility, published on 16 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754450", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754449, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23218", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation on Capacity Market: proposals to modernise Rules and improve participation and delivery assurance of con", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754449", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754448, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23217", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation on Proposed changes to the water company drought plan guideline, published on 16 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754448", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754447, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23216", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what discussions he has had with the Regulatory Innovation Office on (a) detecting, (b) preventing, and (c) removing child sexual abuse images created by generative artificial intellige", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754447", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754446, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23215", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what discussions he has had with the Government Office for Technology Transfer on (a) detecting, (b) preventing, and (c) removing child sexual abuse images created by generative artific", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754446", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754445, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23214", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of AI regulation in (a) detecting, (b) preventing, and (c) removing child sexual abuse images created by generative artificial intelligence.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754445", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754443, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23213", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether he has had discussions with universities on the UK's approach to supporting research into (a) detecting, (b) preventing and (c) removing child sexual abuse images created by gen", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754443", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754442, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23212", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether he has had discussions with businesses on the UK's approach to supporting research into (a) detecting, (b) preventing and (c) removing child sexual abuse images created by gener", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754442", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754441, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23211", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether he has had discussions with UK Research and Innovation on their approach to supporting research into (a) detecting, (b) preventing and (c) removing child sexual abuse images cre", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754441", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754440, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23210", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether he plans to produce a domestic research strategy for (a) detecting, (b) preventing and (c) removing child sexual abuse images created by generative Artificial Intelligence.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754440", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754439, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23209", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether he has had discussions with Horizon Europe on opportunities for research into (a) detecting, (b) preventing and (c) removing child sexual abuse images created by generative Arti", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754439", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754480, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23208", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of single justice procedure convictions were for which recordable offences in the most recent year for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754480", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754505, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23207", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Pakistani counterpart on returning people from that country convicted for involvement in grooming gangs.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754505", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754436, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23206", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will take steps to ensure that the Norfolk County Council elections take place on 1 May 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754436", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754473, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23205", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she plans to extend the assurances provided on funding for the increase in employer National Insurance costs to NHS Trusts to general practice.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754473", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754510, "askingMemberId": 5146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23204", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will issue guidance to local authorities on priority need for housing for people living with HIV.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754510", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754499, "askingMemberId": 5146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23203", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to help ensure the adequacy of the number of wheelchair spaces on (a) buses and (b) other public transport.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754499", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754497, "askingMemberId": 5146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23202", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to (a) support children in foster care and (b) the work of foster carers (i) in Gedling constituency and (ii) nationally.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754497", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754496, "askingMemberId": 5146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23201", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 5.149 of the Autumn Budget, whether receipts from right to buy sales (a) are ringfenced for new council housing or (b) can be used for general spending by local authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754496", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754495, "askingMemberId": 5146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23200", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help (a) provide timely (i) diagnosis and (ii) treatment and (b) improve other support for adults with autism.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754495", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754494, "askingMemberId": 5146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23199", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve the care of people with Addison's disease including (a) providing clearer information and (b) ensuring timely access to (i) treatment and (ii) support.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754494", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754493, "askingMemberId": 5146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23198", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to ensure that (a) patients requiring Creon are updated on the availability of that medication and (b) local guidance issued by (i) his Department and (ii) NHS England is shar", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754493", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754420, "askingMemberId": 5112, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23197", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what information his Department holds on whether drones have been used by the military regime against civilians in Myanmar.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754420", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754538, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23196", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to support vulnerable pensioners during winter 2024-25, in the context of changes to the eligibility criteria for the winter fuel payment.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754538", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754526, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23195", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to help increase storage levels of gas.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754526", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754417, "askingMemberId": 5079, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23194", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the availability of Bedrocan oil.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754417", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754428, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23193", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the availability of NHS cognitive behavioural therapy for insomnia; and whether he plans to increase the coverage of that therapy.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754428", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754427, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23192", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of reducing non-compliance fines in the Clean Heat Market Mechanism on the uptake of heat pumps.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754427", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754426, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23191", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the decision to reduce non-compliance fines in the Clean Heat Market Mechanism on the UK's ability to meet carbon budgets.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754426", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754425, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23190", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make it his policy to return non-compliance fines for the clean heat market mechanism to the level proposed for 2026 in the document entitled Clean Heat Market Mechanism Consultati", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754425", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754537, "askingMemberId": 5074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23189", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of requiring the NHS to pay for all medications supplied to hospices.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754537", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754535, "askingMemberId": 5074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23188", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which hospices (a) have all medication supplied (i) for free and (ii) at a discounted rate and (b) do not have medication supplied by the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754535", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754423, "askingMemberId": 5054, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23187", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of participants in university Officer Training Corps complete the (a) Army Reserve Commissioning Course and (b) Commissioning Course for Regular Officers.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754423", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754492, "askingMemberId": 5053, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-16T00:00:00", "uin": "23186", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of when the review into the proposed North Derbyshire University Academy free school project in Bolsover will be completed.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754492", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754419, "askingMemberId": 5050, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23185", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2024 to Question 15845 on Small Businesses: Recruitment, when he plans to publish the small business strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754419", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754498, "askingMemberId": 4860, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23184", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the police national computer retains nominal records for non-resident people.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754498", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754503, "askingMemberId": 4846, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23183", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on attacks on (a) international aid agencies and (b) their (i) facilities and (ii) staff in northern Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754503", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754518, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23182", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to protect the countryside and wildlife, in the context of her Department's proposed planning reforms.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754518", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754411, "askingMemberId": 4828, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23181", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what actions is her Department taking to mitigate the rise in employer NI contributions on the homelessness charities.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754411", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754418, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23180", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department have had meetings with representatives of the British Society for Genetic Medicine in the last 30 years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754418", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754409, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23179", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2024 to Question HL2771 on Civil Servants: Recruitment, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of crown servant internships not being open those of white Briti", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754409", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754431, "askingMemberId": 4806, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23178", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will direct her Department to share all submissions received for the call for input on single-sex spaces with the Equality and Human Rights Commission.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754431", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754500, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-17T00:00:00", "uin": "23177", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2024 to Question 20261 on Rugby, if she will have further discussions with (a) the Rugby Football Union and (b) Premiership Rugby on (i) current governance i", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754500", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754460, "askingMemberId": 4777, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23176", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce waiting times for autism diagnoses.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754460", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754484, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23175", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing (a) licencing for builders and (b) affordable recourse for people impacted by rogue builders.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754484", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754483, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23174", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of requiring cyclists and motorcyclists to wear high visibility attire after dark.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754483", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754413, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23173", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make an assessment of the potential implications for his policies of the Institute of the Motor Industry's survey entitled EV TechSafe Technician Forecasts - Jan 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754413", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754412, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23172", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of increasing the use of hydrometallurgical separation in the recycling of electric vehicle batteries to help facilitate the recovery of li", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754412", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754531, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23171", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the use of (a) e-scooters and (b) e-bikes on pavements on pedestrians.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754531", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754521, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23170", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department,  pursuant to\u00a0the Answer of 9\u00a0January 2025\u00a0to\u00a0Question 21024 on Migrants: Detainees, if she will specify whether each Brook House Inquiry recommendation has been (a) accepted, (b) partially accepted, (", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754521", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754421, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23169", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve access to (a) healthcare services, (b) GPs and (c) mental health support in (i) Ashfield and (ii) Mansfield constituencies.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754421", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754478, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23168", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether he has had recent discussions with the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on the use of artificial intelligence in farming and agriculture.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754478", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754477, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23167", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to tackle modern slavery in illegal hand carwashes.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754477", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754437, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23166", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) workers and (b) temporary workers each of the sponsors on the register of licensed sponsors sponsored in each year for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754437", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754504, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23165", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of (a) trends in the level of costs of medicines and (b) potential closures of community pharmacies.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754504", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754474, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23164", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will include a target for the number of social rent homes in the long-term housing strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754474", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754472, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23163", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she plans to take if local authorities do not meet their local housing targets.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754472", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754444, "askingMemberId": 4598, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23162", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made a recent assessment of the potential merits of (a) revising the school calendar and (b) reducing the length of the school summer holidays.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754444", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754471, "askingMemberId": 4573, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-16T00:00:00", "uin": "23161", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of increasing the regulation of private dental charges.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754471", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754470, "askingMemberId": 4573, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-16T00:00:00", "uin": "23160", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to make dentistry more affordable.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754470", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754488, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23159", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she plans to publish a summary of findings from the call for evidence on fit note reform.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754488", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754465, "askingMemberId": 4521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23158", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment she has made of the potential merits of routinely publishing disaggregated data for\u00a0Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754465", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754491, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23157", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the delay to the publication of his Department's annual statistics on armed forces equipment will impact the scheduling of other departmental (a) reports and (b) reviews.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754491", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754490, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23156", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many meetings he has held with the incoming US administration on the terms of the Diego Garcia military base as part of the Chagos settlement.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754490", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754489, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23155", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of the UK\u2019s contribution to the cost of Chagos settlement will be funded from his Department\u2019s budget.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754489", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754476, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23154", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to his Department's press release Home upgrade revolution as renters set for warmer homes and cheaper bills, published on 23 September 2024, when he plans to consult on new EPC", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754476", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754529, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23153", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she plans to publish a consultation on data sharing powers between relevant government agencies and political parties.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754529", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754525, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23152", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how the Casey Commission on social care will consult local government.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754525", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754523, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23151", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to prevent potential intimidation of people of the Jewish faith during protest marches past synagogues.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754523", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754522, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23150", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the section entitled timelines and next steps of her Department\u2019s letter to local councils of 16 December 2024 on the devolution white paper, what the methodolo", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754522", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754520, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23149", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2025 to Question 17565 on Chinese Embassy: Planning Permission, if she will place in the Library a copy of the correspondence between her Depa", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754520", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754519, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23148", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2025 to Question 17127 on Levelling Up and Regeneration Act 2023, if she will list each section of the Levelling Up and Regeneration Act that ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754519", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754517, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23147", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2025 to Question 17127 on Levelling Up and Regeneration Act 2023, if she will list each section of the Levelling Up and Regeneration Act 2023 ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754517", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754516, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23146", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2025 to Question 20841 on Local Plans, what parts of the local development scheme will local planning authorities be required to update by Mar", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754516", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754515, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23145", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many times local planning authorities will be required to update Local Plans following (a) the new National Planning Policy Framework, (b) the creation of Strategic Developme", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754515", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754514, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23144", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2025 to Question 20655 on Housing: Migrants, what information her Department holds on the potential impact of immigration on housing costs.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754514", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754513, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23143", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the guidance entitled Council of the Nations and Regions: Terms of Reference, published on 17 October 2024, in which Department is the (a) secretariat and (b) d", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754513", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754512, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23142", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2025 to Question HL3612 on Unitary Councils, what she classes as a small unitary authority.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754512", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754511, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23141", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, which local authorities responded to her Department's letter of 16 December 2024 on local government restructuring to (a) express a formal interest and (b) request that May 2025 ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754511", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754422, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23140", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to make the Chartered Town Planner Level 7 Apprenticeship exempt from any reforms in access to the new Growth and Skills Levy.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754422", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754408, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23139", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the policy paper entitled Planning Reform Working Paper: Planning Committees, published on 9 December 2024, whether the requirements for delegation to planning ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754408", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754416, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23138", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential implications of the number of asylum seekers entering the UK in December 2024 for (a) community cohesion and (b) the use of hotels for housing asylum seek", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754416", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754415, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23137", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of UK nationals in countries bordering the Red Sea.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754415", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754414, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23136", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2024 to Question 19316 on Development Aid: Review, what progress he has made on consideration of the Development Review.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754414", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754534, "askingMemberId": 1482, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23135", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the proportion of children of peripatetic families not in school who will be captured by the proposed register of home schooled children.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754534", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754532, "askingMemberId": 1482, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23134", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the penalty for late payment for not registering home schooled children will be; and what the maximum penalty will be in the event of continued non-payment.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754532", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754530, "askingMemberId": 1482, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23133", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the monetary penalty issued to a person who has not registered their child would be under clause 436E of the Children's Wellbeing and Schools Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754530", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754528, "askingMemberId": 1482, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23132", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to provide additional funding to local authorities to (a) create and (b) enforce a register of children not in school.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754528", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754527, "askingMemberId": 1482, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23131", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the cost to local authorities of (a) establishing and (b) maintaining a register of home schooled children.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754527", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754475, "askingMemberId": 1466, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23130", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information her Department holds on the number of window cleaners electrocuted whilst using water-fed poles in each year for which records are available.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754475", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754429, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23129", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 18 November 2024 to Question 14029 on British Nationality (Irish Citizens) Act 2024, when the operational changes to implement the new route will be completed.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754429", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754424, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23128", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December to Question 16717 on Armed Forces: Cadets, what external organisations other than (a) existing cadets and (b) adult volunteers he is consulting to help expand numbers.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754424", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754410, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23127", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions he has had with relevant stakeholders on the cost of developing Casement Park.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754410", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754469, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23126", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) new and (b) replacement passports were issued in 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754469", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754468, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23125", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has made a recent assessment the effectiveness of self-regulation by the gambling industry with regard to gambling advertising.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754468", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754463, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23124", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the contribution of farming to the economy of (a) South Holland and the Deepings constituency and (b) Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754463", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754462, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23123", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to help small and medium sized businesses with energy costs in (a) South Holland and the Deepings constituency and (b) Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754462", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754461, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23122", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of the proposed Grimsby to Walpole pylon project on the availability of farmland.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754461", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754435, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23121", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she plans to support new FM licences for radio stations in (a) South Holland and the Deepings constituency and (b) Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754435", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754434, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23120", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the number of children that were home-schooled in Lincolnshire in the (a) 2022-23 and (b) 2023-2024 academic years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754434", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754433, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23119", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of the ban on the use of neonicotinoids on agricultural crops on (a) bee and (b) butterfly population trends.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754433", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754432, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23118", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of increases in employer National Insurance contributions on agricultural businesses.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754432", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754430, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23117", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many incidents of flooding have been reported in (a) South Holland and the Deepings constituency and (b) Lincolnshire in the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754430", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754502, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23116", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to discuss the Tonnage Tax scheme with (a) Cabinet colleagues, (b) shipowners and (c) maritime trade unions as part of the current Spending Review.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754502", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754501, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-10T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23115", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the update to Non-structural tax relief statistics, published on 5 December 2024, if she will provide an annual breakdown of the relief from Corporation Tax received by qualifying shipowners in the", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754501", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754162, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23114", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps with his counterparts in the devolved Administrations to implement a national strategy for treating neurological conditions.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754162", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754141, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23113", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps with his counterparts in the devolved Administrations to implement a national brain cancer strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754141", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754158, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23112", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of introducing a national safeguarding framework for all educational institutions including academies.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754158", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754157, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23111", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to introduce a standardised complaints process for academy schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754157", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754144, "askingMemberId": 5358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23110", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2024 to Question 20496 on Scotland Office: Media, which contractors were used for the spending on media training; and which Ministers received the training.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754144", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754143, "askingMemberId": 5358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23109", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 January 2025 to Question 20491 on Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office: Media, which contractors were used for the spending on media train", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754143", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754142, "askingMemberId": 5358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23108", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 23 December 2024 to Question 20489 on Treasury: Media, which contractors were used for the spending on media training; and which Ministers received the media training.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754142", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754150, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23107", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when his Department plans to publish its land use framework.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754150", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754146, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23106", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will undertake a review of the prescription charge exemption list to include more (a) chronic and (b) lifelong conditions.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754146", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754145, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23105", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of increasing the tax allowance for pensioners to \u00a315,000.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754145", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754139, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23104", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has plans to increase funding for STEM education\u00a0at secondary school level.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754139", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754156, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23103", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to involve communities and stakeholders in the development of a new Clean Air Strategy; and what his planned timetable is for completing the strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754156", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754155, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23102", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Department's press release entitled, Government launches rapid review to meet Environment Act targets, published on 30 July 2024, whether the rapid review of the ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754155", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754154, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23101", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he will publish the (a) interim and (b) final report from the Air Quality Information System Review.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754154", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754153, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23100", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2024 to Question 7788 on Air Pollution, if his Department will take steps to amend clean air targets to bring the UK in line with the European Unio", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754153", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754152, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23099", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Independent report by the Disabled Persons Transport Advisory Committee entitled DPTAC position on the eligibility criteria for concessionary bus travel, published on 17 August 2022, wheth", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754152", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754151, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23098", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 November 2024 to Question 14270 on Press: Regulation, what work her Department is undertaking on this issue; which other Departments have participated; and if she wil", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754151", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754137, "askingMemberId": 5308, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23097", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of recent changes to Meta guidelines on hateful conduct which allow Facebook users to refer to LGBT+ people as mentally ill.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754137", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754136, "askingMemberId": 5308, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23096", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what role rural digital connectivity will have in the industrial strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754136", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754148, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23095", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress his Department has made on designating a successor to the standard issue L85A3 service rifle.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754148", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754134, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23094", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps he is taking to help ensure that pornographic sites remove content that promote a sexual interest in children.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754134", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754133, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23093", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment he has made of the role of online pornographic content in perpetuating violence against women and girls.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754133", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754132, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23092", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps he is taking to regulate (a) online and (b) offline pornography to help meet the Government's target of halving violence against women and girls within a decade.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754132", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754131, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23091", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps he is taking to monitor the impact of online and offline pornography on violence against women and girls.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754131", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754129, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23090", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will take steps to ensure that all defibrillators installed at train stations are (a) registered and (b) visible on The Circuit national defibrillator network website.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754129", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754128, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23089", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will take steps to help ensure that emergency services are provided with up to date information on the (a) location and (b) status of defibrillators installed at train stations.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754128", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754147, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23088", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of strengthening media literacy programmes in the ongoing Curriculum and Assessment Review.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754147", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754140, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23087", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the integration of (a) political and (b) media literacy into school curriculums.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754140", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754138, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23086", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of varying fuel prices at nation-wide service station providers; and what steps she is taking to ensure equity for customers.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754138", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754135, "askingMemberId": 5273, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23085", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what plans his Department has to ensure that (a) commercial and (b) retail units utilise (i) solar panels and (ii) other renewable energy sources.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754135", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754130, "askingMemberId": 5273, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23084", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to improve the accessibility of the railways for disabled people.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754130", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754161, "askingMemberId": 5271, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23083", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to increase the (a) number and (b) size of (i) national parks and (ii) national park cities.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754161", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754160, "askingMemberId": 5271, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23082", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to empower (a) individuals, (b) grassroots organisations and (c) local authorities to increase (i) green spaces and (ii) biodiversity in their", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754160", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754159, "askingMemberId": 5271, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23081", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to increase green spaces in urban communities.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754159", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754149, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23080", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the average processing time for Disclosure and Barring Service checks conducted through Sussex Police.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754149", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754045, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23079", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to update guidance on how funds are allocated to GP surgeries in places with high demand such as Seaford, East Essex.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754045", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754044, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23078", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to support communities with high levels of housing growth where necessary infrastructure is not in place; and if she will have discussions wit", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754044", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753984, "askingMemberId": 5259, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23077", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she plans to expand the Flood Recovery Framework to households which (a) have been affected outside named storms and (b) are at risk of flooding in the future.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753984", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753982, "askingMemberId": 5259, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23076", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Flood Recovery Framework will be activated for the flooding in Leicestershire.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753982", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754013, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23075", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of the resources available to local government for planning enforcement in (a) Devon and (b) Somerset.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754013", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753955, "askingMemberId": 5250, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-29T00:00:00", "uin": "23074", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will provide funding to (a) improve water quality in the river Tone in Somerset and (b) reduce pollution discharges (i) upstream of French Weir Bathing Water and (ii) downstream ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753955", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753952, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23073", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 8 January 2025 to Question 21859, on Flexible Working Taskforce, on what dates that taskforce met in each year from 2018 to 2022.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753952", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754072, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23072", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will issue guidance to NHS Trusts on adopting a standardised FOI request system.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754072", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754092, "askingMemberId": 5199, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23071", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with stakeholders on intermittent shortages of (a) Olanzapine and (b) other anti-psychosis medicines in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754092", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754009, "askingMemberId": 5166, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23070", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that people with (a) fibromyalgia, (b) ADHD and (c) other invisible disabilities are supported back into work.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754009", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754101, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23069", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will make an estimate of the annual cost of regulatory compliance for businesses in each of the last five years; and if she will make a comparative estimate of the cost of regulatory compliance (", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754101", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754096, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23068", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what the annual subsidy is for renewable energy projects; and what the average increase in consumer energy bills was in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754096", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754095, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23067", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what the total expenditure was on achieving net zero targets in each year since 2015 by sector; and what the corresponding estimated total reduction in global emissions was in the same period", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754095", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754094, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23066", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of migrants that have been granted (a) asylum and (b) leave to remain in the last five years are receiving Universal Credit; and what estimate she has made of the projected ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754094", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754093, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23065", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the annual cost to the public purse of providing public services including (a) healthcare, (b) education and (c) housing of migrants that have arrived via small boat cros", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754093", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754091, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23064", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of migrants who entered in the UK in the last 5 years are in receipt of state benefits.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754091", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754084, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23063", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to help tackle crimes committed by individuals who have entered the country illegally.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754084", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753999, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23062", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure asylum seekers are no longer housed in hotels in Boston and Skegness constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753999", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753998, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23061", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of excluding people on Personal Independence Payment from eligibility for the winter fuel payment on their ability to meet energy costs.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753998", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753997, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23060", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much his Department has spent on measures to achieve net zero targets in the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753997", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753996, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23059", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how much his Department has spent on measures to achieve net zero targets in the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753996", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753995, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23058", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department has spent on measures to achieve net zero targets in the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753995", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753994, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23057", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how much his Department has spent on measures to achieve net zero targets in the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753994", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753993, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23056", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has spent on measures to achieve net zero targets in the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753993", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753992, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23055", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on measures to achieve net zero targets in the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753992", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753985, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23054", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps he is taking to help improve mobile phone signal coverage in rural areas of Boston and Skegness constituency; and what plans he has to ensure that (a) residents and (b) busin", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753985", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753981, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23053", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will increase police funding in Boston and Skegness constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753981", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753980, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23052", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people who received grants for heat source pumps under (a) the Green Homes Grant and (b) similar schemes are supported when systems prove un", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753980", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754127, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23051", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on how many (a) police officers, (b) officials of local authorities and (c) social workers who were found to have had knowledge at the time of grooming by Pakista", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754127", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754098, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23050", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when a final decision on elections to Norfolk County Council will be made.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754098", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754097, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23049", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what impact the Devolution Priority Programme will have on elections to Norfolk County Council.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754097", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754083, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23048", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of encouraging council tax discounts for residents in authorities without elections on 1 May 2025 due to participation in t", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754083", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754071, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23047", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of providing an alternative title for county councillors who remain in office after 1 May 2025 due to their authority\u2019s par", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754071", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753962, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-17T00:00:00", "uin": "23046", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students were classified as educated otherwise than at school in the latest period for which figures are available; and how many children receiving educated otherwise than at school funding received le", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753962", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754079, "askingMemberId": 5126, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23045", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of police-support staffing levels in England and Wales; and whether her Department has been made aware of instances where police officers have been ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754079", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754010, "askingMemberId": 5112, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23044", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of planned East Coast Main Line timetable change in December 2025 on local rail services in (a) County Durham and (b) the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754010", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754008, "askingMemberId": 5112, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23043", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential implications for her policies of trends in levels of retail and commercial units that are vacant in (a) Chester-le-Street, (b) Sta", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754008", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754007, "askingMemberId": 5112, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23042", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Biggest investment into hospices in a generation, dated 19 December 2024, how much of the \u00a3100 million funding will be allocated to the Nor", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754007", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754082, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23041", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to implement the recommendations of the report by Professor Alexis Jay entitled Report of the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse, HC 720, published on 20 October 2022.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754082", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753988, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23040", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on supporting transport providers to buy British buses.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753988", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753987, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23039", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if the Jet Zero Taskforce Group will make an assessment of the potential merits of transitioning Grangemouth into a Sustainable Aviation Fuel facility.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753987", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753983, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23038", "questionText": "To ask the Leader of the House, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of recent answers to Written Questions in the context of improving transparency in Government.", "answeringBodyId": 34, "answeringBodyName": "Leader of the House", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753983", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754089, "askingMemberId": 5074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23037", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much has been spent on flood prevention works to protect the village of Croston in South Ribble constituency in the last five years; and what funds are allocated for future improve", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754089", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754086, "askingMemberId": 5074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23036", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of pensioners receive Pension Credit in South Ribble constituency; and how many of these are new recipients since 31 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754086", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754077, "askingMemberId": 5068, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23035", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support communities affected by recent flooding in Leicester; and whether he plans to make a flood recovery grant available to local authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754077", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753986, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23034", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of maladministration around communications of State Pension age changes on the six sample cases in the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman's", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753986", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754061, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23033", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 6 September 2024 to Question 2316 on Equality, whether the socio-economic duty will apply to (a) Police and Crime Commissioners and (b) Police Constables.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754061", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754060, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23032", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what flags she plans to fly outside her Department other than the Union flag in the next 12 months; and on which days each flag will be flown.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754060", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754059, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23031", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 7 October 2024 to Question 7443 on Trade Unions: Subversion, whether the Foreign Influence Registration Scheme will regulate foreign actors seeking to (a) lobby and (b) influ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754059", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754058, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23030", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has issued guidance to political parties on the United States of America\u2019s Foreign Agents Registration Scheme for campaigning overseas.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754058", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754039, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23029", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, what industrial disputes are ongoing within (a) their Department and (b) each of the arm\u2019s length bodies connected to their Department; how many (i) staff and (ii) contractors are involved in each dispute; what the form of in", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754039", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754038, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23028", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what industrial disputes are ongoing within (a) their Department and (b) each of the arm\u2019s length bodies connected to their Department; how many (i) staff and (ii) contractors are invo", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754038", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754037, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23027", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what industrial disputes are ongoing within (a) their Department and (b) each of the arm\u2019s length bodies connected to their Department; how many (i) staff and (ii) contractors are involved in each dispute; what the", "answeringBodyId": 28, "answeringBodyName": "Wales Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754037", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754036, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23026", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what industrial disputes are ongoing within (a) their Department and (b) each of the arm\u2019s length bodies connected to their Department; how many (i) staff and (ii) contractors are involved in each dispute; what ", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754036", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754035, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23025", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what industrial disputes are ongoing within (a) their Department and (b) each of the arm\u2019s length bodies connected to their Department; how many (i) staff and (ii) contractors are involved in each disput", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754035", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754034, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23024", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what industrial disputes are ongoing within (a) their Department and (b) each of the arm\u2019s length bodies connected to their Department; how many (i) staff and (ii) contractors are invol", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754034", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754032, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23023", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what industrial disputes are ongoing within (a) their Department and (b) each of the arm\u2019s length bodies connected to their Department; how many (i) staff and (ii) contractors are involved in each dispute; what", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754032", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754031, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23022", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what industrial disputes are ongoing within (a) their Department and (b) each of the arm\u2019s length bodies connected to their Department; how many (i) staff and (ii) contractors are involved in each dispute; what t", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754031", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754030, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23021", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what industrial disputes are ongoing within (a) their Department and (b) each of the arm\u2019s length bodies connected to their Department; how many (i) staff and (ii) contractors are involved in each dispu", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754030", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754029, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23020", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what industrial disputes are ongoing within (a) their Department and (b) each of the arm\u2019s length bodies connected to their Department; how many (i) staff and (ii) contractors are involved in eac", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754029", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753931, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23019", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department issues to schools and local education authorities on the teaching around the British Empire in the National Curriculum.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753931", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754126, "askingMemberId": 5054, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23018", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with refence to the Council of Reserve Forces and Cadets\u2019 Associations' Annual Statutory Report 2024, published on 17 December 2024, what steps he has taken to ensure training courses are adapted to take account ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754126", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754125, "askingMemberId": 5054, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23017", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what funding options are available to students in (a) higher education and (b) further education who commit to joining the Reserves.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754125", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754124, "askingMemberId": 5054, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23016", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the his Department's report entitled Reserve Forces Review 2030: Unlocking the reserves\u2019 potential to strengthen a resilient and global Britain, published in May 2021, what targeted programmes e", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754124", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754123, "askingMemberId": 5054, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23015", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of taking steps to increase recognition and accreditation of relevant civilian courses to facilitate recruitment of university students into the Reserves.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754123", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754017, "askingMemberId": 5048, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23014", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 86 of the document entitled Academies consolidated annual report and accounts: 2021 to 2022, published on 5 February 2024, whether it is her Department's policy that off-payroll arrangeme", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754017", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754016, "askingMemberId": 5048, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23013", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the number of academy trusts that have reported off-payroll arrangements for staff who are also trustees in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754016", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753951, "askingMemberId": 5044, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23012", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking with the voluntary sector to introduce new ways of treating mental ill health.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753951", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753950, "askingMemberId": 5044, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23011", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to (a) help prevent and (b) increase early intervention for mental ill health.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753950", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753949, "askingMemberId": 5044, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23010", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking with the (a) NHS and (b) voluntary sector to introduce (i) clinical and (ii) non-clinical responses for young people with mental health needs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753949", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754015, "askingMemberId": 5038, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23009", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve care for people living with arthritis.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754015", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753964, "askingMemberId": 5038, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23008", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of access to specialist speech and language therapy services for children in (a) Merseyside and (b) Knowsley constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753964", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754012, "askingMemberId": 5031, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "23007", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support democracy in Georgia.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754012", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754003, "askingMemberId": 5031, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-16T00:00:00", "uin": "23006", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate she has made of the (a) total cost to the public purse for, (b) proportion of her Department\u2019s total expenditure that was spent on and (c) spend per head for transport infrastructure in (a) the No", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754003", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754000, "askingMemberId": 5031, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-16T00:00:00", "uin": "23005", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what comparative estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of spending on road infrastructure in (a) the North East and (b) England over the last 15 years by (i) percentage of total Departmental spe", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754000", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753947, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "23004", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to include the perspectives of people with lived experiences of homelessness in the cross-government strategy to end homelessness.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753947", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753970, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23003", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of Electronic Travel Authorisation exemptions for tourists travelling from Dublin to Northern Ireland for one week or less.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753970", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753968, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23002", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of Electronic Travel Authorisations on (a) tourism and (b) the economy in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753968", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753967, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23001", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions her Department has had with (a) the (i) Northern Ireland and (ii) Ireland tourism industry and (b) other stakeholders on the introduction of Electronic Travel Authorisations.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753967", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753966, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "23000", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions her Department has held with the (a) Northern Ireland Executive and (b) Irish Government on the introduction of Electronic Travel Authorisations.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753966", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754122, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22999", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what her Department\u2019s definition of a tax break is.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754122", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754121, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22998", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2025 to Question 21387 on Rachel Reeves: Self-assessment, for what reason she does not plan to publish her tax return.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754121", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754120, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22997", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2025 to Question 19415 on Ed Miliband, whether the Rt Hon Member for Islington North (a) made an application for and (b) received a severance payment.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754120", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754119, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22996", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish of the questionnaire form that incoming Ministers are asked to provide to the Propriety and Ethics Team.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754119", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754118, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22995", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2024 to Question 13808 on 9 Downing Street: Media, whether refurbishment works had been commissioned when this Answer was given.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754118", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754117, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22994", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the answer of 27 December 2024 to Question 20832 on Special Advisers: Pay, if he will ensure that the list of special advisers is published by 31 March 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754117", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754116, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22993", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether Baroness Casey made a declaration of political activity following her appointment as Lead Non-Executive Director.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754116", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754113, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22992", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 9 January 2025 to Question 21403 on Cabinet Office: Pay, whether the mean salary of civil servants in the (a) Women's Equality Unit, (b) Race Disparity Unit and (c) Disability Unit will", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754113", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753959, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22991", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 8 January 2025 to Question 19414 on Non-departmental Public Bodies, how many non-departmental public bodies the Government plans to (a) open and (b) close.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753959", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753958, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22990", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 January 2025 to Question 16332 on Undocumented Migrants, whether she plans to make an estimate of the number of people in the UK illegally.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753958", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753926, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22989", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of (a) 6 January 2025 to Question 21057 on Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs: Unpaid Work and (b) 20 November 2024 to Question 14502 on Gender: Equality, whether guidanc", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753926", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753935, "askingMemberId": 4806, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22988", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2025 to Question 21052 on Gender: Public Consultation, if she will publish the submissions to the call for input on single-sex spaces which were determined not to meet the c", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753935", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753934, "askingMemberId": 4806, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22987", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2025 to Question 21052 on Gender: Public Consultation, if she will publish the submissions to the call for input on single-sex spaces which were determined to have met the s", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753934", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754062, "askingMemberId": 4787, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22986", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to National Audit Office's report entitled, public service pensions, published on 19 March 2021, whether her Department plans to publish updated statistics on the balancing payments made to pensions s", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754062", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753961, "askingMemberId": 4787, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22985", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made in reducing waiting times for (a) speech and language therapy services and (b) neurodevelopmental services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753961", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753960, "askingMemberId": 4787, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22984", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of patients waiting over 52 weeks for elective care in (a) England, (b) Norfolk and Waveney ICB area and (c) Queen Elizabeth King's Lynn Hospital Trust; and ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753960", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753978, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22983", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Pension Credit applications her Department has received in each of the last 12 months; and how many such applications were processed within the 50 day target.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753978", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753963, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-17T00:00:00", "uin": "22982", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of NHS staff have been vaccinated for flu (a) this year and (b) at this stage in the flu cycle in each of the last four years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753963", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754028, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22981", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make an assessment of the sustainability of energy produced by Drax power station in the last 12 years.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754028", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754026, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22980", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether the Government plans to continue providing subsidy payments to the Drax power station.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754026", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754025, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22979", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to help (a) first-time buyers and (b) low-income families secure housing in Ashfield constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754025", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754024, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22978", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to support (a) victims and (b) victims families impacted by grooming gangs; and what steps she is taking to ensure these incidents don't occur in the future.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754024", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754023, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22977", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to support (a) vocational training and (b) apprenticeship programs in Ashfield constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754023", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754066, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22976", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department will continue to support the Rural Housing Enablers Scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754066", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754090, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22975", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, when he plans to roll out the Warm Homes Plan to Runcorn and Helsby constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754090", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754087, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22974", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of young people not in employment, education or training in Runcorn and Helsby constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754087", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753946, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22973", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of support provided to care leavers to access higher education.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753946", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754078, "askingMemberId": 4651, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22972", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of (a) access to (i) deposit and (ii) withdraw cash and (b) the availability of trained people to help with cash access services in Liverpool Walton con", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754078", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754046, "askingMemberId": 4651, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22971", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the US Surgeon General\u2019s recommendations to include health warnings on alcohol labels; and whether he has plans to re-v", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754046", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754074, "askingMemberId": 4573, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22970", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to increase awareness of e-visas in other countries.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754074", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754111, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22969", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason have the annual armed forces equipment statistics not been published.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754111", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754110, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22968", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his planned timetable is for publishing his Department's annual statistics on armed forces equipment.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754110", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754109, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22967", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the MySafety (DURALS) system in recording incidents involving defence personnel.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754109", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754108, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22966", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to avoid underreporting of incidents relating to injuries of civilian and military personnel.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754108", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754106, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22965", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to help protect untrained military personnel from injury during training exercises.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754106", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754105, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22964", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to help mitigate injury rates among armed forces personnel during training exercises.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754105", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754104, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22963", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussion he has had with representatives of the United States administration on the cost to US armed forces of the leaseback of the Diego Garcia military base as part of the Chagos settlement.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754104", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754103, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22962", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of the cost of leasing the Diego Garcia military base will be covered by the United States.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754103", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754102, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22961", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of recent trends in borrowing costs on the Government's capacity to increase defence spending to 2.5% of GDP expenditure.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754102", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753945, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22960", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he has met representatives of farming businesses in South Suffolk constituency to discuss recent trends in farm incomes.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753945", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753944, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22959", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support farm businesses to adapt to adverse weather conditions.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753944", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753943, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22958", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to help mitigate the impact of (a) increased rainfall and (b) storms on arable farm output.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753943", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753942, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22957", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of adverse weather conditions on arable farm output in South Suffolk constituency in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753942", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753941, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22956", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of recent trends in the level of farm incomes in South Suffolk constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753941", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753940, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22955", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has for procuring a replacement for the Hawk T2.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753940", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753939, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22954", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on the number of occasions classified military secrets have been leaked on the online war simulation entitled War Thunder.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753939", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753938, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22953", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to help prevent the leaking of military secrets during online war games.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753938", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753937, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22952", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Defence Recycling and Disposals Team have commenced commercial negotiations with potential buyers for (a) HMS Bulwark and (b) HMS Albion.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753937", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753936, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22951", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the oral contribution by the Minister for Defence Procurement and Industry of 6 January 2025, Official Report, column 586, what the disposal plan is for (a) HMS Albion and (b) HMS Bulwark.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753936", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753933, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22950", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has had recent discussions with the Secretary of State for Education on the potential impact of protest-related activity on university campuses on the ability of defence companies to participate in car", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753933", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754088, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22949", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what role the Fair Work Agency will play in ensuring businesses observe best practice when granting their employees maternity leave.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754088", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754085, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22948", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what the role of the Fair Work Agency will be in helping to ensure businesses observe best practice in granting paternity leave.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754085", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754081, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22947", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of section 158 of the Equality Act 2010 in the context of access to internship opportunities for white, working-class boys.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754081", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754080, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22946", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of section 158 of the Equality Act 2010 in the context of providing white, working-class boys with access to vocational training.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754080", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754076, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22945", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of Section 158 of the Equality Act 2010 in the context of providing white, working-class boys with access to targeted outreach programmes.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754076", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754075, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22944", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of section 159 of the Equality Act 2010 in the context of access to training opportunities for white, working-class boys.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754075", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754014, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22943", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of section 159 of the Equality Act 2010 in the context of access to recruitment opportunities for white, working-class boys.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754014", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754011, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22942", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when she next plans to review the departmental ministerial disability champions programme.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754011", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753990, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22941", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of changes in the level of National Insurance contributions on victims support services.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753990", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753977, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22940", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of changes to employers' National Insurance contributions on women-owned businesses.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753977", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754056, "askingMemberId": 4503, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22939", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average annual number is of case files rejected due to incorrectly submitted documents using (a) Case Overview and Prosecutions Application (COPA) and (b) CONNECT computer software.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754056", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754055, "askingMemberId": 4503, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22938", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average number of open custody records was in (a) 2019, (b) 2022, (c) 2023 and (d) 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754055", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754054, "askingMemberId": 4503, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22937", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average number of case file (a) rejections and (b) discontinuations by the Crown Prosecution Service was (i) before and (ii) after the introduction of the CONNECT computer software.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754054", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754053, "askingMemberId": 4503, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22936", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police forces purchased CONNECT computer software; and how many such forces (a) no longer and (b) continue to use the software.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754053", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754050, "askingMemberId": 4503, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22935", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time it takes an officer to complete a case file is on (a) CONNECT and (b) Case Overview and Prosecutions Application (COPA).", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754050", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754049, "askingMemberId": 4503, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22934", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much has been spent on the CONNECT computer software since its introduction by the Metropolitan Police on (a) further development of the software, (b) training including (i) accommodation, (ii) tr", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754049", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754048, "askingMemberId": 4503, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22933", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time spent by people in custody in police holding cells was in the two years (a) before and (b) after the introduction of the CONNECT software; and how many people have been detained ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754048", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754068, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22932", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 6 September 2024 to Question 2316 on Equality, whether the socio-economic duty will apply to local education authority decisions on (a) parents with children joining the state system ", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754068", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754067, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22931", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to his Department's tender note entitled Procurement of a Contractor to build new British Embassy, Beijing, published on 2 October 2024, what the (a) timetable", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754067", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754065, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22930", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2024 to Question 16945 on Business Rates, if she will make an estimate of business rates receipts for (a) 2024-25 and (b) 2025-26 for England only.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754065", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754064, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22929", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether any private sector companies contracted to her Department will receive increased payments for the increase in employer National Insurance contributions.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754064", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754063, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22928", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential cumulative impact of the (a) increase in National Insurance contributions, (b) changes to the level of retail, hospitality and leisure rate business relief from 2025-2", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754063", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754052, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22927", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 23 December 2024 to Question 20225 on Prisons: Construction, what the status of the planning permission is for each site; and how many additional prison places are proposed in each locat", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754052", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754051, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22926", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 23 December 2024 to Question 20225 on Prisons: Construction, if she will list the four locations affected by the nutrient neutrality rules; on what dates mitigation measures were resolve", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754051", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754047, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22925", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the policy is of (a) her Department and (b) HM Courts and Tribunal Service on granting legal aid to travellers for enforcement cases against unauthorised (i) development and (ii) encampments.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754047", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754022, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22924", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Office for National Statistics' Higher Real Household Disposable Income per head measure takes into account changes to (a) council tax bills and (b) indirect taxation.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754022", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754021, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22923", "questionText": "To ask the Right hon. Member for Kenilworth and Southam, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the Electoral Commission's timetable is for publishing details of spending by Labour Together for the 2024 general election.", "answeringBodyId": 36, "answeringBodyName": "Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754021", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754020, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22922", "questionText": "To ask the Right hon. Member for Kenilworth and Southam, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what estimate the Electoral Commission has made of the number of people on the electoral roll in (a) Northern Ireland and (b) Great ", "answeringBodyId": 36, "answeringBodyName": "Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754020", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754019, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22921", "questionText": "To ask the Right hon. Member for Kenilworth and Southam, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 8 January 2025 to Question 22035 on Candidates: Expenditure, what steps the Electoral Commission is taking", "answeringBodyId": 36, "answeringBodyName": "Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754019", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754018, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22920", "questionText": "To ask the Right hon. Member for Kenilworth and Southam, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 8 January 2025 to Question 22037 on Candidates: expenditure, whether the 20 pence per page prescribed fee ", "answeringBodyId": 36, "answeringBodyName": "Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754018", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754006, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22919", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the Renters' Rights Bill on levels of inflation in (a) the next six months and (b) the six months following the commencement of the Bill's provisions.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754006", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754005, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22918", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time is between a complaint being (a) received and (b) logged at the First Tier Tribunal (Property Chamber \u2013 Residential Property).", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754005", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754004, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22917", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to page 3 of the Renters\u2019 Rights Bill Impact Assessment, published in November 2024, what discussions she has had with insurers on the conclusion that tenants want", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754004", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754002, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22916", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to page 3 of the Renters\u2019 Rights Bill Impact Assessment, published in November 2024, what her Department's evidential basis is that tenants wanting to own a pet wi", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754002", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754001, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22915", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she has had discussions with the President of the First-tier Tribunal (Property Chamber) on the Renters Rights Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754001", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753930, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22914", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether nutrient neutrality mitigation levy measures will be subject to economic viability assessments; and what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the additional ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753930", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753929, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22913", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2024 to Question 18378 on Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Public Appointments, what assessment she made of the potent", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753929", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753928, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22912", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department has issued guidance on foreign donors from which donations including via (a) third parties and (b) corporate companies may be accepted by political parties", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753928", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753927, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22911", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of boycotts of Israeli participation in (a) sporting and (b) cultural events on levels of community cohesion in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753927", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754043, "askingMemberId": 4436, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22910", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish (a) the number and (b) a list of trust names of academy trusts in which the highest paid member of staff including employer pension contributions was paid (i) more than \u00a3200,000, (ii) more t", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754043", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754042, "askingMemberId": 4436, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22909", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish a breakdown of the total number of trustees of schools multi-academy trusts that received remuneration either as a member of staff as well as a trustee, or in their capacity purely as truste", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754042", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754041, "askingMemberId": 4436, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22908", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average pay was for headteachers in (a) primary and (b) secondary school in the maintained sector in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754041", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754040, "askingMemberId": 4436, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22907", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 January 2025 to Question 21323 on Multi-academy Trusts: Pay, if she will take steps to collate a table with the total number of academy trusts reporting (a) one, (b) two and (c) thre", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754040", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754070, "askingMemberId": 4357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22906", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department records the number of enquiries received from (a) hon. Members and (b) Members of Devolved (i) Parliaments and (ii) Assemblies on a quarterly basis.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754070", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754069, "askingMemberId": 4357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22905", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 8 January 2025 to Question 21320 on written representations to the Department of Work and Pensions, whether there have been changes to the directions to Government departments on the lo", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754069", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753971, "askingMemberId": 4118, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22904", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to support local authorities to provide activities which promote children\u2019s (a) health, (b) wellbeing and (c) learning during school holidays.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753971", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754073, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-16T00:00:00", "uin": "22903", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were (a) awarded Pension Credit and (b) paid Winter Fuel Allowance in West Worcestershire constituency in (i) 2024-25 and (ii) 2023-24.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754073", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754057, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22902", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2024 to Question 14034 on Flood Control: Gosport, when her Department plans to confirm the list of projects to receive Government flood resilience", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754057", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753976, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22901", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department provides on schools making second hand uniform available.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753976", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753975, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22900", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what comparative assessment her Department has made of trends in levels of school absence in (a) schools with 40% or more pupils in bands A-F of the Income Deprivation Affecting Children Index and (b) other (i)", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753975", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753974, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22899", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of levels of disadvantaged pupils in schools on rates of absence in schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753974", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753973, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22898", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of free breakfast provision in secondary schools on levels of school attendance.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753973", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753972, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22897", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason a school tie is not permitted as an additional item of branded uniform in primary schools in the Children\u2019s Wellbeing and Schools Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753972", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753969, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22896", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether costs for (a) before-school breakfast and (b) after-school clubs and programmes for children of (I) primary (II) secondary school age are eligible for reimbursement through universal credit as c", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753969", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753954, "askingMemberId": 3912, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22895", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will publish the sources of funding for each public sector pension scheme including balancing payments made by her Department for each fiscal year between 2020-21 and 2023-24.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753954", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754115, "askingMemberId": 1516, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22894", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of ineffective Crown Court trials which started after day one of the set trial date in 2024 reached completion.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754115", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754114, "askingMemberId": 1516, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22893", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of ineffective trials in the Crown Court started later than day one of the set trial date in 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754114", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754112, "askingMemberId": 1516, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22892", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether trials in the Crown Court starting on day two or later are classified as ineffective.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754112", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754107, "askingMemberId": 1516, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22891", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what metrics determine whether a Crown Court trial is classified as ineffective.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754107", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754100, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22890", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his planned timetable is for publishing his Department's annual statistics on armed forces equipment and formations.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754100", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1754099, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22889", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason the annual armed forces equipment and formations statistics was not published on 31 October 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1754099", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753991, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22888", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 8 January 2025 to Question 21267 on Defence: Procurement, what plans he has to review the effectiveness of the NATO test once implemented; and with what metrics.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753991", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753989, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22887", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 8 January 2025 to Question 21267 on Defence: Procurement, when he plans full implementation of the NATO test across all his Department's procurement decisions.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753989", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753957, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22886", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate she has made of the change in GDP per capita by 2030.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753957", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753956, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22885", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will have discussions with financial institutions to establish which additional banks will participate in the roll out of banking hubs.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753956", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753953, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22884", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the potential impact of the action by the Israeli Air Force on 8 September 2024 in Libya on Hezbollah's armed capability.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753953", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753948, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22883", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Army Reserve Centres are envisaged to require armed guarding in Northern Ireland after 2028.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753948", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753979, "askingMemberId": 152, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22882", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make representations to his counterpart in the United Arab Emirates to condemn the (a) detention of Ryan Cornelius in contravention of the ruling of the UN Working", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753979", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753932, "askingMemberId": 152, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22881", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the information presented in the Hong Kong Legislative Council paper CB(2)1779/24-25(01) on 7 January 2025 and the reporting in Ming Pao on 8 January 2025, ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753932", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753965, "askingMemberId": 146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22880", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2024 to Question 19633 on the Biodiversity Beyond National Jurisdiction Agreement, what recent assessment he has made of the extent to w", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753965", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753742, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22879", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to maintain historic places of worship.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753742", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753741, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22878", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that young people leave school equipped with relevant skills for working life.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753741", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753740, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22877", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to help prevent bullying in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in Essex.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753740", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753739, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22876", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted for offences related to human trafficking since January 2020.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753739", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753738, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22875", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to promote alternatives to university to young people.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753738", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753737, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22874", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made with Cabinet colleagues of the UK's vulnerability to cyber-terrorism.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753737", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753736, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22873", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passports were revoked due to links to terrorist activity in each month since January 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753736", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753735, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22872", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to (a) identify and (b) prevent child sex trafficking.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753735", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753734, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22871", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases of child sex trafficking have been identified in the UK in each of the last five years; and what steps she is taking to ensure (a) accurate and (b) transparent data collection for those", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753734", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753733, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22870", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the number of walk-in centres.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753733", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753712, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22869", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding the National Economic Crime Victim Care Unit has received in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753712", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753711, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22868", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what preventative steps she is taking to reduce the number of fraud cases.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753711", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753710, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22867", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with her international counterparts about (a) policing fraud and (b) convicting perpetrators of fraud.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753710", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753709, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22866", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to protect vulnerable people from falling victim to fraud.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753709", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753707, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22865", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of the Action Fraud reporting system.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753707", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753693, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22864", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of HMRC's policies on supporting victims of fraud.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753693", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753692, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22863", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions her Department has had with victims of fraud on their experiences with HMRC.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753692", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753686, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22862", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to lower rates of student absence in secondary schools in (a) Essex and (b) South Basildon and East Thurrock constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753686", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753685, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22861", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to improve teacher (a) recruitment and (b) retention in (i) Essex and (ii) South Basildon and East Thurrock constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753685", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753688, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22860", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Animals in Science Regulation Unit's Annual Report for 2023, published on 17 December 2024, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of (a) letters of reprimand and (b) other", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753688", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753687, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22859", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 24 of the Animals in Science Regulation Unit\u2019s annual report for 2023, published on 17 December 2024, what steps her Department is taking to improve the ability of the inspectio", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753687", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753683, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22858", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2024 to Question 14407 on Trade Agreements, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of the (a) Comprehensive and Progressive Agreement for Trans-Paci", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753683", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753689, "askingMemberId": 5343, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22857", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to open one of the new seven day Community Diagnostic Centres at St Mark's Hospital in Maidenhead.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753689", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753788, "askingMemberId": 5340, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22856", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the number of full-time undergraduate students paying international fees who are (a) British nationals and (b) non-domiciled in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753788", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753672, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22855", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what her planned timetable is for the delivery of the Loan Charge Review.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753672", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753699, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22854", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 19 December 2023 on The Next Stage in Our Long Term Plan for Housing Update, HCWS161, if she will publish (a) the review into the wider", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753699", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753784, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22853", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to improve support for people being released from prison.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753784", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753781, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22852", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to improve support for care leavers in Stoke-on-Trent South constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753781", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753780, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22851", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve outcomes for patients with a pancreatic cancer diagnosis in Stoke-on-Trent.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753780", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753778, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22850", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department plans to ban the (a) sale and (b) use of shock collars for dogs.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753778", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753777, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22849", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve provision of post-natal mental health care in Stoke-on-Trent.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753777", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753776, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22848", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of further restricting the (a) use and (b) sale of fireworks on animal welfare and wildlife.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753776", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753775, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22847", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to improve support for children with (a) autism and (b) SEND in mainstream settings in Stoke-on-Trent South.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753775", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753774, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22846", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to (a) provide support for and (b) increase capacity of drug and alcohol recovery services in Stoke-on-Trent.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753774", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753773, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22845", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce ambulance waiting times in Stoke-on-Trent South constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753773", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753772, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22844", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Pension Credit applications were (a) made and (b) awarded by the smallest geographical area for which data is available since 29 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753772", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753771, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22843", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Pension Credit claims have been awarded to (a) men and (b) women since 29 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753771", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753747, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22842", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the cancer plan will contain measures to improve (a) pathology and (b) testing within the (a) overall cancer and (b) triple negative breast cancer pathway.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753747", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753746, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22841", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department's cancer plan will include measures to improve the collection of data on triple-negative breast cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753746", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753745, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22840", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to improve patient outcomes for (a) rarer cancers, (b) sub-types of cancer and (c) triple negative breast cancer in the cancer plan.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753745", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753730, "askingMemberId": 5311, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22839", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending the time frame in which bereavement support can be claimed.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753730", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753702, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22838", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that fire services in Surrey can guarantee public safety during periods of insufficient staffing.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753702", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753723, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22837", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how much and what proportion of (a) Project Gigabit funding has been (i) spent on and (ii) allocated for and (b) additional funding announced in the press notice entitled Hundreds of th", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753723", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753713, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22836", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many properties are not connected to the national (a) gas and (b) electricity grid in Brecon, Radnor and Cwm Tawe constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753713", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753754, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22835", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) veterans and (b) serving personnel who have served as crew on (A) Sea Kings, (B) Pumas and (C) Chinooks have been diagnosed with (i) multiple myeloma, (ii) sarcoma and (iii) blood cancer in the last ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753754", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753743, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22834", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of enabling local authorities to apply to use ANPR to enforce designated pedestrian zones.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753743", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753684, "askingMemberId": 5278, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22833", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what (a) training and (b) support local authorities will receive to ensure the Children Not In School register does not inadvertently disadvantage parents of children with special educational needs.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753684", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753770, "askingMemberId": 5271, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22832", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to encourage local magazine publishing in Southampton Test constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753770", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753769, "askingMemberId": 5271, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22831", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to support the sustainability of local journalism including (a) magazines and (b) print media (i) nationally and (ii) in Southampton Test constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753769", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753782, "askingMemberId": 5257, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22830", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of changes to Orchestra Tax Relief from 1 April 2024 on the promotion of UK orchestras.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753782", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753696, "askingMemberId": 5257, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22829", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of noise regulation enforcement in residential areas.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753696", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753722, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22828", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the recommendations of the report entitled Our Future Homes: Housing that promotes wellbeing and community fo", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753722", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753721, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22827", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with (a) charitable organisations and (b) community groups on helping to (i) reduce pressure on mental health services and (ii) ensure comprehensive mental health suppor", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753721", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753720, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22826", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to measure the potential impact of the (a) amount and (b) distribution of funding for mental health services on the (i) quality and (ii) accessibility of those s", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753720", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753719, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22825", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure access to mental health services in (a) England, (b) areas with fewer mental health services and (c) rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753719", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753718, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22824", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking the reduce the time taken for people to receive urgent mental health care.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753718", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753717, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22823", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that increased funding for mental health services is (a) improving patient outcomes and (b) reducing waiting times.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753717", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753716, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22822", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent progress his Department has made on meeting the Mental Health Investment Standard; and how this is reflected in the funding allocated to mental health services in the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753716", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753793, "askingMemberId": 5247, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22821", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether she plans to have discussions with EU counterparts on the introduction of the EU Pay Transparency Directive as part of the Government's plans to consult on the draft Equality (Race and Disability) Bill", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753793", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753763, "askingMemberId": 5247, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22820", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage local authorities to include the recycling of small electrical items as part of household waste collections.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753763", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753789, "askingMemberId": 5242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-22T00:00:00", "uin": "22819", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many workers earn under the lower earnings limit in (a) England, (b) Scotland, (c) Wales and (d) Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753789", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753779, "askingMemberId": 5226, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22818", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2024 to Question 19765 on Large Goods Vehicles: Concrete, when her Department plans to publish the findings from the call to evidence on weight limits for Volumetric Concre", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753779", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753715, "askingMemberId": 5218, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22817", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will review the Minimum Income Floor for self-employed farmers on Universal Credit.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753715", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753695, "askingMemberId": 5199, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22816", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to review the adequacy of levels of access to ADHD medication; and if a Minister will meet with the hon. Member for York Outer to discuss ADHD medication shortag", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753695", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753760, "askingMemberId": 5195, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22815", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of trends in the level of persistent school absences in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in (i) Mid Cheshire constituency, (ii) Cheshire and (iii) England; and what step", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753760", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753794, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22814", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of difficulties faced by NHS patients in Somerset in receiving prescriptions of Creon.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753794", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753766, "askingMemberId": 5188, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22813", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of suspending export licences for F-35 components to Israel.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753766", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753675, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22812", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff are employed in the Policy Profession Unit; what the headcount allocation for that Unit is; what grades each civil servant who works in the Unit is; and how many of these are (a) policy professio", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753675", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753674, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22811", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether guidance has been issued to Government Departments on the difference between (a) positive action and (b) positive discrimination in recruitment processes.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753674", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753785, "askingMemberId": 5166, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22810", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to ensure that childcare providers are not able to charge for childcare costs on days where they are unable to deliver the service.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753785", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753767, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22809", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to deport people with dual citizenship who are charged with child grooming offences.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753767", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753765, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22808", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will take steps to ensure that candidates standing in combined authority elections are not also responsible for (a) setting up and (b) overseeing those authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753765", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753764, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22807", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of reliance on imported rare earth minerals for net zero technologies on national security.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753764", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753762, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22806", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of (a) mining and (b) processing rare earth minerals required for renewable technologies including (i) wind turbines and (ii) solar panels ", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753762", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753761, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22805", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of net zero policies on (a) UK manufacturing competitiveness and (b) jobs in carbon-intensive industries.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753761", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753732, "askingMemberId": 5160, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22804", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to continue the Academies Programme.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753732", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753714, "askingMemberId": 5156, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22803", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of an application for Universal Credit automatically triggering a claim for Council Tax Support.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753714", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753768, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-17T00:00:00", "uin": "22802", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she plans to return the (a) areas and (b) activities of private estate management in the private sector to local authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753768", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753744, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22801", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department is taking steps with local authorities to remove the requirement for households on freehold estates to pay estate management charges, in the context of the", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753744", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753708, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22800", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, for how many evacuations of Palestinians in Gaza with (a) pre-determination and (b) biometric excuse decisions his Department has sought permission from the Israeli authoriti", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753708", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753706, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22799", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, for how many evacuations to the UK of Palestinians in Gaza with visas that are valid for more than six months his Department has sought permission from the Israeli authoritie", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753706", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753705, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22798", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how many medical evacuations  to the UK of Palestinians in Gaza who are non-British nationals there have been since 7 October 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753705", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753704, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22797", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, for how many medical evacuations to the UK of Palestinians in Gaza who are non-British nationals his Department has sought permission from the Israeli authorities since 7 Oct", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753704", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753703, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22796", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how many evacuations from Gaza to the UK of (a) British nationals including dual Palestinian and British nationals, (b) their immediate family members, (c) UK visa holders wh", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753703", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753700, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22795", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to bring forward legislation to make all hate crime an aggravated offence.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753700", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753759, "askingMemberId": 5140, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22794", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what additional support is available for self-employed workers in receipt of Universal Credit that experience a short-term fall in their earnings.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753759", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753758, "askingMemberId": 5140, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22793", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the minimum income floor on self-employed workers that are unable to work for brief periods due to (a) health issues and (b) care responsibilities", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753758", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753694, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22792", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of AI road cameras at reducing road accidents in high risk areas.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753694", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753731, "askingMemberId": 5132, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22791", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to help leaseholders with (a) service charges and (b) managing agents in Beckenham and Penge constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753731", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753787, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22790", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of levels of flood preparedness in communities along the (a) Middle Brook, (b) Bessy Brook and (c) Douglas rivers in Bolton West constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753787", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753786, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22789", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much HM Revenue and Customs staff time and resource was dedicated to recovering funds from covid-19 (a) business relief and (b) procurement-related fraud in the latest period for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753786", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753748, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22788", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to assist the Central Bank of Bangladesh in repatriating UK-based assets diverted illegally from that country.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753748", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753701, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22787", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many Houses in Multiple Occupation have been developed without requiring planning permission in Bolton West constituency in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753701", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753698, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22786", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of planning permission requirements for Houses in Multiple Occupation.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753698", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753728, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22785", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of new US tariffs on the UK economy.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753728", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753727, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22784", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions on future US-UK defence collaboration he has had with the incoming US Defense Secretary.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753727", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753726, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22783", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of the incoming US presidency on healthcare research in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753726", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753725, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22782", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of the incoming US presidency on scientific research in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753725", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753724, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22781", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to page 25 of the Government response to the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman's investigation into Women\u2019s State Pension age and associated issues, what the evidential basis is ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753724", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753729, "askingMemberId": 5109, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22780", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve health outcomes for survivors of acquired brain injuries.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753729", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753691, "askingMemberId": 5109, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22779", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to review the list price at which motorists are required to pay additional car tax.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753691", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753690, "askingMemberId": 5109, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22778", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his Department's timetable is for the commencement of dentist contract renegotiations.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753690", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753671, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22777", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what guidance she has issued to civil servants in the Land Registry on how frequently they should attend the office each week; how many and what proportion of desks were occupied", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753671", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753757, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-23T00:00:00", "uin": "22776", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding has been allocated in total for the school rebuilding programme.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753757", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753756, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-24T00:00:00", "uin": "22775", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost to the public purse has been of the school rebuilding programme broken down by spending on (a) completed projects and (b) ongoing projects.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753756", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753755, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-23T00:00:00", "uin": "22774", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of school rebuilding projects have (a) been completed, (b) been completed within their intended time frame and (c) have passed their original deadline.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753755", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753682, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22773", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to incorporate educational resources from the National Crime Agency into the National Curriculum in order to inform children about the dangers of online child sexual exploita", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753682", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753681, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22772", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to take steps to decolonise the national curriculum.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753681", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753680, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22771", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to monitor capacity in state schools in the context of potential pupil transfers from the private to state sector following the introduction of VAT on school fees.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753680", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753679, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22770", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to educate children about (a) online safety and (b) the risk of online sexual predators as part of the National Curriculum.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753679", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753678, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22769", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department is taking steps to make renting easier for people with pets.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753678", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753677, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22768", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to ensure landlords are compliant with the need to ensure that new tenancies have an Energy Performance Rating of at least C from 1 April 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753677", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753676, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22767", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what leadership the Border Security Command provides to (a) Border Force, (b) National Crime Agency, (c) Immigration Enforcement and (d) the police.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753676", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753697, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22766", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions she has had with the Welsh Government on devolving management of the Crown Estate to Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753697", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753673, "askingMemberId": 5073, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22765", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Select Committee on Work and Pensions letter on the Pension Protection Fund and Financial Assistance Scheme payments of 17 December 2024, what progress she has made on implementing", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753673", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753792, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22764", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of increased long term gilt rates on Government borrowing costs.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753792", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753791, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22763", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were (a) arrested and (b) charged for (i) drink and (ii) drug driving in December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753791", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753790, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22762", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of the Autumn Budget 2024 on the number of police officers in Lancashire.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753790", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753783, "askingMemberId": 5069, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22761", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has made an estimate of the revenue accrued from capital gains tax on the sale of crypto-assets in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753783", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753753, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22760", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what industrial disputes are ongoing within (a) her Department and (b) each of the arm\u2019s length bodies connected to her Department; how many (i) staff and (ii) contractors are involved in each dispute; what the", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753753", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753752, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22759", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, whether she plans to decolonise the (a) artwork and (b) heritage assets in (i) the Attorney General's Office and (ii) each of its arm\u2019s length bodies.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753752", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753751, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22758", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to decolonise the (a) artwork and (b) heritage assets in (i) his Department and (ii) each of its arm\u2019s length bodies.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753751", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753750, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22757", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether she plans to decolonise the (a) artwork and (b) heritage assets in (i) her Department and (ii) each of its arm\u2019s length bodies; and what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policie", "answeringBodyId": 28, "answeringBodyName": "Wales Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753750", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753749, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22756", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he plans to decolonise the (a) artwork and (b) heritage assets in (i) her Department and (ii) each of its arm's length bodies.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753749", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753593, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22755", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether he plans to decolonise the (a) artwork and (b) heritage assets in (i) her Department and (ii) each of its arm's length bodies.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753593", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753592, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22754", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether he plans to decolonise the (a) artwork and (b) heritage assets in (i) his Department and (ii) each of its arm\u2019s length bodies.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753592", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753590, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22753", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she plans to decolonise the (a) artwork and (b) heritage assets in (i) her Department, (ii) each of its arm\u2019s length bodies and (iii) railway stations.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753590", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753588, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22752", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to decolonise the (a) artwork, (b) heritage assets in (i) his Department and (ii) each of its arm\u2019s length bodies and (iii) Armed Forces premises of the Armed Forces (A) in and (B) outside the Un", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753588", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753587, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22751", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she plans to decolonise the (a) artwork and (b) heritage assets in (i) her Department and (ii) each of its arm\u2019s length bodies.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753587", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753585, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22750", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the potential implications for her policies of the Welsh Government\u2019s guidance entitled Public commemoration in Wales: guidance, updated on 15 November 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753585", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753584, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22749", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she plans to decolonise the (a) artwork and (b) heritage assets in (i) her Department and (ii) each of its arm\u2019s length bodies; what the policy of the Government Art Collection is on deco", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753584", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753582, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22748", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to decolonise the (a) artwork and (b) heritage assets in (i) her Department and (ii) each of its arm\u2019s length bodies.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753582", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753481, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22747", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps with City of London Police to improve (a) the (i) support services and (ii) reporting tools available to victims of fraud and (b) the quality of intelligence on fraud provided t", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753481", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753480, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22746", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he plans to decolonise the (a) artwork and (b) heritage assets in (i) his Department and (ii) each of its arm's length bodies.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753480", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753479, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22745", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether she plans to decolonise the (a) artwork and (b) heritage assets in (i) her Department, (ii) the (A) courts and (B) prison estates and (iii) each of her Department's arm's length bodies.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753479", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753478, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22744", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he plans to decolonise the (a) artwork and (b) heritage assets in (i) his Department and (ii) each of its arm's length bodies.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753478", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753477, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22743", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to decolonise the (a) artwork and (b) heritage assets in (i) her Department, (ii) HMRC, (iii) the Valuation Office Agency and (iv) the other arm\u2019s length bodies in her Department.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753477", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753476, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22742", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she plans to decolonise the (a) artwork and (b) heritage assets in (i) her Department and (ii) each of its arm's length bodies.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753476", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753644, "askingMemberId": 5038, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22741", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of trends in the level of knife crime in Knowsley constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753644", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753643, "askingMemberId": 5038, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22740", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps her Department has taken to improve neighbourhood policing in Knowsley constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753643", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753642, "askingMemberId": 5038, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22739", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce health inequalities in Knowsley constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753642", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753641, "askingMemberId": 5038, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22738", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the level of health inequalities in Knowsley constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753641", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753640, "askingMemberId": 5038, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22737", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase access to educational opportunities in Knowsley constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753640", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753665, "askingMemberId": 5033, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22736", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to support the UK\u2019s National Nuclear Laboratory in expanding the development of americium so it could be used by the space industry.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753665", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753664, "askingMemberId": 5033, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22735", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the UK\u2019s National Nuclear Laboratory is able to conduct commercially beneficial research.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753664", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753492, "askingMemberId": 5033, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22734", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of issuing a Regulation 12 determination under the Justification of Practices Involving Ionising Radiation Regulations 2004 co", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753492", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753653, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22733", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to document entitled the Reforming elective care for patients, published on 6 January 2025, what estimate he has made of the size of the workforce needed to implement the (a) periope", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753653", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753652, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22732", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 12 of the document entitled Reforming elective care for patients, published on 6 January 2025, what steps he plans to take to implement shared decision-making.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753652", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753651, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22731", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the document entitled Reforming elective care for patients, published on 6 January 2025, which groups of patients will be offered the prehabilitation services outlined in that pla", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753651", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753650, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22730", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential (a) barriers and (b) costs for NHS trusts in implementing the perioperative care measures outlined in the document entitled Reforming elective care for ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753650", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753660, "askingMemberId": 4938, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22729", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to raise public awareness of cancer symptoms in teenagers and young adults to improve early detection rates.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753660", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753659, "askingMemberId": 4938, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22728", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to ensure that teenagers and young adults with cancer have consistent access to specialist psychological support; and how such plans will be implemented as part of the", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753659", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753658, "askingMemberId": 4938, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22727", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help tackle barriers to (a) teenagers and (b) young adults accessing clinical trials; and if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of this on UK ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753658", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753657, "askingMemberId": 4938, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22726", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to (a) increase the use of rapid diagnostic centres and (b) otherwise help improve early diagnosis rates for (i) teenagers and (ii) young adults with cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753657", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753656, "askingMemberId": 4938, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22725", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the unique (a) medical, (b) psychological and (c) social needs of (i) teenagers and (ii) young adults with cancer are included within the NHS Long", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753656", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753654, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22724", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether it is her policy to continue the Opening Schools Facilities funding.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753654", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753662, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22723", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 8 January 2025 to Question 21472 on Industrial Strategy Council: Public Appointments, if he will provide details of the number of people that were considered for appointment t", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753662", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753602, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22722", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) male and (b) female patients who have received a diagnosis of infertility are waiting for fertility\u00a0treatment.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753602", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753601, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22721", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) males and (b) females have an infertility diagnosis.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753601", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753487, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22720", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 3 January 2025 to Question 19776 on Affordable Housing, in what circumstances foreign nationals who are not eligible for social housing are eligible for", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753487", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753486, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22719", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential implications for her policies of the potential role of the United Front Work Department in relation to the planning", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753486", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753485, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22718", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 4.1.6 of the consultation entitled Local authority funding reform: objectives and principles, published on 18 December 2024, whether councils which ha", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753485", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753567, "askingMemberId": 4858, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22717", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what passport benefits of what average value a Pension Credit claimant may be eligible to receive.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753567", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753566, "askingMemberId": 4858, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22716", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average cost to the public purse is of (a) a Pension Credit claimant, (b) their council tax discounts and (c) other passport benefits.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753566", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753565, "askingMemberId": 4858, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22715", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she plans to publish data collected from the fit note trailblazers.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753565", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753619, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22714", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking with local authorities to help support kinship carers in (a) Liverpool and (b) other areas.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753619", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753603, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22713", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the time taken for people on mental health waiting lists to be (a) assessed and (b) treated.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753603", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753496, "askingMemberId": 4828, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22712", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of women murdered by domestic abusers in (a) England and Wales and (b) Merseyside in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753496", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753561, "askingMemberId": 4818, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22711", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to take steps with the Valuation Office Agency to introduce new valuation methods for business rates for grassroots music venues.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753561", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753559, "askingMemberId": 4818, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22710", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of permanently reducing business rates for grassroots music venues.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753559", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753495, "askingMemberId": 4818, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22709", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of increased borrowing costs on the UK's debt repayments.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753495", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753494, "askingMemberId": 4818, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22708", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of higher bond yields on mortgage repayments.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753494", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753493, "askingMemberId": 4818, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22707", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of increased borrowing costs on the UK's debt repayments.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753493", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753634, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22706", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners have been (a) released in error and (b) released in error and not re-apprehended under the Early Release scheme as of 8 January 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753634", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753629, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22705", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 8 January 2025 to Question 21699 on Gonorrhoea: Health Services, what data his Department holds on the cost of treating gonorrhoea to the NHS; and if he will publish that ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753629", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753576, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22704", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will take steps to ensure the availability of positive mental health initiatives including (a) on-site mental health resources, (b) training for employers in mental health first aid and (c) helpl", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753576", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753575, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22703", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department provides support programs including (a) appropriate training, (b) mentorship and (c) career pathways to encourage young people to enter the construction sector.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753575", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753564, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22702", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) national and (b) local inquiries have been carried out into rape grooming gangs.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753564", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753670, "askingMemberId": 4806, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22701", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will publish all submissions to the call for input on single-sex spaces that were determined to have misinterpreted the Equality Act 2010.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753670", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753617, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22700", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to improve border infrastructure for importing (a) large plants and (b) trees.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753617", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753616, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22699", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress he has made on developing an improved plant health alert system; and whether the new system will include real time updates on border holds.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753616", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753615, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22698", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to provide more data to horticulture businesses on (a) sanitary and phytosanitary border movements and (b) inspection rates generated from the Impor", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753615", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753542, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "22697", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing the new Neffy treatment for severe allergic reactions to schools when available on the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753542", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753541, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22696", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the new Neffy treatment for severe allergic reactions will be available on the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753541", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753626, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22695", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answers of 9 December 2024 to Question 17895 on South Western Railway: Nationalisation, Question 17896 on C2C: Nationalisation and Question 17897 on Abellio Greater Anglia: Nationalisation, what", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753626", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753624, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22694", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she plans to take to ensure that (a) rising mobilisation, (b) due diligence and (c) general programme delivery costs are (i) monitored and (ii) restrained during the transfer of train operator servic", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753624", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753621, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22693", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to resolve the strike action by the RMT on Avanti West Coast.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753621", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753595, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22692", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of the Midlands Engine Strategy on economic growth in the Midlands.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753595", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753594, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22691", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on the role of pan-regional partnerships in encouraging regional economic growth in (a) the Midlands and (b) across th", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753594", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753591, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22690", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to (a) support foster placements and (b) develop regional recruitment hubs in the East Midlands.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753591", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753589, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22689", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress her Department has made on the kinship allowance trial; how many kinship carers will be able to join the trial; what date she plans to launch the trial; and whether the findings of the trial be pu", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753589", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753586, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22688", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the National Audit Office report entitled Public chargepoints for electric vehicles, published on 13 December 2024, what discussions her Department has had with (a) industry leaders and (b) lo", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753586", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753583, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22687", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the National Audit Office report entitled Public chargepoints for electric vehicles, published on 13 December 2024, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of ensuring compliance ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753583", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753581, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-16T00:00:00", "uin": "22686", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has had recent discussions with NHS England on flu vaccine uptake among staff working in (a) the NHS and (b) social care settings.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753581", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753580, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-16T00:00:00", "uin": "22685", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase the level of flu vaccine uptake.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753580", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753579, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-16T00:00:00", "uin": "22684", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the level of uptake for the flu vaccine in each of the last four years for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753579", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753578, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-16T00:00:00", "uin": "22683", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the levels of the uptake of the flu vaccine.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753578", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753596, "askingMemberId": 4777, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22682", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure those diagnosed with coeliac disease receive timely and appropriate treatment.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753596", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753551, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22681", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will include podcasts in the broadcasting code.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753551", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753549, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22680", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to reduce the timeframe for the authorisation of new electric vehicle battery recycling facilities.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753549", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753548, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22679", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will update the Green Book to allow for the valuation of the reduced carbon footprint of UK produced materials as opposed to imported ones.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753548", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753547, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22678", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of recycling lithium iron phosphate batteries.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753547", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753546, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22677", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to the Government Office for Science's research entitled What are the technical and policy barriers to increasing EV battery recycling capacity in the UK?, updated on 21 Novemb", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753546", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753498, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22676", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to prevent hand carwash operators from disposing of chemicals illegally down public storm drains.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753498", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753497, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22675", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to encourage community ownership of locally valued assets at risk.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753497", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753614, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22674", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in England and Wales received discretionary housing payment after qualifying for local housing allowance in 2023-24.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753614", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753637, "askingMemberId": 4673, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22673", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what (a) statutory requirements and (b) guidance exist for (i) local authorities and (ii) schools to prevent children with special education needs becoming Children Missing Education.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753637", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753636, "askingMemberId": 4673, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22672", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to mandate local authorities to collect information on special educational needs disaggregated by primary need.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753636", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753635, "askingMemberId": 4673, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22671", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to expand the statutory definition of Children Missing Education to include children with special educational needs not receiving adequate education.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753635", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753647, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22670", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what her planned timetable is for permanent reform of business rates.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753647", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753543, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22669", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of a national screening programme for prostate cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753543", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753540, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22668", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to prioritise screening for brain tumours.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753540", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753500, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22667", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to improve the resilience of drainage systems.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753500", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753536, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22666", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether dual citizens with British or Irish nationality are required to apply for electronic travel authorisation to travel to the UK in instances where their British or Irish passport has expired.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753536", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753535, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22665", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department has issued on whether transport carriers can accept (a) an expired British passport and (b) other evidence of British citizenship as proof of exemption from the electronic", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753535", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753577, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22664", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of (a) times blood donors have been advised in advance of delays to their NHS Blood and Transplant donor session and (b) the number of donors tha", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753577", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753574, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22663", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many times people have been called more than twice per day by NHS Blood and Transplant seeking blood donations in the last 12 months; and whether he is taking steps to ensure that the frequency", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753574", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753618, "askingMemberId": 4623, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22662", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent steps he has taken to support the expansion of university provision in Derry/Londonderry under the terms of the New Decade, New Approach agreement.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753618", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753661, "askingMemberId": 4610, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22661", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure patients that rely on medicines for (a) epilepsy, (b) ADHD and (c) Parkinson's are not impacted by supply shortages.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753661", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753563, "askingMemberId": 4571, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22660", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to (a) protect natural habitats and (b) promote biodiversity net gain.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753563", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753562, "askingMemberId": 4571, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22659", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps he is taking to help increase the uptake of home solar panel installations.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753562", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753570, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22658", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2025 to Question 20687 on Employment, when she expects the Labour Market Advisory Board to finish their work.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753570", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753569, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22657", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department is collecting data about use of the Household Support Fund to support pensioners who are no longer in receipt of the winter fuel payment.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753569", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753568, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22656", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many more people she expects to be in employment as a result of proposals in the Get Britain Working White Paper.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753568", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753669, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22655", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to allow UK defence companies to participate in (a) careers fairs and (b) related events on university campuses.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753669", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753668, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22654", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has had discussions with the Chief of the Air Staff on procuring a replacement for the Hawk T2.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753668", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753667, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22653", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has received enquiries from international partners on the potential sale of (a) HMS Bulwark and (b) HMS Albion.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753667", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753666, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22652", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many hotels are (a) providing and (b) in negotiations to provide accommodation to asylum seekers in East Grinstead and Uckfield constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753666", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753483, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22651", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to appoint a men's health champion.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753483", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753534, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22650", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2024 to Question 14996, on Chinese Embassy: Planning Permission, whether Innovate UK requested that the planning application be called-in.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753534", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753533, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22649", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether free schools will be affected by changes to charitable business rate relief for schools.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753533", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753521, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22648", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to page 99 of the English Devolution White Paper, CP 1218, whether councils will be able to ban smoking in public places under the new byelaw powers.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753521", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753520, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22647", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the provisional Local Government Finance Settlement, published on 18 December 2024, if she will make it her policy to ensure that the Royal Borough of Windsor a", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753520", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753519, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22646", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, which religions and faiths her Department formally recognises; and which faith days for those religions or faiths her Department formally marks.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753519", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753517, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22645", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what her policy is on the provision of pensions funded from the public purse for (a) councillors, (b) council mayors and (c) combined authority mayors.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753517", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753515, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22644", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will take steps to publicly advertise her Department's guidance entitled Paying the right level of Council Tax: a plain English guide to Council Tax, updated 26 April 2024", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753515", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753512, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22643", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what guidance (a) her Department and (b) the Planning Inspectorate has issued on representations on planning applications subject to foreign interference.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753512", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753511, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22642", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether an (a) Equality Impact Assessment and (b) Environmental Principles assessment was undertaken on the decision to call-in the planning application for the Chinese Embassy.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753511", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753507, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22641", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2024 to Question 14996 on Chinese Embassy: Planning Permission, whether the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Aff", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753507", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753506, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22640", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Mayor of London has requested a higher council tax referendum for 2025-26.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753506", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753504, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22639", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2024 to Question 20295 on Counter-terrorism, whether the principles of the written ministerial statement of 14 March 2024 on New Extremism D", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753504", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753503, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22638", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what her Department's timetable is for the commencement of Section 111 of the Levelling Up and Regeneration Act 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753503", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753501, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22637", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 3 January 2025 to Question 16491 on Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Consultants and Special Advisers and pursuant to the Answer o", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753501", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753484, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22636", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will publish any (a) electronic and (b) written communication from Downing Street to his Department on the Chinese Embassy before the decision was made to call in the p", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753484", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753502, "askingMemberId": 4389, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22635", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether applications for the NHS and Social Care Coronavirus Life Assurance payment received after 30 September 2023 are eligible.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753502", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753550, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22634", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, if his Department will publish an annual cost analysis of each of the five milestones.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753550", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753573, "askingMemberId": 4362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22633", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the oral contribution by the Minister for Secondary Care of 18 December 2024, Official Report, column 345, when he chaired the first of the weekly winter preparedness meetings.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753573", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753649, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22632", "questionText": "To ask the Leader of the House, pursuant to her oral contribution of 12 December 2024, Official Report, column 1045, what discussions she has had with (a) the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, (b) the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities an", "answeringBodyId": 34, "answeringBodyName": "Leader of the House", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753649", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753648, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22631", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of small boat crossings of the Channel each day in December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753648", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753646, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22630", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment has he made of the potential merits of an international investigation into the recent Azerbaijan Airlines crash.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753646", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753645, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22629", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking with (a) the Secretary of State for the Home Department and (b) other Cabinet colleagues to reduce the amount of Overseas Development Assistance spent", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753645", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753639, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22628", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business and Trade on the potential impact of accession by China to the Comprehensive and Progressive Trans-Pacifi", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753639", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753638, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22627", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on a treaty with Mauritius on the British Indian Ocean Territory.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753638", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753633, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22626", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what (a) engagement and (b) consultation he (i) has had and (ii) plans to have with parliamentarians on the treaty with Mauritius on the British Indian Ocean Territory.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753633", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753632, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22625", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for the treaty on the British Indian Ocean Territory of his recent discussions with his counterpart in Mauritius.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753632", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753631, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22624", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 2 January 2025 to Question 18873 on Sudan: Humanitarian Aid, what steps he is taking to ensure the protection of civilians.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753631", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753630, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22623", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 2 January 2025 to Question 18873 on Sudan: Humanitarian Aid, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in Sierra Leone following the Russian", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753630", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753628, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22622", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 2 January 2025 to Question 18873 on Sudan: Humanitarian Aid, what potential alternative cross-border routes beyond Adr\u00e9 for humanitarian aid deliver", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753628", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753627, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22621", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 December 2024 to Question 19318 on British Nationals Abroad: Detainees, whether he has made changes to his Department's (a) processes and (b) ser", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753627", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753623, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22620", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2024 to Question 19316 on Development Aid: Reviews, when he received the Development Review.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753623", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753622, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22619", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2024 to Question 19313 on BBC World Service: Foreign Relations, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Culture, Med", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753622", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753620, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22618", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 December 2024 to Question 19307 on Syria: Humanitarian Aid, what assessment he has made of (a) the impact of the situation on civilians in Syria,", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753620", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753545, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22617", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of trends in levels of people diagnosed with dementia over the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753545", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753544, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22616", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of ambulance waiting times over the 2024-25 Christmas and new year period.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753544", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753537, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22615", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people in the UK have been diagnosed with sepsis in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753537", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753525, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22614", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency guidance on the use of medicinal cannabis.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753525", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753524, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22613", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of trends in the level of awareness amongst police constabularies of the legislation around the use of prescribed medical cannabis.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753524", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753523, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22612", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of restrictions on the use of electronic prescriptions for the issuing of medicinal cannabis products.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753523", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753482, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22611", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will take steps to make the application process for Universal Credit more accessible for people (a) who are not able to go online and (b) with learning difficulties.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753482", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753475, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22610", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of trends in the level of interest rates on people with low incomes.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753475", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753474, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22609", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of waiting times for practical driving tests on the duration of the validity of driving theory tests.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753474", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753473, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22608", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has had recent discussions with the British Medical Association on its response to the Cass review.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753473", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753472, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22607", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on funding to support small and medium-sized businesses starting up on high streets in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753472", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753471, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22606", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment with Cabinet colleagues of the potential impact of an IT shutdown initiated by hostile foreign actors on (a) the NHS and (b) other critical digital infrastructure.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753471", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753560, "askingMemberId": 4126, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22605", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has held recent discussions with humanitarian organisations on the adequacy of prosthetics supplies in Gaza; and if he will take steps to assist humanitarian organ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753560", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753558, "askingMemberId": 4126, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22604", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent diplomatic steps he has taken to encourage a ceasefire in Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753558", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753572, "askingMemberId": 4095, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22603", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients were seen at North Cambs Diagnostic Centre in each month since its opening in June 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753572", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753599, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22602", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 3.6 of the minutes of the Covid-19 Vaccine Benefit Risk Expert Working Group held on 18 November 2020, if he will publish (a) the 36 questions posed by the Medicines and", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753599", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753532, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22601", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the potential impact of closer economic ties with China on (a) the UK economy and (b) public finances.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753532", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753531, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22600", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2024 to Question 18362 on Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office: Cost Effectiveness, when he expects to be in a position to provi", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753531", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753530, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22599", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of recent trends in the prevalence of human right abuses in Hong Kong] and if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of such instances", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753530", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753529, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22598", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of recent trends in the prevalence of human right abuses in China; and if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of such instances on ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753529", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753528, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22597", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the decision by the Taliban to prohibit women and girls from undertaking midwifery and nursing c", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753528", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753527, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22596", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking with his international counterparts to promote the rights of women and girls in Afghanistan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753527", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753526, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22595", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether his Department plans to provide humanitarian (a) assistance and (b) aid to Afghanistan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753526", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753625, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22594", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies on Western Sahara of Morocco\u2019s autonomy plan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753625", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753612, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22593", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he has taken to improve retention of officers in the (a) Royal Navy, (b) Army and (c) Royal Air Force.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753612", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753611, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22592", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will increase funding to the UK Maritime Component Command based at the Naval Support Facility in Bahrain.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753611", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753610, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22591", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he has taken to ensure the continued presence of Royal Navy assets in the Middle East maritime theatre.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753610", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753609, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22590", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she has taken with relevant authorities to impove school attendance in Romford constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753609", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753608, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22589", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she has taken with relevant authorities to support armed forces veterans with (a) housing and (b) financial support in Romford constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753608", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753607, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22588", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken help improve rates of early diagnosis of lung cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753607", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753606, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22587", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking with relevant authorities to help tackle drink driving in Romford constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753606", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753605, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22586", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking with relevant authorities to help tackle dangerous driving in Romford constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753605", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753604, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22585", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking with relevant authorities to help reduce the number of fatal car crashes in outer London boroughs.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753604", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753539, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22584", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Institution of Civil Engineers' Roundtable Discussion on the Construction Playbook, published on 15 May 2024, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of aligni", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753539", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753538, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22583", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with the Institution of Civil Engineers on releasing a new edition of the Construction Playbook.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753538", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753554, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22582", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure that the work of Intertrade UK is not affected by trade barriers faced by some GB-based businesses supplying to Northern Ireland-based consumers.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753554", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753571, "askingMemberId": 1211, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22581", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make it his policy to use evidence-based, responsive vaccination programmes around the world.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753571", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753557, "askingMemberId": 429, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22580", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many school days were lost due to weather conditions in each year since 2010.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753557", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753556, "askingMemberId": 429, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22579", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average number of training days undertaken by serving army personnel was in each year since 2015 by rank.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753556", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753555, "askingMemberId": 429, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22578", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the sickness rate was for service personnel by rank in each year since 2015.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753555", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753553, "askingMemberId": 429, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22577", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many injured service personal required rehabilitation services in each armed service in each year since 2015; and how much his Department on rehabilitation of injured service personnel in each service in the ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753553", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753552, "askingMemberId": 429, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22576", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has had recent discussions with universities on allowing defence companies to attend university (a) careers fairs and (b) events.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753552", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753613, "askingMemberId": 394, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22575", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister for Policing, Fire and Crime Prevention in response to the question from the hon. Member for Sheffield South East of 29 July 2024, Official Repo", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753613", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753491, "askingMemberId": 394, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22574", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the average length of motorway (a) maintenance and (b) improvement contracts in terms of (i) duration and (ii) distance covered has changed in the last 10 years.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753491", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753490, "askingMemberId": 394, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22573", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the impact of time delays on road users is taken into account when determining the length of motorway (a) maintenance and (b) improvement contracts.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753490", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753489, "askingMemberId": 394, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22572", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many miles of the M1 motorway between Junction 34 and Junction 1 had speed restrictions as a result of roadworks as of 1 January in each year between 2015 and 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753489", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753488, "askingMemberId": 394, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22571", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she plans to introduce new regulations to clarify the legal use of (a) ebikes and (b) escooters.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753488", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753600, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22570", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to support SME manufacturers of farm equipment in cases where demand has fallen, in the context of funding provided by the Farming Investment Fund.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753600", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753598, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22569", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to align future application windows of the Farm Equipment and Technology Fund with the agricultural calendar.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753598", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753597, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22568", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to announce his decision on the future of the Farming Investment Fund.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753597", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753518, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22567", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate she has made of the annual running costs of the Jet Zero Taskforce.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753518", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753516, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22566", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the annual running costs of the Child Poverty Taskforce.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753516", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753514, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22565", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate he has made of the annual running costs of the National Energy System Operator.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753514", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753513, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22564", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate he has made of the annual running costs of Mission Control.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753513", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753510, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22563", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate he has made of the annual running costs of the Global Clean Power Alliance.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753510", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753509, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22562", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what estimate he has made of the annual running costs of the Regulatory Innovation Office.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753509", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753508, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22561", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate she has made of the annual running costs of the New Towns Taskforce.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753508", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753505, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22560", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate he has made of the annual running costs of the Solar Taskforce.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753505", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753499, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22559", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what additional funding his Department has provided to (a) communities and (b) local authorities affected by recent flooding in Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753499", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753663, "askingMemberId": 242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22558", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of applications to the Vaccine Damage Payment Scheme relating to Covid-19 vaccinations have been (a) made and (b) successful for (i) Vaccine-induced thrombocytopenia an", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753663", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753522, "askingMemberId": 242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22557", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to stop the spread of the HMPV virus from China.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753522", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753655, "askingMemberId": 152, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22556", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an estimate of the number of high-street gambling operators in possession of non-remote bingo licenses that are operating as adult gambling centres.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753655", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753465, "askingMemberId": 4612, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "902098", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking with Cabinet colleagues to improve transport links between Great Britain and Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753465", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753462, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-15T00:00:00", "uin": "902095", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking with Cabinet colleagues to improve trade links between Northern Ireland and the channel ports.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753462", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753306, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22555", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many individuals suspected of being victims of pension fraud have been investigated for tax penalties by HMRC in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pensions: Fraud", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753306", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753305, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22554", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support her Department is providing for victims of pension fraud schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pensions: Fraud", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753305", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753304, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22553", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many advisers in HMRC have been accused of (a) behaving dishonestly and (b) committing tax fraud in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Revenue and Customs: Disciplinary Proceedings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753304", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753303, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22552", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions her Department has had with HMRC on taking steps to ensure that advisers who behave dishonestly are removed from their positions.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Revenue and Customs: Disciplinary Proceedings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753303", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753302, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22551", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2025 to Question 21166 on Fraud: Compensation, what discussions her Department has had with HMRC on victims of fraud being taxed on the money taken from them.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fraud: Compensation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753302", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753301, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22550", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2024 to Question 18093 on Education: Access, what progress the Regional Improvement for Standards and Excellence teams are making on engaging with schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Education: Access", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753301", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753300, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22549", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to help reduce the number of children who need to travel long distances to a school with SEND provision.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: Transport", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753300", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753299, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22548", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure schools with SEND provision are accessible for low-income families.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: Low Incomes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753299", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753298, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22547", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions her Department has had with (a) parents and (b) teachers about home-to-school transport for children with special educational needs and disabilities.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Transport", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753298", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753290, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22546", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what percentage of British produce is being brought in (a) hospitals, (b) army bases and (c) prisons.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Public Sector", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753290", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753288, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22545", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make an estimate of the potential impact of GB Energy on the cost of energy bills paid by farmers.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753288", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753223, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22544", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will take steps to ensure that cases involving members of the House of Lords convicted of serious crimes do not adversely impact public confidence in the criminal justice system.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Peers: Convictions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753223", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753261, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22543", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the (a) effectiveness of the application of the Armed Forces Covenant in Northern Ireland and (b) adequacy of Armed Forces Covenant arrangements in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753261", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753258, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22542", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much from the public purse the UK provided to the EU for any purpose in financial years (a) 2019-20, (b) 2020-21, (c) 2021-22, (d) 2022-23 and (e) 2023-24.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753258", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753255, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22541", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether the conditions for notification to the EU that the Stormont Brake has been triggered have been met on Regulation (EU) 2024/2865 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 23 October 2024 am", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753255", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753254, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22540", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions he has had with relevant stakeholders on ensuring the continuity of full employment at the Spirit AeroSystems site in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753254", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753217, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22539", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the potential (a) merits and (b) impact on trade barriers of re-joining the EU (i) single market and (ii) customs union.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Relations with EU: Trade Barriers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753217", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753216, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22538", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the impact of the EU General Product Safety Regulation on UK small businesses exporting to the EU.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Consumer Goods: Safety", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753216", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753215, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22537", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will take steps to support small businesses with the costs of compliance with (a) EU general safety and performance requirements and (b) EU regulations.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Small Businesses: UK Trade with EU", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753215", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753316, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22536", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the conclusions within his Department's Animal Welfare (Licensing of Activities Involving Animals) (Englan", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Animal Welfare", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753316", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753243, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22535", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to (a) monitor and (b) help tackle far right extremism.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Radicalism", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753243", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753242, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22534", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to expand bus service provision in rural (a) villages and (b) other areas.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bus Services: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753242", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753241, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22533", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to help ensure that people carrying out jury duty do not experience financial hardship.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Juries: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753241", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753240, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22532", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of trainee GPs who undertake specialist training in mental health.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners: Mental Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753240", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753239, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22531", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to support local councils to tackle antisocial behaviour within council homes.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Council Housing: Anti-social Behaviour", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753239", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753238, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22530", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase recruitment of (a) healthcare and (b) dentistry professionals in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Professions: Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753238", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753237, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22529", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to (a) reduce waiting lists and (b) expand provision for pain management services in Stoke-on-Trent.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pain: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753237", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753236, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22528", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to improve mental health provision for young people in Stoke-on-Trent South constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health Services: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753236", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753235, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22527", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps he is taking with social media platforms to help tackle the spread of extremism online.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Media: Radicalism", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753235", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753234, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22526", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she has taken to help support the regeneration of town centres in Stoke-on-Trent South constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753234", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753233, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22525", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to provide support for veterans who are homeless and rough sleeping in Stoke-on-Trent South constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753233", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753232, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22524", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to help reduce the number of (a) adults and (b) children living in temporary accommodation in Stoke-on-Trent South constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753232", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753231, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22523", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his Department's press release entitled New reforms and independent commission to transform social care, published on 3 January 2025, how these reforms will improve service provis", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753231", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753230, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22522", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to increase recruitment of firefighters in Stoke-on-Trent South.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fire and Rescue Services: Stoke-on-Trent South", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753230", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753229, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22521", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to fund improved provisions for addiction support services in Stoke-on-Trent South.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Addictions: Stoke-on-Trent South", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753229", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753228, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22520", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to help reduce levels of reoffending among people released on licence.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners' Release: Reoffenders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753228", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753227, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22519", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the appropriacy of custodial sentences for pregnant women.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners: Pregnancy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753227", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753226, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22518", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to support people with a criminal record to find employment.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment: Offenders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753226", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753225, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22517", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking through the implementation of an alcohol strategy to tackle problem drinking.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Alcoholic Drinks: Misuse", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753225", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753326, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22516", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to answer Question 18061, tabled by the hon. Member for Mid Leicestershire on 4 December 2024 for answer on 9 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753326", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753259, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22515", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and which hotels are being used to house asylum seekers in Mid Leicestershire constituency; and how many asylum seekers there are in each hotel.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753259", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753260, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22514", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has had recent discussions with his Moroccan counterpart on the potential merits of a compensation scheme for UK citizens that lost their investments in the Paradi", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Paradise Golf and Beach Resort", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753260", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753327, "askingMemberId": 5323, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22513", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to ensure that planned reforms to the disability benefit system ensure security and support for seriously ill and disabled people.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Security Benefits: Chronic Illnesses and Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753327", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753324, "askingMemberId": 5323, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22512", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure the needs of children placed with kinship carers are fully assessed and supported especially in cases of (a) trauma and (b) disrupted care.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children: Protection", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753324", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753319, "askingMemberId": 5323, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22511", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that mental health services in rural communities are adequately (a) staffed and (b) supported.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health Services: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753319", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753318, "askingMemberId": 5323, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22510", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to ensure that people in rural communities have access to mental health support within a one-hour radius using public transport.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health Services: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753318", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753310, "askingMemberId": 5323, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22509", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps he is taking to help tackle digital exclusion in Forest of Dean constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Digital Technology: Forest of Dean", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753310", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753275, "askingMemberId": 5323, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22508", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to fund research into potential treatments for brain tumours to help (a) extend life expectancy and (b) alleviate suffering.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Brain: Tumours", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753275", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753267, "askingMemberId": 5320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22507", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that (a) hospitals and (b) other publicly owned healthcare settings are compliant with the UK Health Security Agency guidance entitled Reducing the spread of respi", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Respiratory Diseases: Disease Control", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753267", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753307, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22506", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of either (a) removing the margin or (b) capping the interest rate on student loans.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Students: Loans", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753307", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753323, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22505", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of losses in (a) personnel and (b) ships on the capability of the Royal Fleet Auxiliary.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Royal Fleet Auxiliary", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753323", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753320, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22504", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to (a) retain and (b) recruit personnel into the Royal Fleet Auxiliary.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Royal Fleet Auxiliary: Labour Turnover and Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753320", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753315, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22503", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has made a comparative assessment of the relationship between switching off lighting on stretches of (a) motorways and (b) major trunk roads and trends in the level of accidents on these roads.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Roads: Lighting", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753315", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753314, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22502", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many road lighting schemes on (a) motorways and (b) all-purpose trunk roads that were switched off following completion of the TA 501 appraisal process were in the final 18 months of their design life in ea", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Roads: Lighting", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753314", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753311, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22501", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many miles worth of road lighting on (a) motorways and (b) all-purpose trunk roads have been permanently switched off following completion of the TA 501 appraisal process each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Roads: Lighting", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753311", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753266, "askingMemberId": 5287, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22500", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of supporting charities that support pregnant women and newborn babies in Afghanistan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Afghanistan: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753266", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753265, "askingMemberId": 5287, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22499", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of establishing an independent inquiry into options for the future UK-EU relationship.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Relations with EU", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753265", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753263, "askingMemberId": 5287, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22498", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of making defibrillators exempt from VAT.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defibrillators: VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753263", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753262, "askingMemberId": 5286, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22497", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of UK support for a UN convention on the rights of older persons.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "United Nations: Older People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753262", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753308, "askingMemberId": 5280, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22496", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when she plans to respond to the correspondence of 17 October 2024 from the hon. Member for Aberdeenshire North and Moray East, reference number MC2024/14787.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Members: Correspondence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753308", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753264, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22494", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what diplomatic steps his Department is taking to help tackle anti-Semitism.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Antisemitism", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753264", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753253, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22493", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Australian counterpart on (a) the arson attack on the Adass Israel Synagogue in Melbourne and (b) changes in the level of antisemitic inc", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Australia: Antisemitism", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753253", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753218, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22492", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how much Mauritius has requested in (a) reparations and (b) annual subsidy in the negotiations on sovereignty of the Chagos islands.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "British Indian Ocean Territory: Sovereignty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753218", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753309, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22491", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to deliver a consultation on technical issues associated with renewable liquid heating fuel under Section 159 of the Energy Act 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Fuels: Public Consultation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753309", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753248, "askingMemberId": 5250, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22490", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding his Department plans to provide to (a) Quantock Hills, (b) Blackdown Hills and (c) other national landscapes in the 2025-26 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753248", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753273, "askingMemberId": 5238, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22489", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make an assessment of the potential implications for her policies of the Motorcycle Industry Association\u2019s publication entitled A Licence to Net Zero, published in October 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motorcycles: Licensing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753273", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753272, "askingMemberId": 5238, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22488", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions she has had with the Motorcycle Industry Association on user licensing for powered light vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motorcycles: Licensing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753272", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753271, "askingMemberId": 5238, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22487", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she plans to consult on introducing licence upgrade courses for powered light vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motorcycles: Licensing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753271", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753270, "askingMemberId": 5238, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22486", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total number of passes for the AM moped licence was in 2024; and what assessment she has made of the potential merits of conducting a review of user licensing for powered light vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motorcycles: Licensing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753270", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753257, "askingMemberId": 5238, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22485", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to tackle issues related to falsified (a) driving licences and (b) other transport-related documents created by AI.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Transport: Documents", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753257", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753276, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22484", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to section 7.2.12 of her Department's publication entitled School workforce census guide 2024: Guide for schools including academies within a Multi Academy Trust, published on 11 October 2024, ho", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753276", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753269, "askingMemberId": 5218, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22483", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate she has made of the potential impact of public ownership on rail fares on the East Coast mainline.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "East Coast Main Line: Fares", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753269", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753268, "askingMemberId": 5218, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22482", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to improve enforcement on people riding e-scooters illegally.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Scooters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753268", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753313, "askingMemberId": 5211, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22481", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to tackle health inequalities in (a) England, (b) London, and (c) West Ham and Beckton constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health: Disadvantaged", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753313", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753312, "askingMemberId": 5211, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22480", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to tackle anti-social behaviour in (a) England, (b) London, and (c) West Ham & Beckton constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Anti-social Behaviour", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753312", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753274, "askingMemberId": 5211, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22479", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of GP provision in (a) England, (b) London and (c) West Ham and Beckton constituency; and what steps he is taking to improve patient access.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753274", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753321, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22477", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how he plans to allocate the \u00a3100m of capital funding to upgrade 200 GP practices; and how GP practices will be able to apply for that funding.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753321", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753317, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22476", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December to question 19158 on GP recruitment, for what reason this information is unavailable; and if he will make it his policy to publish the data once it is availabl", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753317", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753224, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22475", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2024 to Question 18282 on Breast Cancer: Genetics, whether workforce planning for genetic councillors will prioritise areas that have regional inequities in acc", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Breast Cancer: Genetics", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753224", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753252, "askingMemberId": 5197, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22474", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the value of charity given to (a) state schools and (b) local communities by independent schools in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Charitable Donations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753252", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753325, "askingMemberId": 5196, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22473", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has (a) shared F-35 flight mission data files with the Israeli air force and (b) received such files from that air force since October 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Israel: Air Force", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753325", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753282, "askingMemberId": 5195, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22472", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment her Department has made of the number of unfilled teacher posts in (a) Mid Cheshire constituency, (b) Cheshire, (c) the North West and (d) England in each of the last five years; and what", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753282", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753246, "askingMemberId": 5188, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22471", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when her Department will confirm allocations for the \u00a3900 million Shared Prosperity Funding announced in the Autumn budget.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Shared Prosperity Fund", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753246", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753245, "askingMemberId": 5188, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22470", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate his Department has made of when the satellite sites for Great British Energy in Edinburgh will (a) be announced and (b) open.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Great British Energy: Edinburgh", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753245", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753244, "askingMemberId": 5188, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22469", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what remit the Great British Energy satellite sites in (a) Edinburgh and (b) Glasgow will have.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Great British Energy: Scotland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753244", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753251, "askingMemberId": 5177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22468", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate he has made of the cost of remedial work due to be carried out in properties in Wales as a result of work undertaken through the (a) ECO4 scheme and (b) Cavity Insulation Guaran", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753251", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753250, "askingMemberId": 5177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22467", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate he has made of the number of properties in Wales waiting for remedial work as a result of work undertaken through the (a) ECO4 scheme and (b) Cavity Insulation Guarantee Agency.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753250", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753249, "askingMemberId": 5177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22466", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the (a) oversight and (b) remedial mechanisms of the (i) ECO4 scheme and (ii) Cavity Insulation Guarantee Agency.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753249", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753297, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22465", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 12 November 2024 to Question 9057 on Treasury: Minister\u2019s Private Offices, what was spent on each item.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Treasury: Ministers' Private Offices", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753297", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753296, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22464", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of proposed changes to the non-domiciled tax regime on the number of non-domiciled people who will relocate to other European countries.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Domicil: Taxation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753296", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753295, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22463", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the answer of 11 December 2024, to Question 17676, on Ministers: Official Cars, if the Chancellor\u2019s car travel arrangements are at public expense.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministers: Official Cars", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753295", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753294, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22462", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Answer of 13 November 2024 to Question HL2210 on Government Departments: Communication, which communications campaigns have been (a) downsized and (b) ended following the review.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Communication", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753294", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753293, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22461", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Civil Service Equality, Diversity and Inclusion Expenditure Guidance, published on 14 May 2024, who is responsible for authorising external equality, diversity and inclusion expenditure in ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Service: Equality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753293", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753292, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22460", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether agreement is required from a Minister in his Department before departments employ recruitment consultants for use in public appointment campaigns.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Appointments: Employment Agencies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753292", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753291, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22459", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Honours and Appointments Secretariat last updated the guidance on involvement of Ministers in the Honours System; and if he will place a copy of the current guidance in the Library.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Honours", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753291", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753289, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22458", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 11 December 2024 to Question 18218 on Ministers: Convictions, whether the established process for appointing Ministers involves the Cabinet Office Ethics and Propriety Team asking if an", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministers: Convictions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753289", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753287, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22457", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Security and Intelligence Agencies Financial Statement 2023-24, for what reason the net cash requirement for the Security and Intelligence Agencies was \u00a3419.85 million lower than the estima", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Intelligence Services: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753287", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753286, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22456", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, who are the members of the Civil Service Board; how often does it meet; and where does it meet.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Service Board", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753286", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753285, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22455", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2024 to Question 14108 on Arm\u2019s Length Bodies, on what statutory basis Permanent Secretaries rather than Ministers approve framework agreements.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Arms Length Bodies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753285", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753284, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22454", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2024 to Question 14352 on Government Departments: X Corp and with reference to the SAFE Framework for HMG Brand Safety, how many instances have been recorded where HM Govern", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: X Corp", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753284", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753283, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22453", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to paragraph 60 of the Government response to the 17th Report of Session 2022-23 of the House of Lords Constitution Committee, Permanent Secretaries: their appointment and removal, HL 258, publish", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Permanent Secretaries: Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753283", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753281, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22452", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's press notice on start-ups published on 9 December 2024, how will the new secondment scheme differ from previous secondment schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Secondment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753281", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753280, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22451", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the new Cabinet Secretary has recused himself from any policy areas.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Public Appointments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753280", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753279, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22450", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many members of the senior civil service in his Department have been in post on an interim basis for more than 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Senior Civil Servants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753279", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753278, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22449", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 26 November 2024 to Question 14113 on the Permanent Secretary Remuneration Committee, whether decisions on Permanent Secretary remuneration are subject to ministerial (a) review and (b)", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Permanent Secretary Remuneration Committee", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753278", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753277, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22448", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department has taken to safeguard British semiconductor firms from hostile foreign involvement; and how many transactions in that sector have been referred to his Department under the National Sec", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foreign Investment in UK: National Security", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753277", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753247, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22447", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the level of net migration in the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753247", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753222, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22446", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions (a) she and (b) her Department has had with the Queen Elizabeth Memorial Committee since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport: Queen Elizabeth Memorial Committee", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753222", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753221, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22445", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many Ramsar sites have had their ecological character threatened in each of the last 14 years.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Wetlands: Conservation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753221", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753219, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22443", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to support youth democracy in (a) primary schools, (b) secondary schools, (c) alternative provision and (d) sixth forms and colleges in Newcastle-under-Lyme.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Citizenship", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753219", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753032, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22442", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the (a) effectiveness, (b) potential and (c) adequacy of relations between the UK and West Africa.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "West Africa: Foreign Relations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753032", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753031, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22441", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the (a) effectiveness, (b) potential and (c) adequacy of relations between the UK and East Africa.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "East Africa: Foreign Relations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753031", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753030, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22440", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the (a) effectiveness, (b) potential and (c) adequacy of relations between the UK and North Africa.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "North Africa: Foreign Relations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753030", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753029, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22439", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the (a) effectiveness, (b) potential and (c) adequacy of relations between the UK and sub-Saharan Southern Africa.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sub-saharan Africa: Foreign Relations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753029", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753028, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22438", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how many times Ministers in his Department have engaged with the leadership of the Caribbean Community (CARICOM) since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Caribbean Community: Foreign Relations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753028", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753027, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22437", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how many times Ministers in his Department have engaged with the leadership of the Southern African Development Community since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Southern African Development Community", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753027", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753026, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22436", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to help increase the (a) volume and( b) value of trade between the United Kingdom and Greece.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Trade: Greece", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753026", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753208, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22435", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of a system to provide appropriate redress for people who were (a) officially reprimanded, (b) prosecuted and (c) faced other punitive action for", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753208", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753207, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22434", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if the Minister will make an assessment of the potential merits of immediately releasing of all court transcripts related to the Pakistani heritage grooming gangs.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children: Prosecutions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753207", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753204, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22433", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people deported as a result of a conviction for involvement in a Pakistani heritage grooming gang benefited from her Department's Reintegration Programme.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753204", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753203, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22432", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse of her Department's Reintegration Programme was in the last ten years; and how many people of what countries of origin benefited from that Programme in that period.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Repatriation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753203", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753201, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22431", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visa applications from people with Pakistani nationality have been rejected because of their criminal record in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Pakistan", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753201", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753200, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22430", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people convicted for their involvement in Pakistani heritage grooming gangs were in receipt of (a) Universal Credit and (b) another benefit when they committed their crimes.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Security Benefits: Convictions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753200", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753199, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22429", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on how many (a) police officers, (b) officials of local authorities and (c) social workers (i) lost their jobs, (ii) faced legal proceedings and (iii) suffered ot", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753199", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753193, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22428", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of establishing a police task force to (a) identify and (b) investigate (i) local and (ii) national officials that had knowledge of and failed to", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753193", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753191, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22427", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign national offenders convicted for their involvement in the grooming gangs scandal were deported; how many deportation orders failed; and for what reason.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753191", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753190, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22426", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many of those convicted for their involvement in Pakistani heritage grooming gangs (a) are still in prison, (b) have been deported, (c) have been released back into the same community and (d) did not serve a ", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children: Convictions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753190", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753186, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22425", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of (a) restricting foreign aid, (b) restricting visas and (c) using other punitive international measures to encourage t", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pakistan: Extradition", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753186", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753184, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22424", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on whether family members (a) had knowledge of or (b) facilitated the crimes of people prosecuted for their involvement in Pakistani heritage grooming gangs.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children: Prosecutions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753184", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753174, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22423", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of establishing a confidential government process for whistleblowers to safely raise concerns over foreign rape gangs.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753174", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753154, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22422", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many men convicted for their involvement in Pakistani heritage grooming gangs have been given access to children born from their crimes against the mothers\u2019 wishes; and if she will make it her pol", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753154", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753153, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22421", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children have been born following rape committed by people convicted for their involvement in Pakistani heritage grooming gangs.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753153", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753152, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22420", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of people convicted for their involvement in Pakistani heritage grooming gangs (a) had previous convictions and (b) have reoffended.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children: Reoffenders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753152", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753151, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22419", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will publish the nationality of people convicted for their involvement in grooming gangs.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children: Convictions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753151", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753150, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22418", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate her Department has made of the number of girls that are still involved with Pakistani heritage grooming gangs.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753150", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753149, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22417", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate her Department has made of how many girls have been victims of Pakistani heritage grooming gangs.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children: Girls", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753149", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753214, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22416", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Migration Advisory Committee will conduct the next review of the Skilled Worker visa: immigration salary list.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Migrant Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753214", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753202, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22415", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what financial support her Department has given the Rugby Football Union to support the Women's Rugby World Cup in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753202", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753049, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22414", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to improve rates of persistent absence among pupils in state-funded (a) primary, (b) secondary and (c) special schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pupils: Absenteeism\r\n", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753049", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753188, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22413", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to support parents and carers that require more than 38 weeks of funded pre-school care provision per year.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Childcare", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753188", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753187, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22412", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason funding for pre-school care provision is restricted to 38 weeks per year, the same number of weeks as school term time.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Childcare: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753187", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753185, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22411", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, is she will take steps to extend funding for pre-school child care provision beyond 38 weeks a year.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Childcare: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753185", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753106, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22410", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of Pension Credit at tackling financial hardship among older people; and what steps she is taking to improve levels of (a) awareness and (b) ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pension Credit", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753106", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753197, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22409", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which prisons offer the provision of braille transcription services for prisoners with visual impairments.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners: Braille", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753197", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753157, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22408", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate her Department has made of the cost of constructing East-West Rail in 2024 prices.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "East West Rail Line: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753157", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753148, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-20T00:00:00", "uin": "22407", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which contractors have been chosen to carry out works under the school rebuilding programme; and on what criteria these contractors were chosen.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753148", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753147, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-23T00:00:00", "uin": "22406", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many temporary classrooms are currently in use in schools across England, broken down by number in use in (a) primary schools (b) secondary schools and (c) special schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753147", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753060, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22405", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students will require individual home invigilation to sit their (a) GCSEs, (b) A-Levels and (c) other exams in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Education: Assessments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753060", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753056, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22404", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people smuggling gangs have been disbanded since the establishment of the Border Security Command.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753056", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753055, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22403", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what resources her Department has allocated to law enforcement agencies to help tackle the level of Child Sexual Exploitation cases due to AI.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753055", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753175, "askingMemberId": 5083, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22402", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Q36 of the oral evidence given by the Office for Value for Money to the Treasury Select Committee on 11 December 2024, HC 521, which Departments have not (a) defined and (b) commenced their zero-ba", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Cost Effectiveness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753175", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753209, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22401", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department plans to take through the Victims, Courts and Public Protection Bill to support victims of domestic abuse.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753209", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753081, "askingMemberId": 5073, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22400", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she plans to review the (a) Ebbsfleet and (b) Ashford services of the Eurostar line.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Eurostar: Kent", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753081", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753189, "askingMemberId": 5071, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22399", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects (a) Adil Khan and (b) Qari Abdul Rauf, convicted for their part in a Rochdale grooming gang, to be deported.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children: Rochdale", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753189", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753166, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22398", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the impact of breeding for extreme conformations on the health and welfare of (a) dogs and (b) cats.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cats and Dogs: Animal Breeding", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753166", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753165, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22397", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department plans to take to regulate the use of stud dogs in dog breeding.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dogs: Animal Breeding", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753165", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753164, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22396", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the Animal Welfare Committee\u2019s December 2024 opinion on specialised dog reproductive practices.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dogs: Animal Breeding", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753164", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753156, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22395", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the terms of reference are for the Motor Insurance Taskforce.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Insurance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753156", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753171, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22394", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to (a) improve access to neurology services for people with multiple sclerosis and (b) increase funding for research into neurological conditions.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Multiple Sclerosis: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753171", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753192, "askingMemberId": 5054, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22393", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the time taken between developers signing the remediation contract and cases reaching the works contract signing stage on ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Buildings: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753192", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753155, "askingMemberId": 5054, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22392", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking to help support access for UNRWA to northern Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: UNRWA", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753155", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753039, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22391", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will meet with members of ForThe100 to discuss duty of care owed by higher education providers to their students.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Higher Education: Liability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753039", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753017, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22390", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to review the use of NHS Shared Business Services for finance services such as (a) payroll, (b) pensions, (c) procurement and (d) taxation.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS Shared Business Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753017", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753016, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22389", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she plans to take steps to reform funding arrangements for Internal Drainage Board levies.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Internal Drainage Boards: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753016", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753066, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22388", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his statement of 6 January 2025 on Health and Social Care Reform, Official Report, column 597, what his definition is of working class areas.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753066", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753063, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22387", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his statement of 6 January 2025 on Health and Social Care Reform, Official Report, columns 595 to 598, what steps he is taking to ensure equal access to healthcare in rural and ur", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753063", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753129, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22386", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make it her policy to amend the guidance entitled Illustrative text for local code of conduct, last updated on 20 September 2013, to include a free speech protection ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Codes of Practice", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753129", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753128, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22385", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will publish a breakdown of efficiency savings made by her Department in (a) 2024-25 and (b) 2025-26.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Cost Effectiveness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753128", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753127, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22384", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the change in grant is in (a) cash and (b) real terms in areas with a significant rural population between 2024-25 and 2025-26.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Grants: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753127", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753126, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22383", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2024 to Question 18514 on Social Media: National Security and Politics and Government, whether her Department has issued guidance on whether", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Media: National Security and Politics and Government", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753126", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753125, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22382", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2024 to Question 20283 on Chinese Embassy: Planning Permission, if the (a) Chinese Embassy (b) the Chinese Government and (c) its representa", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chinese Embassy: Planning Permission", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753125", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753124, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22381", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what representations she has received from (a) Westminster City Council and (b) business representatives on proposals to (i) create a Mayoral Development Corporation for and (ii)", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pedestrian Areas: Greater London", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753124", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753123, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22380", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 27 December 2024 to Question 20641 on Local Government Services: Rural Area, what the (a) cash (b) real terms and (c) proportional change in core spendi", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Services: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753123", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753122, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22379", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 16 December 2024 on the Devolution White Paper, HCWS316, what steps her Department is taking to end the use of (a) competit", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Finance: Devolution", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753122", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753121, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22378", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, whether (a) council tax and (b) other local taxes will be included in the target of higher Real Household Disposable", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disposable Income: Taxation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753121", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753120, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22377", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she plans to make changes to the council tax social care precept prior to the conclusions of the Casey Commission on social care.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Services: Council Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753120", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753119, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22376", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of changes to payments for the Homes for Ukraine scheme on (a) homelessness and (b) temporary accommodation.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homes for Ukraine Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753119", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753118, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22375", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether an (a) Impact Assessment and (b) Equality Impact Assessment was produced for changes to the Homes for Ukraine scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homes for Ukraine Scheme: Impact Assessments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753118", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753117, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22374", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many households are being supported in each local authority area by sponsors receiving thank you payments under the Homes for Ukraine scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homes for Ukraine Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753117", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753213, "askingMemberId": 4869, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22373", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether the Government plans to raise case of Alaa Abd el-Fattah at the upcoming Universal Periodic Review session for Egypt at the United Nations.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753213", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753212, "askingMemberId": 4869, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22372", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has had discussions with international allies on efforts to help secure the release of Alaa Abd el-Fattah in Egypt.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753212", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753024, "askingMemberId": 4869, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22371", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will embed youth work in A&Es.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Youth Work: Accident and Emergency Departments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753024", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753018, "askingMemberId": 4869, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22370", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of increasing the overseas development assistance budget to 0.7% of gross national income without applying a fiscal test.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753018", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753183, "askingMemberId": 4853, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22369", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has plans to extend the Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme beyond the current deadline of 31 March 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753183", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753181, "askingMemberId": 4853, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22368", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to protect Listed Places of Worship in Epping Forest.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753181", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753180, "askingMemberId": 4853, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22367", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to tackle the import of illegal vapes.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753180", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753179, "askingMemberId": 4853, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22366", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to tackle the sale of illegal vapes.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753179", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753057, "askingMemberId": 4828, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22365", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that Prison pathfinder meetings are provided with intelligence risk assessments on the release of prisoners that could pose a threat to national security.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753057", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753053, "askingMemberId": 4828, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22364", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the press notice entitled Pat McFadden vows to make the state more like a start up as he deploys reform teams across country, published on 9 December 2024, what discussions he has had with the ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753053", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753052, "askingMemberId": 4828, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22363", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has had discussions with local authorities on the provision of temporary accommodation for test-and-learn pilots.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753052", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753051, "askingMemberId": 4828, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22362", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department has set up expert boards for homelessness policy.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753051", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753196, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22361", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of (a) withdrawing the Copyright and Performances (Application to Other Countries) (Amendment) (No.2) Order 2024 (SI, 2024, No. 112", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753196", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753048, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22360", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether any internship programmes at (a) MI5, (b) M16 and (c) GCHQ were open to people from white British backgrounds.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Intelligence Services: Unpaid Work", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753048", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753047, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22359", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if the Environment Agency plans to run an internship programme which is open to people from white British backgrounds in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753047", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753046, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22358", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2025 to Question 21057 on Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs: Unpaid Work, if he will list each internship scheme operated by (a) hi", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753046", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753172, "askingMemberId": 4806, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22357", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when his Department plans to publish its response to the consultation entitled NHS Constitution: 10 year review, which closed in June 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753172", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753040, "askingMemberId": 4790, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22356", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to increase the security of tenure of houseboat dwellers.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Houseboats: Security of Tenure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753040", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753096, "askingMemberId": 4787, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22355", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether members of the National Wealth Fund Taskforce are remunerated.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "National Wealth Fund Taskforce: Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753096", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753036, "askingMemberId": 4786, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22354", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the additional \u00a3880 million allocated to the Social Care Grant.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Services: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753036", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753170, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22353", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many new teachers will be delivered in (a) South Shropshire and (b) other rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Teachers: Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753170", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753168, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22352", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will make the Responsible Car Wash Scheme\u2019s Code of Practice mandatory.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Car Washes: Codes of Practice", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753168", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753093, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22351", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she plans to review the adequacy of the Charities Act 2011.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753093", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753210, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22350", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the (a) adequacy of flood warnings and (b) potential merits of steps to ensure they are as (i) timely and (ii) accurate as possible.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Floods: Warnings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753210", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753206, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22349", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the number of additional homes in (a) Runcorn and Helsby constituency and (b) the North West at risk of flooding by 2050.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Floods: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753206", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753163, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22346", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what step he plans to take to increase access to rehabilitation health services in the (a) community and (b) acute health sectors.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rehabilitation: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753163", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753205, "askingMemberId": 4637, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22345", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Civil Aviation Authority is reviewing the ban on Pakistan International Airlines; and what assessment she has made of the potential impact of that ban on travel between the UK and Pakistan\u00a0since\u00a0202", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pakistan International Airlines", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753205", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753137, "askingMemberId": 4623, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22344", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has had discussions with the England and Wales Cricket Board on the England Cricket team's participation in the championship trophy match with Afghanistan.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753137", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753138, "askingMemberId": 4598, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22343", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of extending the boiler upgrade scheme to social housing tenants.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Rented Housing: Boiler Upgrade Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753138", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753112, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22342", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the next Pension Credit applications and awards dataset will be published.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pension Credit", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753112", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753139, "askingMemberId": 4521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22341", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much and what proportion of defence spending is allocated to Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753139", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753211, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22340", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she has made an assessment of the potential effect of the APPG on British Muslims definition of Islamophobia on (a) free speech and (b) the ability to criticise criminal ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Islamophobia", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753211", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753078, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22339", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether site specific viability assessments should be undertaken to assess whether the affordable housing requirement on development in the Green Belt is viable and developer con", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Affordable Housing: Green Belt", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753078", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753075, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22338", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government has taken to tackle (a) anti-semitism and (b) anti-Muslim hatred since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Antisemitism and Islamophobia", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753075", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753074, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22337", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2024 to Question 20555 on Elections: Kent, if she will publish the letter dated 16 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Elections: Kent", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753074", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753073, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22336", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 31 July 2024 to Question HL46 on Faith Matters, what payments have been made to (a) Faith Matters and (b) Tell MAMA since 4 July 2024; and what th", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Faith Matters and Tell MAMA: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753073", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753072, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22335", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2024 to Question 20229 on Chinese Embassy: Planning Permission, for what reason the readout does not include reference to discussions on the Chinese Embassy.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chinese Embassy: Planning Permission", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753072", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753071, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22334", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she plans to mandate local government restructuring as part of her plan for devolution.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Reorganisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753071", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753070, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22333", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the transparency data entitled Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: procurement pipeline, published on 3 December 2024, what Project Heart is.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753070", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753069, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22332", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the written statement of 28 November 2024 on Local Government Finance, HCWS265, what estimate her Department has made of what business rate receipts will be in ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates: Tax Yields", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753069", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753068, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22331", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what her policy is on business rate relief in (a) freeports, (b) investment zones and (b) legacy enterprise zones; and how that relief will apply to the new business rate multiplier on hereditaments over \u00a3500,000 ra", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates: Tax Allowances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753068", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753067, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22330", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether private landlords will be required to pay an ongoing fee to register with the (a) Private Rented Sector database and (b) private rented sector landlord ombudsman in addit", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Rented Housing: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753067", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753065, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22329", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what guidance her Department issues to local authorities about (a) planning, (b) licensing and (c) statutory nuisance aspects of noise complaints about (i) long-standing clocks a", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Noise: Pollution Control", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753065", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753064, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22328", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the average capital grant subsidy is per unit for a social rent dwelling.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Rented Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753064", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753062, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22327", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2024 to Question 16498 on Affordable Housing: Construction, if she will publish the grant given to each (a) developer and (b) consortium und", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Affordable Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753062", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753061, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22326", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2024 to Question 16198 on Queen Elizabeth II Conference Centre, if she will make it her policy to facilitate use of the QE2 Conference Centre", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Queen Elizabeth II Conference Centre", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753061", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753059, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22325", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2024 to Question 16197 on Prisoners\u2019 Release: Homelessness, what steps she is taking with the Secretary of State for Justice to monitor level", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners' Release: Homelessness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753059", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753058, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22324", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential implications for her policies of the compliance rate of public sector buildings with requirements to display energy certificates.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Buildings: Energy Performance Certificates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753058", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753054, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22323", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of permitting community owned facilities to use red diesel for the purposes of (a) heating and (b) electricity generation.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Buildings: Red Diesel", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753054", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753035, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22322", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what guidance her Department issues on whether the erection of an electricity pylon close to a dwelling is a material consideration in relation to the current valuation and counc", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Pylons", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753035", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753034, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22321", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2024 to Question 15805 on Mo Baines, for what reason Mo Baines\u2019 declaration of political activity was not published when her appointment as L", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mo Baines", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753034", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753033, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22320", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government plans to take to amend the rules on (a) donations to political parties and (b) the permissibility of donations from foreign business owners through UK-r", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Political Parties: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753033", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753146, "askingMemberId": 4436, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22319", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make representations to his Israeli counterparts on the immediate release of Palestinian healthcare workers currently being detained without charge or trial.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Palestinians: Detainees", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753146", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753136, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22318", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, if he will make it his policy to publish minutes of cross-departmental delivery board meetings to monitor the im", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Departmental Coordination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753136", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753135, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22317", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, if his Department will commission an independent review of the (a) reliability and (b) robustness of the (i) tar", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Departmental Coordination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753135", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753134, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22316", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, whether his Department plans to have an independent audit of the plan's performance metrics.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Departmental Coordination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753134", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753133, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22315", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that cross-departmental dependencies are identified and managed in", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Departmental Coordination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753133", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753132, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22314", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, what guidance his Department has issued to ensure cross-departmental alignment.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753132", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753131, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22313", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the document entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, what plans his Department has to publish guidance for Departments on using consistent (a) definitions, (b) methodologies and", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Departmental Coordination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753131", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753130, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22312", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the document entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, if his Department will take steps to publish a consolidated annual report on the Government\u2019s performance against the Plan f", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Departmental Coordination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753130", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753114, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22311", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what Key Performance Indicators have been set to evaluate the success of the test-and-learn programme during its (a) initial wave and for (b) planned expansion.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Sector", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753114", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753110, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22310", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many transactions were referred to his Department under the National Security and Investment Act 2021 have involved organisations with links to the Chinese (a) state and (b) Community Party since 5 July 2024", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753110", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753089, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22309", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure transparency in tracking the progress of the Plan for Change m", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Departmental Coordination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753089", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753088, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22308", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, what steps the Government is taking to prevent duplication of efforts across departments involved in delivering ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753088", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753087, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22307", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, whether the Government has implemented a formal reporting framework to hold individual (a) Secretaries of State ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753087", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753086, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22306", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, if his Department will publish an annual report detailing private investment leveraged by it", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Energy: Investment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753086", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753085, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22305", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, what key performance indicators his Department will use to measure energy security; and how ", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Supply", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753085", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753084, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22304", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he plans to lay an Official Statistics Order to include Great British Energy.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Great British Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753084", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753083, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22303", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, whether his Department plans to publish an updated roadmap for achieving 95% clean power by ", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753083", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753082, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22302", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, what criteria he will use to measure the success of Great British Energy; and if his Departm", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Great British Energy and Renewable Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753082", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753038, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22301", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, how she plans to measure good development for school readiness; whether she plans to use teacher-completed Earl", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pre-school Education: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753038", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753037, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22300", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 6 of the policy paper entitled Plan for Change: Milestones for mission-led government, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, how many and what proportion of the additional polic", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753037", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753162, "askingMemberId": 4368, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22299", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what her Department's target response time to Freedom of Information requests is; and when she plans to respond to Case NC39961.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753162", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753145, "askingMemberId": 4362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22298", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Environment Agency's budget for flood prevention and mitigation was in Leicestershire in the 2023-24 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753145", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753143, "askingMemberId": 4362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22297", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of trends in the number of developments on flood risks in Leicestershire.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753143", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753142, "askingMemberId": 4362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22296", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what additional (a) funding and (b) support his Department has provided to (i) communities and (ii) local authorities in Leicestershire to help tackle the impact of recent flooding.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753142", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753141, "askingMemberId": 4362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22295", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which NHS Trusts have declared a critical incident since 1 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753141", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753140, "askingMemberId": 4362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22294", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the total cost to the hospice sector of the increase in employers National Insurance contributions.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753140", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753116, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22293", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 December 2024 to Question 19309 on Syria: Women, what plans he has to support education for women and girls in Syria.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753116", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753115, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22292", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 December 2024 to Question 19309 on Syria: Women, what recent discussions he has had with (a) women's rights activists, (b) women-led organisation", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Syria: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753115", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753113, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22291", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2024 to Question 19311 on Syria: Development Aid, what discussions his Department has had at official level to support the transition pr", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Syria: Development Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753113", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753109, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22290", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2024 to Question 19310 on Syria: Religious Freedom, what recent discussions he has had with his Syrian counterparts on protecting freedo", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Syria: Religious Freedom", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753109", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753107, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22288", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications of the recent (a) Georgian parliamentary election and (b) presidential inauguration on Georgia\u2019s relationship with (", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Georgia: Politics and Government", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753107", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753105, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22287", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications of the recent (a) Georgian parliamentary election and (b) presidential inauguration on UK-Georgia relations.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Georgia: Foreign Relations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753105", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753104, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22286", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Georgian counterpart since the parliamentary election in that country.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Georgia: Elections", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753104", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753103, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22285", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of (a) the parliamentary election, (b) the inauguration of a new president and (c) other recent eve", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753103", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753102, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22284", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of providing funding for the Nutrition for Growth replenishment campaign before the pledging event in Paris in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753102", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753101, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22283", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2024 to Question 16959 on Gavi, the Vaccine Alliance: Finance, whether he plans to announce a commitment in relation to the Gavi, The Va", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753101", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753100, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22282", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he has taken with the Secretary of State for Defence to progress the AUKUS agreement since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "AUKUS", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753100", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753099, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22281", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with (a) the Secretary of State for Defence, (b) his Australian counterpart and (c) his US counterpart on the AUKUS agreement.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "AUKUS", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753099", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753098, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22280", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he plans an audit of the UK\u2019s relationship with China.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "China: Foreign Relations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753098", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753097, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22279", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking to help protect UK nationals in Europe from Dengue.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "British Nationals Abroad: Dengue Fever", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753097", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753095, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22278", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure UK humanitarian aid reaches civilians in Syria.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Syria: Humanitarian Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753095", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753094, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22277", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what the (a) terms of reference and (b) timeline is for Baroness Shafik's review of international development.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753094", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753092, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22276", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on the provision of weapons to Sudan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sudan: Weapons", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753092", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753091, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22275", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what percentage of humanitarian aid spending on Sudan was spent on refugees outside of Sudan in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sudan: Humanitarian Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753091", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753182, "askingMemberId": 4357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22274", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of lighting on trains on the levels of violence against women and girls travelling on the network.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Gender Based Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753182", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753178, "askingMemberId": 4357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22273", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department has a strategy for tackling violence against women and girls on trains after the passage of the Passenger Railway Services (Public Ownership) Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Gender Based Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753178", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753177, "askingMemberId": 4357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22272", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has made an assessment of the impact of the Passenger Railway Services (Public Ownership) Bill on safety on trains.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Safety", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753177", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753176, "askingMemberId": 4357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22271", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department will have responsibility for safety on trains following passage of the Passenger Railway Services (Public Ownership Bill).", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Safety", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753176", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753161, "askingMemberId": 4357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22270", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps her Department is taking to measure links between differences in pay and the socioeconomic background of employees.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Equal Pay: Social Class", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753161", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753023, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22268", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the safety of zoos.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Zoos: Safety", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753023", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753022, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22267", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of levels of energy prices in 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy: Prices", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753022", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753021, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22266", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport on protecting women from online harassment.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Harassment: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753021", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753020, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22265", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he is taking steps to promote the use of energy saving lightbulbs in domestic properties.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lighting: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753020", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753019, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22264", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to encourage more young people into (a) further education and (b) apprenticeships.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Apprentices and Further Education: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753019", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753015, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22263", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to increase the availability of spirometry testing in primary care.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Respiratory Diseases: Screening", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753015", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753014, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22262", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the number of spirometry tests carried out in Community Diagnostic Centres.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Respiratory Diseases: Screening", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753014", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753012, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22261", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Education on support for victims of rape and sexual assault who are under 18 and in the education system.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children: Pupils", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753012", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753045, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22260", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much the Environment Agency has spent on dredging rivers in each year since 2009.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rivers: Dredging", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753045", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753044, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22259", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his Department's policy is on the regular dredging of rivers.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rivers: Dredging", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753044", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753043, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22258", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the regular dredging of rivers on flooding.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Flood Control: Dredging", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753043", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753042, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22257", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the (a) River Rother and (b) River Hipper was last dredged.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "River Hipper and River Rother: Dredging", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753042", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753158, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22256", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2025 to Question 20932 on Diego Garcia, what his planned timetable is to publish details of the Prime Minister\u2019s meetings between July and December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753158", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753050, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22255", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he plans to replace the Advanced Nuclear Fund after March 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753050", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753041, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22254", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many new applications for Pension Credit were (a) made and (b) approved between 10 September 2024 and 21 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753041", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753025, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22253", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2024 to Question 11832 on the Living Wage, if the Impact Assessment will provide an estimate of the number of national living wage earners who will become income ta", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753025", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753013, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22252", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many general aviation reports were submitted by region in (a) 2023 and (b) 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753013", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753111, "askingMemberId": 429, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22251", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion patients who attended A&E with a respiratory condition and were admitted to a hospital ward were subsequently readmitted with a respiratory condition at a later date at", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Respiratory Diseases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753111", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753090, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22250", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will commission a review into the reasons that teachers have left that profession in the last 10 years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Teachers: Resignations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753090", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753080, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22249", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if he will bring forward legislative proposals on the use of artificial intelligence to (a) address safety concerns and (b) ensure its responsible (i) development and (ii) deployment in", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Artificial Intelligence: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753080", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753079, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22248", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans she has to provide funding for the expansion of electric vehicle chargepoints in (a) South Holland and The Deepings constituency and (b) Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Charging Points", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753079", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753077, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22247", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will set targets to reduce memory clinic waiting times in (a) South Holland and The Deepings constituency and (b) Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Memory Clinics: Lincolnshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753077", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753198, "askingMemberId": 165, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22245", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to update the technology required to read (a) diacritical characters and (b) accents marks in the biographical information of UK passport holders.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Passports: Biometrics", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753198", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753195, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22244", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, what the Government's policy is on the potential prosecution of UK nationals returning to the UK after serving as volunteer fighters in the Ukrainian armed forces if they hold (a) both Ukrainian and UK citizenship, (b) sole U", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753195", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1753194, "askingMemberId": 40, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22243", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his Oral Statement of 6 January 2026 on Health and Adult Social Care Reform, Official Report, Column 597, where new diagnostic centres in (a) Essex and (b) Suffolk will be based.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Diagnostic Centres: Essex and Suffolk", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1753194", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752912, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22242", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to expand the grounds under which a peerage can be revoked to include crimes involving (a) sexual offences and (b) abuse of power.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Peers: Convictions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752912", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752911, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22241", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has made an assessment of the adequacy of legislation for revoking peerages in cases involving serious criminal convictions.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Peers: Convictions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752911", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752910, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22240", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to reform the process for the forfeiture of peerages where a peer has been convicted of serious crimes.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Peers: Convictions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752910", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752909, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22239", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to ensure that interim Serious Crime Prevention Orders are not used to target individuals engaging in lawful political dissent.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Serious Crime Prevention Orders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752909", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752907, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22237", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions her Department has had with the BBC on the potential merits of introducing an alternative funding scheme to the licence fee.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "BBC: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752907", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752906, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22236", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of custodial sentences for child sexual offences in preventing reoffending.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children: Sentencing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752906", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752904, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22235", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what progress her Department has made on setting up the Inter-Ministerial Group on ending homelessness.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homelessness: Departmental Coordination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752904", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752903, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22234", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of requesting the Sentencing Council for England and Wales produce guidelines on the sentencing of grooming gangs.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children: Sentencing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752903", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752902, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22233", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions her Department has had with the independent Sentencing Council for England and Wales on the adequacy of sentencing guidelines for child sexual offences in (a) reflecting the severity of the crime", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children: Sentencing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752902", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752901, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22232", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent estimate she has made of when the Independent Review of Sentencing will be complete.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Independent Sentencing Review", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752901", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752940, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22231", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to redistribute sea worthy boats used in migrant crossings to youth groups such as Sea Scouts.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: Boats", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752940", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752876, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22228", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to reform the marine licensing process.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Marine Environment: Licensing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752876", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752875, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22227", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans the Young Future Hubs to be jointly run with third sector partners.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Young Futures Hubs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752875", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752874, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22226", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether Dorset will receive a Young Future Hub.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Young Futures Hubs: Dorset", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752874", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752893, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22225", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to (a) support British companies bidding for electric bus contracts and (b) ensure that (i) BYD, (ii) Yutong and (iii) other foreign companies do not have a disproportionate share of Go", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Buses: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752893", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752886, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22224", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish perpetrator ethnicity data for (a) grooming and (b) sexual violence collected by the Tackling Organised Exploitation Programme.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children: Ethnic Groups", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752886", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752892, "askingMemberId": 5319, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22221", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress he has made on the War Widow(er)s Recognition Payment scheme; how many applicants have received payments; and what the (a) branch of service and (b) regiment of such recipients is.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "War Widow(er)s Recognition Payment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752892", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752888, "askingMemberId": 5286, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22220", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 4.69 of the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, how she plans to use the additional funding for cycling and walking infrastructure in the 2025-26 financial year", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cycling and Walking: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752888", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752873, "askingMemberId": 5286, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22217", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that UK international climate finance reaches (a) children and (b) communities most vulnerable to climate change.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Development Aid: Climate Change", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752873", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752942, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22216", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his timetable is for proposed reforms to the Bathing Water Regulations 2013.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bathing Water Regulations 2013", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752942", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752944, "askingMemberId": 5240, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22213", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when her planned timetable is for allocating the next round of Access for All funding.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railway Stations: Access", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752944", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752943, "askingMemberId": 5240, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22212", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what proportion of funding from the most recent round of the Community Ownership Fund was allocated to bids from Scotland.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Ownership Fund: Scotland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752943", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752871, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22210", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many air cleaning units were provided to education facilities in (a) Birmingham Northfield constituency, (b) Birmingham, (c) the West Midlands and (d) England since 2020.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Educational Institutions: Air Conditioning", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752871", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752941, "askingMemberId": 5186, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22203", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish the terms of reference for the independent commission into adult social care to be led by Baroness Casey; and if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of inclu", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Independent Commission into Adult Social Care", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752941", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752938, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22201", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's guidance entitled Public Bodies Handbook \u2013 Part 2: The Approvals Process for the Creation of New Arm\u2019s-Length Bodies, whether his Department's public bodies team assessed Great", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Great British Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752938", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752937, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22200", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department has spent on carbon offsetting for Ministerial travel since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministers: Aviation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752937", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752936, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22199", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether (a) Downing Street and (b) his Department collates information on each (i) domestic and (ii) overseas flight undertaken by (A) the Prime Minister and (B) other Ministers.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministers: Aviation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752936", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752934, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22197", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2024 to Question 8637 on Cabinet Office: Vacancies, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of the length of the application window on the effectiveness the rec", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752934", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752933, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22196", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 11 November 2024, to Question 5280, on Senior Civil Servants: Recruitment, if he will list each of the (a) job titles and (b) associated unit of the Senior Civil Service roles that were", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Senior Civil Servants: Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752933", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752932, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22195", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government's web page entitled Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: spending over \u00a30, published on 10 October 2024, if he will p", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752932", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752931, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22194", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many Civil Service fast stream applicants self-declared a disability in each year for which figures are available.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752931", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752930, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22193", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many special advisers have affiliated to the First Division Association; and whether special advisers are a collective bargaining unit.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Advisers: FDA", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752930", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752929, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22192", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the answer of 20 November 2024 to Question 14502 on Gender: Equality, what guidance the (a) Civil Service People Group and (b) Office for Equality and Opportunities has produced on whether positive", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ethnic Groups: Equality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752929", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752928, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22191", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many of the reviews by Departments of public bodies in the financial year 2023/24 as part of the Public Bodies Review Programme (a) have been completed, (b) remain outstanding and (c) have been abandoned.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Bodies: Reviews", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752928", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752927, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22190", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he plans to include appointments to the Industrial Strategy Advisory Council in the Public Bodies Order in Council; and whether the chair appointment will be classified as a significant appoint", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Industrial Strategy Advisory Council: Public Appointments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752927", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752926, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22189", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff work in the mission delivery unit; and what its (a) function and (b) remit is.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752926", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752925, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22188", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's publication entitled Special adviser data releases: numbers and costs, November 2024, published on 28 November 2024, for what reason his Department has not published the list o", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Advisers: Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752925", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752924, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22187", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2024 to Question 16604 on 11 Downing Street: Art Works, if she will publish a corresponding list of the reference numbers of Government Art Collection works t", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Official Residences: Government Art Collection", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752924", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752923, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22186", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2024 to Question 15193 on Ministers: Code of Practice, for what reason the Prime Minister included the previously removed duty for ministers to comply with international law ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministers: Codes of Practice", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752923", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752922, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22185", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, who provided the lectern used by the Prime Minister for his press conference at Pinewood Studios on 5 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prime Minister: Furniture", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752922", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752921, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22184", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has issued guidance to Cabinet colleagues on engagement with the 48 Group.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: 48 Group", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752921", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752889, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22183", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 13 December 2024 to Question 18268 on Firearms: Licensing, when she last held discussions with (a) the police, (b) gun control groups, (c) the British Shooting Sports Council", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Firearms: Licensing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752889", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752900, "askingMemberId": 5163, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22181", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will hold discussions with the Health and Safety Executive on the potential merits of taking steps encourage employers to (a) organise regular hearing tests, (b) distribute adequate personal hear", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752900", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752899, "askingMemberId": 5163, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22180", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure (a) expertise and (b) public confidence are retained in Hyperbaric Oxygen Therapy services available on the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Oxygen: Medical Treatments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752899", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752879, "askingMemberId": 5163, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22179", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress he has made on the implementation of the Genetic Technologies (Precision Breeding) Act 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Genetic Technology (Precision Breeding) Act 2023", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752879", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752891, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22178", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the independent review of the loan charge will cover the (a) current and (b) historic roles of (i) promoters, (ii) umbrella companies and (iii) HMRC; what steps she is taking to ensure the independence of th", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tax Avoidance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752891", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752884, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22176", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department has made a recent assessment of the level of contribution of coaches to the tourism industry.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tourism: Buses", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752884", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752883, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22175", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department holds data on the number of coaches booked by schools for (a) cultural and (b) sports trips in (i) 2024 to date and (ii) the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Educational Visits", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752883", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752882, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22174", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many coaches were registered by the Traffic Commissioners for Great Britain in (a) 2024 to date and (b) each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Buses: Registration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752882", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752919, "askingMemberId": 5140, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22171", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has had recent discussions with its international counterparts on (a) coordination and (b) information sharing in the context of the circulation of highly pathog", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Avian Influenza : Disease Control", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752919", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752918, "askingMemberId": 5140, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22170", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the current research his Department is conducting on the impacts of gamebird releases includes looking at the impacts of mallard releases.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Game: Birds", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752918", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752917, "askingMemberId": 5140, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22169", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on how many (a) mallard and (b) other gamebird rear and release facilities where cases of (i) highly pathogenic avian influenza and (ii) other not", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Avian Influenza and Notifiable Diseases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752917", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752916, "askingMemberId": 5140, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22168", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on how many (a) mallards and (b) other gamebirds of which species have been destroyed at rearing and release facilities due to (i) highly pathogen", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Avian Influenza and Notifiable Diseases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752916", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752915, "askingMemberId": 5140, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22167", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) mallard and (b) other gamebird rearing and release facilities have been found to be infected with (i) highly pathogenic avian influenza and (ii) which other notifiable dis", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Avian Influenza and Notifiable Diseases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752915", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752894, "askingMemberId": 5140, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22166", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking with his international counterparts to help tackle extra-judicial imprisonment.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Detainees", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752894", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752877, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22165", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department has issued guidance to (a) local authorities and (b) bus companies on the pricing of children's fares.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Buses: Fares", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752877", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752797, "askingMemberId": 5132, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22163", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to help improve support for children with cerebral palsy in education settings.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pupils: Cerebral Palsy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752797", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752794, "askingMemberId": 5132, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22162", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the child poverty strategy will include specific measures to help tackle child poverty amongst (a) disabled and (b) other groups that are most affected.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Poverty: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752794", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752826, "askingMemberId": 5125, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22160", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of blood cancer data.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Blood Cancer: Databases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752826", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752785, "askingMemberId": 5105, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22158", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress she has made on introducing tooth brushing lessons in primary schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Dental Health", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752785", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752700, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22157", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the NHS is taking to provide better pain relief for people suffering from chronic urinary tract infections.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Urinary Tract Infections: Analgesics", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752700", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752697, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22154", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve access to mental health services for young people in London.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health Services: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752697", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752695, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22152", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reason late-night services at Worcester Park station are not being reinstated between Thursday and Sunday.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railway Stations: Greater London", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752695", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752694, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22151", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to tackle underreporting of stalking.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Stalking", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752694", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752693, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22150", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to increase public trust in the Metropolitan Police Service.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Metropolitan Police", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752693", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752692, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22149", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to provide training for (a) police officers and (b) legal professionals on implementation of new legislation on stalking.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Stalking", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752692", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752691, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22148", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans (a) national and (b) local awareness campaigns on the crime of stalking.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Stalking", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752691", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752690, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22147", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to bring forward legislative proposals to tackle stalking by putting victims first and increasing the protections available to them.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Stalking", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752690", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752781, "askingMemberId": 5102, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22146", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has had discussions with representatives of the Five Eyes on the potential implications for that community of President-elect Donald Trump\u2019s plan to appoint Tulsi Gabbard as US Director of National Int", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "USA: Intelligence Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752781", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752831, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22142", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) operational and (b) support staff Border Security Command employs as of 1 January 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Border Security Command: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752831", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752830, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22141", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff the Border Security Command will have; and at what grade.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Border Security Command: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752830", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752828, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22139", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether farm equipment was included when assessing the number of farms impacted by changes to inheritance tax.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752828", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752825, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22138", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what discussions he has had with Nissan on safeguarding jobs in Sunderland, in the context of the potential merger of Nissan, Honda and Mitsubishi.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nissan: Sunderland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752825", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752823, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22137", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to help reduce (a) motor neurone disease, b) Alzheimer's and c) chronic traumatic encephalopathy in retired professional rugby union players.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rugby: Dementia and Motor Neurone Disease", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752823", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752822, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22136", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) dependents and (b) extended family members have been requested to join Afghans residing in Service Families Accommodation.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Afghanistan: Refugees", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752822", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752821, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22135", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps he is taking to prevent the use of denudifying apps by children in the creation of pornographic deepfake images.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Intimate Image Abuse: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752821", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752818, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22134", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps the Government is taking to prevent the use of denudifying apps used to create pornographic deepfake images.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Intimate Image Abuse: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752818", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752813, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22133", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to tackle the use of artificial intelligence in the creation of images for online child sexual exploitation.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Intimate Image Abuse: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752813", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752811, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22132", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people claiming out of work benefit for sickness reasons have done so immediately following leaving full-time education.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sickness Benefits: School Leaving", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752811", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752701, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22131", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the processing time for Disclosure and Barring Service checks for people working in the health and social care sector.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Vetting: Health Services and Social Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752701", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752820, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22130", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has had discussions with Whizz Kidz on their report entitled Beyond fare Equality through Concessionary Bus Travel; and if she will mandate free travel for disabled bus pass holders.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bus Services: Concessions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752820", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752815, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22129", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what her planned timetable is for responding to the Gingerbread report entitled Fix the Child Maintenance Service, published on 25 November 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Child Maintenance Service", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752815", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752814, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22128", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance her Department issues to Disability Living Allowance claimants during the wait for their claim to be assessed; and what steps she is taking to reduce waiting times.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disability Living Allowance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752814", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752798, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22127", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to include Annatto (E160b) on the list of allergens that must be labelled under UK food labelling regulations.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752798", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752791, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22126", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve the diagnosis and recognition of Lyme Disease.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752791", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752790, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22125", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the scheduled ending of the Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme in March 2025 on local projects aimed at restoring listed plac", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752790", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752788, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "22124", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate her Department has made of the average processing times for deputyship applications by the Court of Protection.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752788", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752787, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22123", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to (a) encourage NHS trusts in Greater Manchester to participate in the Early Access Programme for Givinostat and (b) to help tackle barriers to participation.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Givinostat: Greater Manchester", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752787", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752718, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22122", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of the recall to prison programme.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners' Release", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752718", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752742, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22121", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will publish the latest modelling conducted by his Department or its agencies of (a) energy supply and demand and (b) network capacity constraints.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Supply", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752742", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752852, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22119", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department is encouraging developers to make provisions for (a) hedgehogs and (b) other wildlife.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Planning: Conservation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752852", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752733, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22117", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether the Government (a) participates in and (b) funds geoengineering activities; what information his Department holds on organisations in the UK which participate in geoengineering; and w", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Geoengineering", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752733", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752732, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22116", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a weekly cap on domiciliary care costs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Care Homes: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752732", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752677, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22111", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will amend planning regulations to facilitate converting holiday lodges into permanent primary homes.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Second Homes: Planning Permission", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752677", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752676, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22110", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will (a) review and (b) update the definition of anti-social behaviour in the (i) Antisocial Behaviour Act 2003 and (ii) Police Reform and Social Responsibility Act 2011.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Anti-social Behaviour", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752676", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752673, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22107", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that all further education colleges comply with (a) accessibility regulations on (i) access to assistive technology and (ii) the use of accessible design in learning resources", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Further Education: Assistive Technology", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752673", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752672, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22106", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of Vision Impairment education services; and what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the recommendations proposed by th", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: Visual Impairment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752672", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752671, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22105", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has received representations about the funding of small rugby union clubs.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rugby: Clubs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752671", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752717, "askingMemberId": 5034, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22103", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of making (a) Integrated Care Boards and (b) NHS trusts statutory consultees in the planning process.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752717", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752800, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22102", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate she has made of the increase in the number of veterans able to vote due to the introduction of the Veterans ID card as voter ID.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Elections: Proof of Identity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752800", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752714, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22098", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, when he plans to appoint the (a) special envoy for hostage affairs and (b) special envoy for arbitrary detention.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hostage Taking", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752714", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752713, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22097", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made a recent assessment of the potential merits of making cuckooing a crime.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Drugs: Organised Crime", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752713", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752712, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22096", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when the next round of the Community Ownership Fund will open for applications.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Ownership Fund", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752712", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752711, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22095", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps he is taking to improve mobile phone and broadband access in South Kesteven.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Broadband and Mobile Phones: South Kesteven", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752711", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752726, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22086", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what age ranges Young Futures hubs will work with.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Young Futures Hubs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752726", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752725, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22085", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether Young Futures hubs will work with local prevention partnerships; and whether those services will be co-located.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Young Futures Hubs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752725", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752859, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22084", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding his Department has allocated for the public consultation on a new NHS 10-year-plan.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Public Consultation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752859", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752817, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22082", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it is her Department\u2019s policy to notify successful applicants that they have been issued with an eVisa.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752817", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752793, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22081", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to publish a decision on which apprenticeships will be impacted by cuts to Level 7 apprenticeship funding.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Apprentices: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752793", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752792, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22080", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2024 to Question 4279 on Housing: Bricks, what steps she plans to take to increase rates of swift brick installation in new build propertie", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Bricks", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752792", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752783, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22078", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the (a) Rough Sleeping Initiative, (b) Rough Sleeping Accommodation Programme and (c) Night Shelter Transformation Fund will continue in 2025-26.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sleeping Rough", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752783", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752782, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22077", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when her Department will publish a breakdown of planned spending on homelessness (a) support and (b) prevention for 2025-26.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homelessness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752782", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752724, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22075", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many youth hubs will be established in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Young Futures Hubs: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752724", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752704, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22071", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether there will be future intakes for the development programme for CEOs of multi-academy trusts run with the National Institute of Teaching.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Multi-academy Trusts: Managers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752704", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752703, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22070", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 30 December 2024 to Question 20254 on Asylum: Housing, what difference each of the Contract Change Notices made to the contract.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752703", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752702, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22069", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 30 December 2024 to Question 20254 on Asylum: Housing, what the cost was of each of the Contract Change Notices.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752702", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752862, "askingMemberId": 4673, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22067", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the enforcement practices of the Information Commissioner's Office cohere with the regulatory duties of that Office.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Information Commissioner's Office", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752862", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752861, "askingMemberId": 4673, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22066", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how the Data (Use and Access) Bill will ensure that publishers can access data effectively when ensuring regulatory compliance.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Databases: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752861", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752865, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22065", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the availability of national grid connections in Runcorn and Helsby constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "National Grid: Runcorn and Helsby", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752865", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752805, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22064", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help reduce NHS waiting lists in Runcorn and Helsby constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Runcorn and Helsby", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752805", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752804, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22063", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects the recommendations of 2022 Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Exploitation to be implemented.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Child Sexual Abuse Independent Panel Inquiry", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752804", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752740, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22062", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the University of Central Lancashire's report entitled Minimising firefighters\u2019 exposure to toxic fire effluents, publish", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fire and Rescue Services: Health Hazards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752740", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752738, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22061", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the potential merits of regular health checks for fire fighters.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fire and Rescue Services: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752738", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752689, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22060", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the cost to the public purse was of sending letters on the GP Patient Survey in the last 12 months; how many letters were sent to recipients; and whether any patients were contacted by e-mail.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners: Surveys", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752689", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752688, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22059", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether his Department is taking steps to allow people to retain their mobile numbers when changing mobile contracts while retaining the same network provider.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mobile Phones", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752688", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752686, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22057", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much funding her Department has provided the Mobility Foundation in each of the last five years; and for what purpose.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mobility Foundation: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752686", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752668, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22056", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of the unavailability of (a) digital thermometers and blood pressure monitors and (b) other low cost equipment for clinical staff on NHS (i) st", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Medical Equipment: Shortages", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752668", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752864, "askingMemberId": 4630, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22055", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the retained margin element of the NHS drug tariff.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Drugs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752864", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752836, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22054", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2024 to Question 20241 on Electronic Government, what his planned timetable is for onboarding HMRC to One Login.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Revenue and Customs: Electronic Government", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752836", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752741, "askingMemberId": 4591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22051", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will work with the care sector to establish a (a) National Care Agency to (i) set minimum standards of care and (ii) act as a regulator and (b) Royal College of Careworkers to (A) improve rec", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Services: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752741", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752802, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22050", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he has had recent discussions with the Secretary of State for Defence on the potential national security risks of the AQUIND interconnector project.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Aquind: Electricity Interconnectors", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752802", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752801, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22049", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to protect national security in the context of the AQUIND interconnector project.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Aquind: Electricity Interconnectors", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752801", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752763, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22048", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the consultation entitled Reforms to the Energy Performance of Buildings regime, published on 4 December 2024, what assessment she has made of the potential imp", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752763", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752762, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22047", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the consultation entitled Reforms to the Energy Performance of Buildings regime, published on 4 December 2024, what estimate she has made of the potential impac", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Rented Housing: Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752762", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752761, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22046", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will publish her response to the letter from the Inter-Parliamentary Alliance on China of 4 December 2024 on the consultation process for the Chinese Embassy planning appl", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chinese Embassy: Planning Permission", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752761", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752759, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22045", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, through what mechanism small business rate relief is financed; and how local authorities are reimbursed for the cost.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Small Businesses: Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752759", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752757, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22044", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the answer of 3 December 2024 to Question 15932 on Council of the Nations and Regions, for what reason council (a) leaders and (b) mayors were not invited.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Council of the Nations and Regions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752757", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752756, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22043", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2024 to Question 15832 on Labour: Civil Servants, whether her Departments holds information on how many civil servants other than special adv", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Labour: Civil Servants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752756", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752755, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22042", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2023 to Question 15517 on Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Consultants, if she will publish the savings made on consult", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Consultants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752755", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752751, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22041", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment has been made of the cost of the Employment Rights reforms on local authorities, including the indirect cost through outsourced social care services.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Conditions of Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752751", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752750, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22040", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2024 to Question 15443 on Government departments: trade unions, which recognised trade unions in her Department have their membership subscri", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Trade Unions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752750", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752749, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22039", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2024 to Question 15929 on Local Government: Standards, what her definition is of regional government; and what the statutory basis is of regi", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752749", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752748, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22038", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2024 to Question 15203 on Council Tax: Probate, whether the 12 month period for marketing for sale and let is in addition to the 12 month pe", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Council Tax: Probate", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752748", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752669, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22033", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to her Department\u2019s press release entitled Ministers set to unleash biggest building boom in half a century, published on 5 December 2024, what metrics will be use", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752669", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752666, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22032", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will take steps to integrate the regulatory requirements for private landlords of (a) the Minimum Energy Efficiency Standards, (b) the Decent Homes Standard, (c) the Socia", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Rented Housing: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752666", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752743, "askingMemberId": 4464, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22031", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when it was decided that community interest companies should be ineligible for capital funding provided to NHS mental health trusts in the 2024-25 financial year; and whether he plans to make an as", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health Services: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752743", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752780, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22028", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to page 6 of the publication entitled Plan for Change: Milestones for mission-led government, what metrics his Department will use to track the commitment to generate at least ", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752780", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752779, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22027", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, at what grades new teachers will be recruited; and if she will publish recruitment targets by subject area.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Teachers: Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752779", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752776, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22024", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to page 33 of the policy paper entitled Plan for Change: Milestones for mission-led government, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, how she plans to measure success in building confidence in the ", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Criminal Proceedings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752776", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752774, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22022", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change: Milestones for mission-led government, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, how he plans to measure the impact of digital transformatio", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Digital Technology", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752774", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752773, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22021", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 28 of the policy paper entitled Plan for Change: Milestones for mission-led government, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, what key performance indicators he plans to use ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752773", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752771, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22019", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, if she will make it her policy to publish regular reports on progress towards t", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Infrastructure: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752771", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752770, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22018", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, if she will make it her policy to publish an annual report on progress towards ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752770", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752769, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22017", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, how her Department plans to measure progress towards the target to raise living", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Standard of Living", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752769", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752768, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22016", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, if she will make it her policy to publish an annual spending review for the milestones set out in the Plan for Chang", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752768", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752766, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22014", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the written statement entitled Plan for Change: Milestones for mission-led Government, published on 5 December 2024, HCWS285, and the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752766", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752765, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22013", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, what metrics she plans to use to measure economic stability beyond gross domestic product.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Economic Situation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752765", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752764, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22012", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the policy paper entitled Plan for Change, published on 5 December 2024, CP1210, what metrics she plans to use to measure progress towards the target to deliver the highest sustained growth in the ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Economic Growth", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752764", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752803, "askingMemberId": 4368, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "22011", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will undertake a review of the (a) funding model and (b) role of community pharmacies.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752803", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752858, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22010", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what proportion of UK humanitarian aid to Sudan is spent in-country.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sudan: Humanitarian Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752858", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752857, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "22009", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to identify potential additional routes for humanitarian aid delivery into Sudan since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sudan: Humanitarian Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752857", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752856, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22008", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking with (a) international and (b) NGO partners to remove blocks on humanitarian aid entering Sudan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sudan: Humanitarian Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752856", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752854, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22006", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies on Syria of the fall of the Bashar al-Assad government.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Syria: Politics and Government", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752854", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752853, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22005", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking with international partners to prosecute the former President of Syria Bashar al-Assad.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bashar al-Assad", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752853", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752851, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22004", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2024 to Question 19310 on Syria: Religious Freedom, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the treatment of", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Syria: Religious Freedom", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752851", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752849, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22002", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 17 December 2024 to Question 19695 on Foreign Relations: Elections, what recent discussions has he had with his counterpart in Georgia; and if he wi", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Georgia: Elections", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752849", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752848, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22001", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2024 to Question 19314 on Belarus: Sanctions, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of sanction avo", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Belarus: Sanctions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752848", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752847, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "22000", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2024 to Question 19314 on Belarus: Sanctions, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of sanction avo", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Belarus: Sanctions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752847", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752846, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21999", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2024 to Question 19314 on Belarus: Sanctions, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of sanction avo", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Belarus: Sanctions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752846", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752844, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21997", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 December 2024 to Question 19304 on Syria: Armed Conflict, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the (a) availability in and (b) access o", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Syria: Armed Conflict", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752844", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752843, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21996", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 December 2024 to Question 19304 on Syria: Armed Conflict, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of those discussions in ensuring a p", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Syria: Armed Conflict", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752843", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752841, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21995", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking with international partners to facilitate mediation between parties to reduce conflict in the Middle East.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Middle East: Armed Conflict", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752841", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752840, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21994", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has had recent discussions on (a) effective deconfliction and (b) the humanitarian situation in Gaza with his Israeli counterpart.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: Israel", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752840", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752667, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21992", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister for Development of 28 November 2024 on UK Leadership on Sudan, Official Report, column 945, what discussions he has ha", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: Conflict Resolution", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752667", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752728, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21991", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential implications for his policies of China's treatment of Falun Gong practitioners.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "China: Falun Gong", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752728", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752727, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21990", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Syrian counterpart on the protection of Christians in that country.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Syria: Christianity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752727", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752685, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21989", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of people referred for alcohol addiction support.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Alcoholism: Rehabilitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752685", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752684, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21988", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of income for farmers in 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Farmers: Income", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752684", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752681, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21985", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to help tackle disability discrimination in workplaces.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disability: Discrimination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752681", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752680, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21984", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what discussions he has had with his Northern Irish counterpart on the new solar farm installed at Hydebank Prison.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hydebank Wood Prison: Solar Power", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752680", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752679, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21983", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of community energy projects on local employment.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Energy: Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752679", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752678, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21982", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the cost of electricity on people with health conditions requiring medical devices which use electricity.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Medical Equipment: Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752678", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752723, "askingMemberId": 4126, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "21981", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to introduce specialist rape courts at every Crown Court.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752723", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752812, "askingMemberId": 1524, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21979", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if her Department will take steps to encourage insurance companies to insure buildings with a PAS 9980 assessment of (a) low and (b) medium tolerable that do not require remediat", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Buildings: Insurance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752812", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752816, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21978", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of alleged reports that Russia has used chemical weapons in Ukraine .", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Russia: Chemical Weapons", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752816", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752807, "askingMemberId": 429, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-09T00:00:00", "uin": "21977", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of classifying clinical engineers as healthcare professionals under the Health and Care Worker Visa.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Professions: Engineering", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752807", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752753, "askingMemberId": 373, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "21975", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department has issued to police forces on the use of surveillance powers to carry out surveillance on journalists and lawyers.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752753", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752752, "askingMemberId": 373, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "21974", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what data her Department holds on the number of times UK police forces have authorised targeted surveillance of journalists and lawyers.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752752", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752838, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21973", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much was paid in bonuses to staff in his Department in 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752838", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752796, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21972", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the English Devolution White Paper on the delivery of public services in Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Sector: Lincolnshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752796", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752795, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21971", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of people convicted for shoplifting offences reoffended within (a) 12 months and (b) two years in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Shoplifting: Reoffenders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752795", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752739, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21970", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will introduce an exemption from changes to employer National Insurance contributions for (a) small and (b) local charities.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Charities: Employers' Contributions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752739", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752737, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21969", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps she has taken to ensure school uniform is affordable.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Uniforms", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752737", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752736, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21968", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when Ministers in her Department held meetings on grooming gangs in the last five years; and who the external attendees at those meetings were.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752736", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752734, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21967", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people arriving on small boats died in the English channel in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: English Channel", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752734", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752722, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21966", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what her Department's definition of gender identity is.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gender", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752722", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752720, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21965", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate she has made of the funding gap for district councils in Lincolnshire in the next two years.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Finance: Lincolnshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752720", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752719, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21964", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve the availability of GP appointments in South Holland and the Deepings constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners: South Holland and the Deepings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752719", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752552, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21961", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has made an assessment of the potential impact of changes to business property relief on (a) plant hire companies and (b) the ability of those companies to help meet housebuilding targets.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Construction: Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752552", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752551, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21960", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to support the Data Communications Company in the (a) development and (b) testing of the Virtual Wide Area Network; and whether he plans to make funding av", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Smart Data Communications Company: Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752551", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752557, "askingMemberId": 5357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21959", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on the asylum applications of Palestinian refugees who were formerly residents of Syria and left under the Assad regime.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Palestinians", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752557", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752555, "askingMemberId": 5357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21958", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's policy is on Syrian immigrants who have been granted leave to remain status.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration: Syria", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752555", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752561, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21956", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he has made an assessment of the potential risk of investment by Macquarie in (a) Lime Down Solar Park and (b) other Nationally Significant Infrastructure Developments.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Macquarie Infrastructure Group", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752561", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752559, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21953", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of repurposing vacant (a) shops, (b) offices and (c) houses; and whether this would reduce local new-build housing targets.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Empty Property", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752559", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752491, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21951", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of legislating to increase the minimum percentage of affordable housing requirement when hew housing developments are (", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Affordable Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752491", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752459, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21946", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a protected minimum floor for Universal Credit.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Universal Credit", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752459", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752457, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21945", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps her Department is taking to help reduce the number of families dependent on food banks.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food Banks", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752457", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752434, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21943", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer,\u00a0what recent assessment she has made of the potential impact of rises in fuel duty on rural communities.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fuels: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752434", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752433, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21942", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential impact of (a) maintaining and (b) reducing levels of fuel duty on (i) households, (ii) small businesses and (iii) the haulage sector.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fuels: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752433", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752432, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21941", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of providing additional (a) funding and (b) support for (i) local authorities and (ii) harbourmasters to (A) safely dispose of and (B) reclaim abandoned ve", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Boats: Waste Disposal", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752432", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752431, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21940", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a detailed national registration system for leisure vessels.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Shipping: Registration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752431", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752430, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21939", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps her Department has taken to (a) reduce the number of abandoned leisure boats and (b) mitigate environmental damage from those boats.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Boats: Environment Protection", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752430", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752429, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21938", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will commission an independent review of alternative renewable energy technologies.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752429", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752428, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21937", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what discussions his Department has had with oil and gas companies on renewables policy.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752428", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752422, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21936", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of attaching emergency batteries for mobile phones to telephone masts in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Telecommunications: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752422", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752421, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21935", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that rural communities remain connected following the digital switchover.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Voice Over Internet Protocol: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752421", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752357, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21932", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2024 to Question 17477 on RFA Argus: Amphibious Vehicles, whether his Department has identified reductions in amphibious capability from the use of RFA Argus in place of HMS A", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "RFA Argus: Amphibious Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752357", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752356, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21931", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2024 to Question 17476 on Amphibious Vehicles, whether his Department has identified reductions in amphibious capability from the use of Bay Class Landing Ship Docks in place ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Amphibious Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752356", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752463, "askingMemberId": 5340, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21930", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2024 to Question 19590 on Newspaper Press: Foreign Investment in UK, whether the response to the consultation is contingent on free trade negotiations.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Newspaper Press: Foreign Investment in UK", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752463", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752462, "askingMemberId": 5340, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21929", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December to Question 19589 on Newspaper Press: Foreign Investment in UK, whether her Department has (a) considered and (b) taken legal advice on issuing Foreign State", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Newspaper Press: Foreign Investment in UK", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752462", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752461, "askingMemberId": 5340, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21928", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December to Question 19589 on Newspaper Press: Foreign Investment in UK, what level of indirect investment by foreign states will trigger the issuing of a Foreign Sta", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Newspaper Press: Foreign Investment in UK", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752461", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752353, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21925", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of funding for (a) legal aid and (b) criminal courts.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Courts and Legal Aid Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752353", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752476, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21921", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to her Department's guidance entitled Pension freedoms and DWP benefits, published on 27 March 2015, what assessment she has made of the impact of that policy on defined contribution pens", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752476", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752474, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21919", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of defined contribution pensions were accessed after a Pension Wise guidance appointment in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pensions: Advisory Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752474", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752502, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "21917", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made a recent assessment of the potential merits of including grief education in the relationships and sex education curriculum.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752502", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752550, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21915", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how she measures the success of literacy programs; and if she will set benchmarks to track progress of those programs.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisons: Literacy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752550", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752549, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21914", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will allocate funding to support research on effective literacy interventions for prisoners.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisons: Literacy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752549", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752548, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21913", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will take steps to help tackle the (a) stigma and (b) barriers preventing prisoners from participating in literacy programs.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners: Literacy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752548", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752547, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21912", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether her Department is taking steps to form partnerships with (a) external organisations and (b) volunteers to support literacy initiatives in prisons.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisons: Literacy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752547", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752546, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21911", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to (a) assess (i) feedback from and (ii) outcomes of and (b) improve literacy programmes for prisoners.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisons: Literacy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752546", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752545, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21910", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether her Department is taking steps to tailor literacy programmes for prisoners (a) with learning disabilities and (b) for whom English is a second language.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisons: Literacy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752545", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752544, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21909", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she plans to take to support the use of (a) technology and (b) digital resources to enhance literacy education in prisons.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisons: Literacy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752544", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752543, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21908", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether she plans to take steps to integrate prisoner literacy programs with other (a) educational and (b) vocational training opportunities.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisons: Education and Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752543", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752542, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21907", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she plans to take to tackle the shortage of qualified (a) teachers and (b) staff to provide literacy education in prisons.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisons: Literacy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752542", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752541, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21906", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she plans to take to ensure that all prisoners have access to high-quality literacy programs.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners: Literacy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752541", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752540, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21905", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking assess the effectiveness of loneliness reduction initiatives; and whether she plans to take steps to amend her policies in the context of the findings of these", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Loneliness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752540", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752539, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21904", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department plans to provide funding for research on effective interventions to tackle loneliness across different demographics.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Loneliness: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752539", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752537, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21902", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if he will take steps to ensure that digital inclusion initiatives are accessible to (a) all, (b) the elderly and (c) people in remote areas.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Digital Technology: Older People and Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752537", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752536, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21901", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will take steps to encourage employers to create workplace environments that reduce employee loneliness.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment: Loneliness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752536", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752535, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21900", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department is taking steps to integrate loneliness prevention programmes into the healthcare system.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Loneliness: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752535", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752534, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21899", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to help (a) reduce the stigma associated with and (b) encourage more people to seek help for loneliness.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Loneliness: Social Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752534", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752533, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21898", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will take steps to promote community-based initiatives that foster social connections among vulnerable populations.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Development", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752533", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752359, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21896", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of increasing penalties for water companies that discharge sewage into (a) watercourses and (b) coastal waters.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sewage: Waste Disposal", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752359", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752364, "askingMemberId": 5309, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21894", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the impact of the introduction of IR35 on tax receipts.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Off-payroll Working: Tax Yields", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752364", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752360, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21893", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether any funding previously allocated to the Dental Recovery Plan has been withdrawn.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752360", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752473, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21892", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for his policies of the recommendations of the Independent Review of Children\u2019s social care final report (MacAlister,2022), published on the 23rd of Ma", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children's Social Care Independent Review", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752473", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752528, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21891", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to provide (a) training and (b) other support to special educational needs coordinators in schools in Surrey.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: Surrey", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752528", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752481, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21890", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the English Devolution White Paper on the delivery of public services in Surrey.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Devolution: Surrey", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752481", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752480, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21889", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that local councils can (a) recruit and (b) retain educational psychologists in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Educational Psychology: Surrey Heath", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752480", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752479, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21888", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to help support students with special educational needs who have left independent schools in Surrey Heath constituency following the application of VAT to private school fees.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Education: Special Educational Needs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752479", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752396, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21886", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, with reference to the Government Digital Service's report entitled Accessibility monitoring of public sector websites and mobile apps from 2022 to 2024, published on 17 December 2024, w", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Digital Technology: Internet", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752396", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752466, "askingMemberId": 5275, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21885", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how often Royal Navy vessels have been tasked to shadow Russian navy ships near the UK in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Russia: Shipping", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752466", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752454, "askingMemberId": 5275, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21883", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what forces are committed to defending the High North.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Arctic: Defence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752454", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752453, "askingMemberId": 5275, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21882", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he last had discussions with his NATO counterparts on protecting the High North.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Arctic: Defence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752453", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752447, "askingMemberId": 5275, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21876", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking to help tackle the threat from the Russian shadow fleet.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Russia: Shipping", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752447", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752446, "askingMemberId": 5275, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21875", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he last had discussions with his Finnish counterpart on Russian shadow fleet aggression in the Baltic Sea.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Russia: Shipping", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752446", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752417, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21872", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of airside transit electronic travel authorisation on the UK's international competitiveness.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electronic Travel Authorisations: Trade Competitiveness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752417", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752529, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21868", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 December 2024 to Question 20098 on Environment Agency: Motor Vehicles, what colour wheel lug nuts are standard for vehicles purchased by the Environment Ag", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Environment Agency: Motor Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752529", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752494, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21867", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 December 2024 to Question 20097 on Environment Agency: Motor Vehicles, whether livery expenditures are classified as (a) essential and (b) non-essential mo", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Environment Agency: Motor Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752494", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752493, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21866", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 December 2024 to Question 20098 on Environment Agency: Motor Vehicles, whether wheel lug nuts on Environment Agency vehicles are (a) painted and (b) otherw", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Environment Agency: Motor Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752493", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752492, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21865", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 December 2024 to Question 20097, on road Environment Agency: Motor Vehicles, how much the Environment Agency has spent on vehicle livery broken down by (a)", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Environment Agency: Motor Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752492", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752531, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21863", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of extending the provision of air cleaning units to education facilities.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Educational Institutions: Air Conditioning", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752531", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752530, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21862", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress her Department has made on the guidance for schools on mitigating poor air quality.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Air Pollution", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752530", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752426, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21857", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 98 of the Education and Skills Funding Agency's publication entitled Annual report and accounts for the year ended 31 March 2024, published on 29 July 2024, if she will break down the tab", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Academies and Further Education: Fraud and Maladministration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752426", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752458, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21855", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking to support (a) small and (b) large family owned businesses.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business: Government Assistance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752458", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752351, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21854", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to publish the research her Department commissioned from London Economics on large scale commercial prize draws.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prize Money: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752351", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752376, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21834", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the accessibility of the consultation on Non-Jury Trials Justice and Security (Northern Ireland) Act 2007, published on 9 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Justice and Security (Northern Ireland) Act 2007", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752376", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752485, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21832", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the ability of the NHS to adopt precision medicines with companion diagnostics at pace.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Drugs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752485", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752484, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21831", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment she has made of the number of cancer medicines used in the NHS compared to other European countries.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Drugs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752484", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752425, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21828", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, which groups his Department will consult for its biennial monitoring reports on the (a) UK-Australia and (b) UK-New Zealand free trade agreements.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trade Agreements: Australasia", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752425", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752424, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21827", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, which parts of the (a) UK-Australia and (b) UK-New Zealand trade agreements will be monitored as part of the biennial monitoring reports on those treaties.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trade Agreements: Australasia", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752424", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752368, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21826", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if he will make an assessment of the impact of the delay in implementing the final provisions of the Product Security and Telecommunications Infrastructure Act 2022 on (a) mobile connec", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Product Security and Telecommunications Infrastructure Act 2022", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752368", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752367, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21825", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, for what reason the remaining provisions of the Product Security and Telecommunications Infrastructure Act 2022 have not been implemented; and what steps he is taking to implement these", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Product Security and Telecommunications Infrastructure Act 2022", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752367", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752366, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21824", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, when he plans to implement sections (a) 61 to 65, (b) 67 and (c) 70 to 74 of the Product Security and Telecommunications Infrastructure Act 2022.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Product Security and Telecommunications Infrastructure Act 2022", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752366", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752420, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21822", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she plans to take with probate services to find a solution for cases where there is a chain of representation but the name of the applicant will not match that on the Grant of Probate.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Probate", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752420", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752419, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21821", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of providing a similar Orchestra Tax Relief to vocal concerts.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Choirs: Tax Allowances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752419", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752363, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21820", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what sanction regime will be used for young people under the Youth Guarantee; how that regime will differ from the conditionality regime; and what assessment she has made of the potential impact of that", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Young People: Education and Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752363", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752442, "askingMemberId": 5188, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21816", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the banning of windows overlooking places used by women in Afghanistan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Afghanistan: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752442", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752441, "askingMemberId": 5188, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21815", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what funding from ending the VAT exemption on private schools she plans to provide to the Scottish Government.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Education: VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752441", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752414, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21813", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to increase access to rail links in rural communities.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752414", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752413, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21812", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of passenger rail performance.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752413", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752412, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "21811", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to make rail fares more affordable.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752412", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752409, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21808", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what recent assessment he has made of the impact of artificial intelligence on intellectual property rights.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Artificial Intelligence: Intellectual Property", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752409", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752408, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21807", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps he is taking with Cabinet colleagues to help SMEs adopt digital technology.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Digital Technology: Small Businesses", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752408", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752406, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21805", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether he has had recent discussions with the Secretary of State for the Home Department on the potential impact of visa restrictions on the research sector.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Research: Migrant Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752406", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752405, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21804", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps his Department is taking to regulate Artificial Intelligence.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Artificial Intelligence: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752405", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752404, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "21803", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to increase access to assessments for Special Educational Needs.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752404", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752402, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-13T00:00:00", "uin": "21801", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to increase access to GP appointments.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752402", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752525, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21797", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how many times Ministers in his Department have met with the leadership of the African Union since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "African Union", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752525", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752524, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-14T00:00:00", "uin": "21796", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the adequacy of the Disabled Facilities Grant.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752524", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752519, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21791", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to help increase the (a) volume and (b) value of trade between the UK and Malawi.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Trade: Malawi", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752519", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752518, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21790", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to help increase the (a) volume and (b) value of trade between the UK and Tanzania.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Trade: Tanzania", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752518", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752517, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21789", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to help increase the (a) volume and (b) value of trade between the UK and Indonesia.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Trade: Indonesia", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752517", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752516, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21788", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to help increase the (a) volume and (b) value of trade between the UK and Japan.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Trade: Japan", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752516", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752515, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21787", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to help increase the (a) volume and (b) value of trade between the UK and Norway.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Trade: Norway", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752515", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752512, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21784", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to help increase the (a) volume and (b) value of trade between the UK and Zimbabwe.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Trade: Zimbabwe", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752512", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752511, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21783", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to help increase the (a) volume and (b) value of trade between the UK and Botswana.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Trade: Botswana", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752511", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752510, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21782", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to help increase the (a) volume and (b) value of trade between the UK and Namibia.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Trade: Namibia", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752510", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752508, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21780", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of the Disabled Facilities Grant.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disabled Facilities Grants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752508", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752504, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21776", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many people have received funding from the Disabled Facilities Grant in (a) Newcastle-under-Lyme constituency and (b) Staffordshire in each of the last 14 years.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disabled Facilities Grants: Staffordshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752504", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752487, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21775", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to tackle organised immigration crime.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "People Smuggling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752487", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752486, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21774", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of Serious Crime Prevention Orders.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Serious Crime Prevention Orders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752486", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752471, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21772", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, when he plans to appoint country-specific trade envoys.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trade Promotion", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752471", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752468, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21769", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps the Government has taken to help secure the release of the remaining hostages in Gaza since 19 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: Hostage Taking", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752468", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752467, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21768", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps the Government has taken to help stop the loss of life in Gaza since 19 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: Armed Conflict", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752467", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752465, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21767", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions he has had with the (a) Southern African Development Community and (b) African Union on the political situation in Mozambique.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mozambique: Politics and Government", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752465", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752440, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21765", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the (a) performance and (b) adequacy of the services provided by Avanti West Coast to residents in Newcastle-under-Lyme since her appointment.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Avanti West Coast: Newcastle-under-Lyme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752440", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752439, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21764", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions she has had with the management of Avanti West Coast since her appointment.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Avanti West Coast", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752439", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752438, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21763", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions he has had with the Chemical Industries Association about the (a) access to and (b) regulation of safe and approved chemicals in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chemicals: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752438", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752437, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21762", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of chemical regulation in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chemicals: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752437", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752418, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21761", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she plans to take to increase the opportunities for young people at (a) school, (b) college and (c) university in (i) Newcastle-under-Lyme and (ii) Staffordshire to visit museums, theatres and art ga", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Young People: Arts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752418", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752501, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21760", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will (a) issue an apology for failures to tackle rape gangs and (b) make an assessment of the potential merits of a compensation scheme for the victims of such gangs.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752501", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752500, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21759", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the immigration status of people prosecuted for membership of a rape gang.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752500", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752499, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21758", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to prevent the (a) grooming, (b) rape, (c) exploitation and (d) abuse of young girls.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752499", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752498, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21757", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will commission an investigation into officials who had knowledge of rape gangs and failed to act.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752498", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752497, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21756", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of removing UK citizenship from dual nationals prosecuted for membership of a rape gang.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752497", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752496, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21755", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will deport (a) foreign nationals prosecuted for membership of a rape gang, (b) UK dual nationals prosecuted for membership of a rape gang scandal and (c) foreign national family members of tho", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752496", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752427, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21753", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will take steps to ensure that local authorities hold a legally binding bond to ensure new housing developments are completed if the developer declares bankruptcy.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752427", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752423, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21752", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans she has to ensure that charges for freehold homeowners for the upkeep of shared (a) areas and (b) facilities are equitable.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Freehold: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752423", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752234, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21751", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to prevent new housing developments being left (a) uncompleted and (b) unadopted by the local authority following developer bankruptcy.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752234", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752230, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21750", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to support applications for apprenticeships for students on Homes for Ukraine visas that expire before the course concludes.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Students: Ukraine", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752230", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752207, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21749", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference page 36 of the publication entitled Plan for Change: Milestones for mission-led government, published on 5 December 2024, what level of qualification will be considered higher-level.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Qualifications", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752207", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752179, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21748", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to improve national oversight of local commissioning of (a) specialist led-by and (b) domestic abuse services.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Domestic Abuse: Victim Support Schemes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752179", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752184, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21745", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people convicted of causing a death have been granted parole before the halfway point in their original sentences in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parole: Homicide", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752184", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752245, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21741", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers reported abuse by offenders in (a) 2022, (b) 2023, and (c) 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisons: Crimes of Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752245", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752244, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21740", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders perpetrated further crimes in prison in (a) 2022, (b) 2023, and (c) 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Reoffenders: Prisons", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752244", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752243, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21739", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of domestic abusers perpetrated further crimes in prison in (a) 2022, (b) 2023, and (c) 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Domestic Abuse: Reoffenders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752243", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752242, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21738", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of violent offenders reoffend within (a) one year, (b) three years, (c) five years and (d) ten years of conviction.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Reoffenders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752242", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752241, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21737", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what (a) programmes and (b) interventions are used to reduce reoffending among domestic abusers in the community; and what the reoffending rates are among people who participate.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Domestic Abuse: Rehabilitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752241", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752240, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21736", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what (a) programmes and (b) interventions are used to reduce reoffending among domestic abusers in prison; and what the reoffending rates are among prisoners who participate.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Domestic Abuse: Rehabilitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752240", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752239, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21735", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of domestic abusers perpetrate domestic abuse against their original victims within (a) one year, (b) three years, (c) five years and (d) ten years of conviction.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Domestic Abuse: Reoffenders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752239", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752238, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21734", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of domestic abusers reoffend within (a) one year, (b) three years, (c) five years and (d) ten years of conviction.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Domestic Abuse: Reoffenders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752238", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752237, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21733", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many domestic abusers are serving prison sentences in England and Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners: Domestic Abuse", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752237", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752185, "askingMemberId": 5076, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21731", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will have discussions with the BBC on maintaining a sustainable production department in Scotland.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "BBC: Scotland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752185", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752324, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21729", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people are waiting for their pension credit application to be processed in each region.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pension Credit", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752324", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752250, "askingMemberId": 5054, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21725", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with (a) his Ukrainian counterpart, (b) MOAS, (c) other humanitarian charities and (d) other stakeholders on the value of frontline medical evacuation services provided by humanitarian", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ukraine: Humanitarian Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752250", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752155, "askingMemberId": 5052, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21724", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to increase (a) the number of specialist teams to deal with vehicle crime and (b) the funding available to track stolen cars across borders.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Crime", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752155", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752177, "askingMemberId": 5042, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21722", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether (a) his Department and (b) the Cabinet Office is required to sign off procurement of services over \u00a320m by the East Suffolk and North Essex NHS Foundation Trust.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "East Suffolk and North Essex NHS Foundation Trust: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752177", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752302, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21721", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to change the voting system to Supplementary Vote for mayoral elections.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mayors: Elections", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752302", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752301, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21720", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart about Dr Hussam Abu Safiya.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hussam Abu Safiya", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752301", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752229, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21714", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what her planned timetable is for the implementation of the National Youth strategy; what steps she is taking to involve youth sector organisations in the development of that strategy; and how he", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Youth Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752229", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752165, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21713", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether hubs that provide open access mental health services for children and young people in every community will be delivered only through the Young Futures programme.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health Services: Children and Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752165", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752193, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21712", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of allowing a Physician Associate to Junior Doctor conversion course.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Junior Doctors: Physician Associates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752193", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752215, "askingMemberId": 4869, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21711", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to protect teenagers from violence and abuse in relationships.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Domestic Abuse: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752215", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752214, "askingMemberId": 4869, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21710", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the findings of the 2024 report by the Youth Endowment Fund entitled Children, violence and vulnerability.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752214", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752211, "askingMemberId": 4869, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21707", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the (a) impact of the proposed pay rise for teachers on school budgets and (b) potential merits of providing additional funding to cover such a pay rise.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Teachers: Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752211", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752180, "askingMemberId": 4869, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21704", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential impact of supporting the expansion of (a) local authority supply pools and (b) not-for-profit supply provision on (i) supply teachers and (ii) schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Supply Teachers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752180", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752216, "askingMemberId": 4860, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21703", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2024 to Question 19427 on the Police National Computer, what proportion of PNC records relate to dead people.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police National Computer", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752216", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752176, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21697", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many people with citizenship of other countries can vote in UK elections; of which countries such people hold citizenship; which elections they are eligible to vote in; and w", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Voting Rights: Foreign Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752176", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752172, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21693", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to the Answer of 3 December 2024 to Question HL2771 on Civil Servants: Recruitment and pursuant to the Answer of 20 November 2024 to Question 14502 on Gender: Equality, if she will issue guidanc", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Unpaid Work: Discrimination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752172", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752171, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21692", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of efficiency savings she plans to require of Government departments in each year of the Spending Review Phase 2 in order to meet her planned 5% savings over this Parliament; and what assessment she ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752171", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752170, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21691", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff in his Department have undertaken two consecutive jobs without external competition since 3 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752170", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752169, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21690", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Answer of 2 May 2023 to Question 182119 on Cabinet Office: Training, if he will take steps to encourage other public sector employers to phase out unconscious bias training.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752169", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752168, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21689", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he plans to discuss the jurisdiction of the European Court of Justice in negotiations on changes to the EU-UK relationship.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "European Court of Justice", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752168", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752167, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21688", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2024 to Question 16341 on Political Parties: Discrimination, if she will issue guidance on the distinction between philosophical and political belief.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Political Parties: Discrimination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752167", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752348, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21682", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she plans to support new FM licences for radio stations in (a) Rutland, (b) Mid-Wales and (c) other rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Radio: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752348", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752318, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21678", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will (a) collect and (b) publish the ethnicity of (i) abusers and (ii) victims of grooming gangs.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752318", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752191, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21676", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what the total amount of Government investment into retinal detachment occlusion research was in 2023-24; and which public bodies provided that investment.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ophthalmology: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752191", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752190, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21675", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how much Government funding into central retinal vein occlusion research there was in 2023-24; and which public bodies provided that funding.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ophthalmology: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752190", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752189, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21674", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how much Government funding into blepharitis research there was in 2023-24; and which public bodies provided that funding.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Blepharitis: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752189", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752188, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21673", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how much Government funding into keratoconus research there was in 2023-24; and which public bodies provided that funding.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Keratoconus: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752188", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752187, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21672", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how much Government funding into cataract research there was in 2023-24; and which public bodies provided that funding.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cataracts: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752187", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752186, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21671", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how much Government funding into uveitis research there was in 2023-24; and which public bodies provided that funding.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Uveitis: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752186", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752210, "askingMemberId": 4783, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21670", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will take steps to identify all people impacted by the collapse of McClure solicitors.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "McClure Solicitors: Insolvency", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752210", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752284, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21664", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the value of penalties issued in illegal working civil penalties was in each quarter for which data is available; and how many and what proportion of the penalties issued in each quarter have bee", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Workers: Fines", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752284", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752283, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21663", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of schools that will be impacted by the extension of statutory pay and conditions arrangements to Academy teachers in the Children\u2019s Wellbeing and Schools Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Teachers: Academies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752283", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752275, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21661", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of public sector workers of working age who have become economically inactive in each of the last 10 years.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Sector: Unemployment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752275", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752345, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21657", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department has taken to implement the Buckland Review of Autism Employment.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Autism Employment Review", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752345", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752341, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21653", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for her policies of the 40 safety measures that Ofcom has set out for social media platforms to tackle misogyny.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hate Crime: Social Media", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752341", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752340, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21652", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking with Cabinet colleagues to increase the number of white working-class boys taking up apprenticeships.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Apprentices: Boys", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752340", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752339, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21651", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking with Cabinet colleagues to increase the number of white working-class boys attending university.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Universities: Boys", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752339", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752311, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21650", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when her Department plans to respond to the consultation entitled Limitation law in child sexual abuse cases, which closed on 10 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children: Civil Proceedings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752311", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752310, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21649", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure young girls who are unaccompanied children seeking asylum are (a) able to access education and (b) supported to stay in school.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Asylum", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752310", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752309, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21648", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to improve the central data collection on access to education for unaccompanied children seeking asylum.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Asylum", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752309", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752308, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21647", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of Unaccompanied Children Seeking Asylum who were not in school in each of the last five years, broken down by gender.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Asylum", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752308", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752305, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21644", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to help councils reduce the (a) need for and (b) costs of temporary accommodation.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Temporary Accommodation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752305", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752304, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21643", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate she has made of the cost of temporary accommodation for London councils in each of the last four years.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Temporary Accommodation: Greater London", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752304", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752278, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21635", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the financial impact of potential changes to Small Business Rate Relief after the introduction of new non-domestic rate multipliers on small businesses; and whether she pla", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Small Businesses: Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752278", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752277, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21634", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps her Department is taking to support small high street businesses reliant on Small Business Rate Relief.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Small Businesses: Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752277", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752276, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21633", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether properties with a rateable value of \u00a315,000 or less will be able to continue to claim Small Business Rate Relief for the 2026-27 year.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Small Businesses: Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752276", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752268, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21631", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of biodiversity net gain on the sale of land previously used for agriculture.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Land Use", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752268", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752267, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21630", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of biodiversity net gain on the cost of housebuilding.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752267", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752266, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21629", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2024 to Question 15441 on Local Government: Staff, how the Local Government Workforce Development Group members will be selected; and whethe", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752266", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752265, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21628", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2024 to Question 15439 on Local government finance, if she will list each of the bidding schemes that have operated in her Department in 202", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752265", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752264, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21627", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the increase in employers' National Insurance contributions on (a) construction and (b) housebuilding.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Construction: Employers' Contributions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752264", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752263, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21626", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2024 to Question 15451 on Renters\u2019 Rights Bill, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that Impact Assessments (a) receive clearance ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renters' Rights Bill", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752263", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752262, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21625", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many households were on social housing waiting lists in (a) England and (b) London in each year since 2009-10.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Rented Housing: Waiting Lists", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752262", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752261, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21624", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what her planned timetable is for the implementation of the proposals in the English Devolution White Paper, published on 16 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Devolution", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752261", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752260, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21623", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the English Devolution White Paper, published on 16 December 2024, what financial resources will be made available by her Department to support mayoral combined", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Development Plans", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752260", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752259, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21622", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the English Devolution White Paper, published on the 16 December 2024, what discussions she had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer before setting the populati", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752259", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752258, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21621", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to her Department\u2019s English Devolution White Paper, published on 16 December 2024, what the evidential basis is for the decision to set new unitary council sizes a", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Unitary Councils", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752258", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752257, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21620", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to her Department's publication entitled English Devolution White Paper, published on 16 December 2024, if she will make it her policy to ensure elections to princ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Elections", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752257", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752164, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21619", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2024 to Question 16200 on Local Government: Productivity, for what reason her Department does not routinely publish letters issued to local a", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Correspondence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752164", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752161, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21618", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the (a) full time equivalent and (b) headcount number of staff assigned to work in each of her Department\u2019s offices is.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752161", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752160, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21617", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answers of 3 December 2024 to Question (a) 15923 and (b) 15934 on Mayors: Elections, for what reason Greater Lincolnshire is not listed as having a mayoral electi", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mayors: Lincolnshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752160", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752159, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21616", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 6 December 2024 to Question 16892 on Regional Planning and Development: Finance, what her Department's policy is on the (a) continuation of the Thames E", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Regional Planning and Development: Thames Estuary", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752159", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752158, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21615", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the average grant subsidy per unit is to build an average affordable dwelling under the (a) social rent, (b) affordable rent and (c) affordable home ownership tenures for th", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Affordable Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752158", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752157, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21614", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, on what dates the public hearings will be held for the Planning Inspectorate's inquiry into the Chinese Embassy planning application; and which planning inspector will be chairin", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chinese Embassy: Planning Permission", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752157", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752156, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21613", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 3.35 of Autumn Budget 2024, HC 295, how much and what proportion of the \u00a346 million in funding allocated to her Department will be spent on (a) recrui", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Planning Authorities", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752156", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752152, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21612", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she plans to introduce replacement legislation for the Vagrancy Act 1824.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Vagrancy Act 1824", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752152", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752151, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21611", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of (a) increases to (i) capital gains tax and (ii) stamp duty, (b) fixed term tenancies and evictions in the Renters\u2019 Rights ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Rented Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752151", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752199, "askingMemberId": 4396, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21609", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the Skilled Worker Visa sponsorship salary threshold requirements introduced in April 2024 on retention of civil service staff initially employe", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Migrant Workers: Civil Servants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752199", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752312, "askingMemberId": 4267, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21608", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of amending the definition of animals in the Animal Welfare Act 2006 to include (a) decapod crustaceans and (b) cephalopod mollusc", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cephalopods and Shellfish: Animal Welfare", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752312", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752196, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21606", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that people who emigrate to (a) Canada and (b) Australia are aware that their state pensions will be frozen.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "State Retirement Pensions: British Nationals Abroad", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752196", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752206, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21605", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the answer of 17 December 2024 to Question 19694 on Department for Work and Pensions: Artificial Intelligence, what period of time her Department considers a regular interval.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Work and Pensions: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752206", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752204, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21603", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of the Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme on religious minority groups in the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme: North West", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752204", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752203, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21602", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of building repair costs on inner-city congregations of listed places of worship.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752203", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752202, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21601", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme on religious minority groups.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752202", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752336, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21600", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, who the recipients were of grants from the Listed Places of Worship Scheme in Essex since 2001; and how much each recipient received.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme: Essex", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752336", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752335, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21599", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2024 to Question 18359 on Cabinet Office: Infrastructure, which existing projects will count towards the target of 150 major infrastructure ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Infrastructure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752335", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752334, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21598", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what representations he has made to the (a) Chinese Government and (b) authorities in Hong Kong on reports of the Hong Kong Police offering rewards for the arrests of pro-dem", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hong Kong: Demonstrations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752334", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752333, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21597", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to implement the measures agreed in the Leaders\u2019 Statement and Samoa Communique at the Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting on 26 Octo", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752333", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752332, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21596", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what contacts his Department has had with Hayat Tahrir al-Sham in Syria.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Syria: Hay'at Tahrir Al-Sham", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752332", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752330, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21594", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the progress on delivery of each of the Sustainable Development Goals by (a) the UK and (b) other governments.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sustainable Development", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752330", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752329, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21593", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the proposals from Brazil during their Presidency of the G20 for an 18th Sustainable Development", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Brazil: G20", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752329", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752328, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21592", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions he has had with his South African counterpart on that country's objectives for the G20 Presidency.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "South Africa: G20", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752328", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752326, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21590", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answers of 6 December 2024 to Question 16721 and of 9 December 2024 to Question 16720 on British Indian Ocean Territory: Sovereignty, for what reason he was u", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "British Indian Ocean Territory: Sovereignty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752326", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752325, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21589", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 22 November 2024 to Question 14333 on Diego Garcia: Military Bases, which Departments will incur the costs of the (a) lease of the military base, (b) economic partnership and (c) Chagossian", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Military Bases: Diego Garcia", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752325", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752299, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21587", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students took higher technical education courses at Institutes of Technology in each academic year between 2018-19 and 2023-24.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Institutes of Technology", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752299", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752298, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21586", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to support Institutes of Technology.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Institutes of Technology", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752298", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752297, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21585", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2024 to Question 16135 on Crown Prosecution Service and with reference to the The Better Case Management Revival Handbook, published in January 2023, what steps her Department", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Crown Prosecution Service", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752297", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752296, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21584", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to extend Continuity of Education Allowance to all service personnel.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Private Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752296", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752295, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21583", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will review the uplift in Continuity of Education Allowance for costs associated with VAT on independent school fees after six months.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Private Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752295", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752294, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21582", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to increase retention of service personnel.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Labour Turnover", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752294", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752293, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21581", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the uplift in Continuity of Education allowance for costs associated with VAT on independent school fees.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Private Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752293", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752292, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21580", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to maintain (a) Service Family Accommodation and (b) training base accommodation in Gosport.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "DM Gosport", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752292", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752315, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21579", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to monitor trends in Education Health and Care Plan applications by local authority area.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752315", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752314, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-08T00:00:00", "uin": "21578", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department is collecting data on trends in the number of in-year school applications in each local authority area.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Admissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752314", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752313, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21577", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the average fees charged by independent schools for the term starting in (a) January 2024, (b) September 2024 and (c) January 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Education: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752313", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752289, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21575", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to her Department's press release entitled One of the largest mental health trials launches in schools, published on 4 February 2019, what the results of those trials were.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Mental Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752289", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752287, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21573", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to NHS England's statistics entitled Mental Health of Children and Young People in England, 2023 - wave 4 follow up to the 2017 survey, published on 21 November 2023, whether he plan", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health: Children and Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752287", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752192, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21572", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to promote STEM courses across the education system.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "STEM Subjects: Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752192", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752228, "askingMemberId": 1576, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21571", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many minors were murdered by family members in 2022-23; and what steps she plans to take to help prevent such deaths.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homicide: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752228", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752246, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21568", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has made an assessment of the potential impact of requiring Electronic Travel Authorisation on (a) BN(O) and (b) Hong Kong passport holders seeking sanctuary.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electronic Travel Authorisations: British National (Overseas) and Hong Kong", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752246", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752198, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21566", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking to support mine clearance programmes in Sri Lanka.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sri Lanka: Land Mines", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752198", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752256, "askingMemberId": 410, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21565", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of Airbus not completing the takeover of the Spirit AeroSystems site in Belfast on jobs (a) at Airbus and (b) throughout the supply chain in (i) Northe", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Spirit Aerosystems: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752256", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752255, "askingMemberId": 410, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21564", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the break up of Spirit on the Northern Ireland economy.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Spirit Aerosystems: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752255", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752254, "askingMemberId": 410, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21563", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps he is taking to support Spirit AeroSystems (a) production and (b) jobs.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Spirit Aerosystems: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752254", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1752227, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-01-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-01-07T00:00:00", "uin": "21562", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many Great Western Railway trains were cancelled due to lack of drivers in December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Great Western Railway", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1752227", "method": "GET"}]}]